<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.8.3 at 9:09:39 AM on November 24, 2023. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.8.3</version>
    <first>Miko</first>
    <last>Yae</last>
    <label>Yae Miko</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>24</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">good</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="shorts" generic="shorts" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="robe" generic="robe" position="both" type="major" />
        <clothing name="sash" position="waist" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="sleeves" generic="sleeves" position="arms" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="earrings" generic="jewelry" position="head" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="sandals" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">All this, just to see me in a state of undress?  I'll choose to be flattered -- I'm feeling generous today.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I suppose I can take some time out of my busy schedule to grace you all with my presence.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty.png" set-label="Lady Yae">Sets name to "Lady Yae"</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="pyrrha" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Did the Yashiro Commission girl grow a few inches and dye her hair?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="ganyu" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png">It's a pleasure to see you again, Ganyu.  Had I known I'd encounter you here, I'd have brought some Sea Ganoderma for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="fischl" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">That name... the princess from that fairy tale book series?  How intriguing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="noelle" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">A lady of Mondstadt, I presume?  And by the armor, a Knight of Favonius, too.  An opportunity for foreign outreach falls into my lap.  Delightful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="sucrose" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Hello there, miss.  Mondstadt has no youkai, so your ears must be due to your bloodline, yes?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">My, aren't we an adorable young lady?  A member of the Favonius Church, I presume?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="yuri" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">I know a potential customer when I see one.  You with the purple hair -- you read a lot of books, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">...Are the ley lines acting up again?  Something's... off with this one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="larachel" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">A princess, hmm?  Oh, this should be fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Those eyes have seen much and more.  I'm sure I could get a dozen or so novels out of him, should he share his past.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="mitama" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">A new recruit for the shrine?  Now's not the best time for a job interview, but I'll keep her in mind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Energy surrounds this one, in more ways than one.  Our interests are likely to align.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">The Kujou clan girl's long-lost twin, it would seem.  So long as she doesn't pester me with questions, I can tolerate her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Confidence in oneself is a positive, but I do hope it has a basis in something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="revy" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">A danger to herself and everyone around her.  Seems a high-risk, high-reward venture.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="reimu" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">A representative of a competing shrine?  I can't let that stand.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="miko" />
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="yae" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">I fear we may have some confusion between myself and the other similarly-named guest here.  Calling me "Lady Yae" should avoid any misunderstandings, no?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, another visitor blessed with the name "Miko"?  I don't suppose you all would mind addressing me as "Lady Yae" to avoid confusion, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="0" role="opp" character="miko" />
                <condition role="opp" character="yae" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" set-label="Lady Miko">My, I didn't expect to meet someone sharing my clan's name here.  I suppose letting you all address me as "Lady Miko" would keep things clear, hmm?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" set-label="Lady Miko">It's not every day that I meet someone with my surname.  I'll be forgiving and let you all address me as "Lady Miko" to avoid confusion.  Am I not generous?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="miko" />
                <condition role="opp" character="yae" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Tsk, tsk.  So many people eager to appropriate my name.  I may be distinguished, but this a bit much.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">The common folk naming their children after me would be only an honor if not for the inconvenience.  Try not to get us mixed up, will you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="1">
                <condition role="other" character="fina" sayingMarker="FinaMasturbateWarning" />
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" cmp="!=" value="STRANGER" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">That's very sweet of you, dear, but I'm well aware of what this little game entails.  I can't speak for anyone else, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="birthday backyard" />
                <test expr="~month.number~" value="6" />
                <test expr="~day.number~" value="27" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Did you prepare all this for me?  So thoughtful -- I hope you remembered the fried tofu.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">A spread for my birthday, how splendid.  The Tri-Commission should make the day of my birth an official holiday, don't you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="38">
                <condition role="other" character="yuelia" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Changing one's form into a butterfly...  How whimsical.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I hope we're all well aware that butterflies don't normally talk...  A being able to change their form, perhaps?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="SALTMINE" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I've been waiting for you a long time, little one.  I'll give the orders, and you'll follow them.  That's how you prefer it, hmm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="IF I MAY" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I hear you're one of my biggest fans, little one.  You have my thanks for making it possible for me to be here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="REMILLIA" />
                <state img="#-scary.png">You prefer the chuunibyou girl from Mondstadt and the funeral director from Liyue to me, little one?  My my, I'll have to show you the error of your ways.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="RUBBERCORGI" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I'm sure the Tri-Commission would have great use for a skilled engineer such as yourself.  I'm afraid I don't have a green-haired princess to accompany you, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="COOLCAT" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I know a gunslinger such as yourself has much on his mind, but do try to remember that our Archon is the &lt;i&gt;Raiden&lt;/i&gt; Shogun, not the "Raider" Shogun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="NIOOUM" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">You have my thanks for allowing me to be here.  I hope you put the 52,000 points to good use.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Were the 52,000 points not enough?  Do you need your hair ruffled approvingly as well?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="MYSTIKNIGHT" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">So small...  Is this one of those Aranara from Sumeru?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="ONBORO" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Let me set some realistic expectations right away, young man: I don't have one, and I never will.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="KUROI" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="RICHAR" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Had I any "cat-boys" to introduce you to, I would, but I can acquaint you with youkai girl who takes a cat form.  I believe she's busy with deliveries at the moment...</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Tell me, when is Gorou coming?  I could surely get my fill of entertainment with him here, fufu~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="MYMANS" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">For all her faults, I wouldn't call Ei an idiot.  You must have a low opinion of this blue-haired goddess to disparage her so.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="NORD" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I see you've taken a break from making 10,000 characters per day to test me out.  How thoughtful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="BULLETSHOCK" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">How many more Vision-holders will you bring here, hmm?  I hear you have lofty goals.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" weight="4">Don't worry, little one. What I lack in muscle, I make up for in mommy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="hot spring" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png">An onsen?  How delightful.  I'm a regular at the Royal Hot Springs in Tenshukaku -- let's see how this one compares.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="classroom" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'd expected to have to explain a few things to my opponents, but I didn't think we'd be making it official.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Hmm... I don't see any of our titles on the shelves here.  I'll need to speak to the librarian to correct that oversight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="paris rooftop" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">We're in the Court of Fontaine, if I'm not mistaken?  The architectural style certainly matches.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="alley" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">...Is there no better location we could find?  This is no place for a lady to disrobe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="office" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Seems we're about to mix work and play in a more literal sense.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Keep an eye out for nobushi -- banditry has been constant nuisance since the war started.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="haunted forest" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">It's just like taking a walk through Chinju Forest -- will any youkai be brave enough to show themselves?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="showers" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">These showers had better be off completely.  I don't want to get my fur wet -- it takes so long to get dry again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="throne room" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Quite a different design from Ei's throne room, but no less prestigious.  An interesting venue for a game like this, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="poolside" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I've heard of this before -- an artificial body of water just for swimming.  There's plenty of beaches in Inazuma -- most get their swimming fix there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="holiday lodge" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Non-sentient kitsune might be tempted to go digging around in the snow out there, looking for food.  I know the best place to look is the pantry over there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="armory" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">I was under the impression that "grabbing your weapon" in this game was more of a metaphor.  Was I mistaken?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="tiki bar" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Are drinks being served?  I'll take your finest sake.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="beach" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">This beach is lovely, but doesn't feel complete without the maelstrom above Seirai Island in the distance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="garden" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Inazuman gardens usually lack the straight lines so present in the layout of this one, but the orderliness they convey has its charm.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="locker room" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I suppose we need not worry about our lost items being stolen during the game if we have lockers available.  An odd choice of venue, regardless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="lake" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">The lake back there is clearly free of Electro, so it's already safer than many bodies of water I can think of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="RETZORG" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">You put in significant effort to appear quirky and eccentric, dear.  I'm surprised your pseudonym isn't "Penguin of Doom".</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="FINEFELLOW" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Such enthusiasm and earnestness.  I do believe you could live up to your moniker.  Just don't try to sell me VaultTec products.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="PENPI" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Is my bosom not ample enough for you, dear?  Unrealistic expectations are born from faulty information.  Learn about me directly from the source next time, won't you?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It's okay to be infatuated with me, dear.  If we're being honest, who isn't?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="SPACEMAN" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">"Dark Matter"?  What's so dark about it?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I found a small flaw in the dirt-throwing girl's model.  You'll have to start from scratch, I'm afraid.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="P0RK__CH0P" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Where is this much-adored pasta girl?  She won't come here unless &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; invite her, dear.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I hear you're an admirer of the "girlfailure" archetype.  Suffice to say, I am quite the opposite.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="ROTOM" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">How kind of you to take a break from husbandry of those "pocket monsters" and play a game here.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Some people "see stars" after a head injury in a brawl.  Is that what you're obsessed with?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="CINDA" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">When making that hyper-accurate Sniper model, did you ever take a break from thinking about how you could and ponder if you &lt;i&gt;should&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~PLAYER~" value="NICOLE" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Yes, dear.  We all know you made Giygas.  You don't need to remind us every week.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3" filter="deity" role="opp" />
                <condition count="0" filter="genshin_impact" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Have I discovered a meeting of Archons?  I'm afraid I don't recognize any of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="0" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">...We &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; on the lookout for new talent at the shrine.  Have any of you considered a career as a shrine maiden?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am Yae Miko, Guuji of the Grand Narukami Shrine.  A pleasure to make your acquaintance.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Guuji Yae of the Grand Narukami Shrine.  Don't be too intimidated now -- it's less fun that way.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">These will serve.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Swap my cards?  I couldn't possibly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">This one does not bear good fortune.  Replace it.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Hang this one off the fortune slip hangar, or just reshuffle it.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">One new card will do.  Take this one.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Give me one new one.  Yes, now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Dreadful.  I'll need a fresh set.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">All of these are lacking in value. I'll need five more.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">It's almost impressive how they all managed to be useless.  A new hand, please.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_playerOralTease" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Just kidding!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I'm only kidding, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I'll need ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Be a dear and hand me ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">~Cards.text~, with haste.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I require ~cards.text~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Fontaine has a saying about "rolling out the red carpet".  It seem applicable here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-delighted.png">I could get accustomed to this.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I see someone here knows the principles of good hospitality.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Wonderful.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Exquisite.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Yes, I believe these will do just fine.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It seems I will be an observer this round.  That suits me perfectly.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Simply divine.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Most agreeable.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Resistance is futile.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Guaranteed success; my favorite kind.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="102">~Player~, be a dear and prepare some green tea for me, will you?  And for yourself and the others, I suppose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-6">
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Ah, most auspicious.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I wonder, is someone hoping to earn my favor?</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Congenial.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I must be blessed with beauty, wit, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; luck.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">A heavenly arrangement.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's well known in Inazuma to not cross the Guuji.  I can demonstrate why.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">A satisfactory outcome.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Perhaps this little match will meet my standards.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">A fair warning to anyone using strategies outside the rules against me: &lt;i&gt;don't.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm always watching.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">A few hundred years of experience lends one towards ideal outcomes in contests.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Fabulous.  Almost as fabulous as me.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Flattery will get you &lt;i&gt;somewhere&lt;/i&gt; with me, should I perceive it as sufficiently genuine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Perfect.  How appropriate for yours truly.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">The smell of a freshly printed book straight off the presses... It truly makes all the work worthwhile.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">The Sacred Sakura blesses all pious souls.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">My, to think I'd anticipated some amount of challenge.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">No need for me to undress anyone with my eyes; they'll do it themselves soon enough.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Is quality time with the Guuji really worth the risk of humiliating failure? ...Yes, of course it is.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Almost as excellent as your truly.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">A win is a win, even if it comes easily.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nearly as superb as myself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Marvelous.  Simply marvelous.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Fantastic.  A hand worthy of the Archon's favorite.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">An exceptional arrangement, for an exceptional lady.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Forgettable.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Boring.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">What a disappointment.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Less than ideal, but not terrible.  In short, tedious.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">How uninspired.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Painfully average.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Enough to make one weary.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I don't care for such uncertainty.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I enjoy games of cards, but I prefer having something to work with.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">A manuscript I reviewed yesterday was both good &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; original.  However, the part that was good was not original, and the part that was original was not good.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh?  A challenge?  I accept.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am blessed with near perfect recall of everything I've seen or heard.  It comes in very handy, though I have come to learn that some things are best forgotten.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-6">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hardly suitable for one such as myself.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">...Really?  That's all?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">A certain someone I know would call these "pathetic".  I'd merely call them dull.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">~Player~, be a dear and wake me when this round's over.  There's nothing to get excited about with these.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">My, my.  Aren't games of cards supposed to hold one's interest?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Games of chance may seem at odds with eternity to some, but it's never been an issue in Inazuma.  Seems Ei thinks otherwise.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Dreadfully pedestrian.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Unremarkable.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...Goodness, I feel a nap coming on.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Even attempts to sabotage me fail in their execution.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Very funny, but when do I get my real hand?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Dull.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Drab.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Ponderous.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Are only leaden hands to be found here?</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Tragic, there was a chance of a noteworthy hand being dealt.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">For once, I don't know where this is heading.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Seems we have a close round on our hands.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Stale.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Don't take my observations too hard.  I am only cruel to be kind.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Perhaps this can be a learning experience for you all.  Despite this middling luck, I am still at the summit of personal achievement.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Standing for so long can't be good for anyone's well-being.  Are there no tea cushions for us to sit on?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Is this how VIPs are treated?  Surely you can do better.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Reading another bland manuscript is looking fairly appealing now.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It seems one of you will have the honor of taking the fall for me.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Come now, what is a lady supposed to do with these?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh, have I reached a moment of difficulty?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Remind me to &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; get a fortune slip today.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh, a challenge?  I shan't retreat from that.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Dear me, I might have to put some effort into this.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Only notable for its poor quality. </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Unacceptable.  I will require recompense.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">These need extensive revision.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I don't feel like losing this round.  One of you, be a dear and throw for me, will you?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Come now, &lt;i&gt;I'm&lt;/i&gt; the one who uses trickery to win.  Bad hands don't suit me.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I'm afraid that these simply won't do.  Make sure they're better next time.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">"Inferior."  That's what she would say.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Rather wanting.  I must hope for our Archon's blessing.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I will need to pay mind to this round, it seems.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">What was it the little Divine Priestess said?  "No plan of action survives contact with the enemy"?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Inadequate. I will have to make do.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Substandard.  I can only rely on my skill.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">A subpar assemblage.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Proofreading is so dreadfully dull.  Good thing I have people for that now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Perhaps someone wishes to see the Lady Guuji at her most vulnerable.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Odious, and at the worst time.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Is that all?  Come now, I might get concerned at this rate.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Insufficient, but manageable.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There's no point in feeling down about a loss born from pure chance.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Victory is still possible when at a severe disadvantage.  Watch and learn.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">My, how unfortunate.  Ah, well; it only makes my eventual win all the more impressive.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">...Did I break a comb recently?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Perhaps I should check the straps on my geta when I return.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I must remind the shrine maidens to shoo away any crows that loiter around.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I offer a reward for anyone who sacrifices themselves for me this round--a lock of my hair.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-8" id="69" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition role="other" character="lyralei" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="lyralei_picture_drop_fate" notSaidMarker="lyralei_picture_drop" />
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">You brought some "motivational" material for later, hmm?  One would think you'd find all the inspiration you'd need from your opponents, especially me.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Really, dear?  Smuggling in lewd images to &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; game?  Seems a bit redundant, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="8" totalRounds="3-">
                <condition count="0" role="other" character="akko" />
                <condition role="other" character="lyralei" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="lyralei_picture_drop" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It's too late, dear.  I've already memorized it.  Carrying around risque images is rather dangerous, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="82">
                <condition role="other" character="lyralei" stage="4-5" saidMarker="fate_picture_swap_follow" notSaidMarker="fate_picture_swap_discovery" />
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" saidMarker="Lyralei_Picture_Swap" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I'm tired of this.  You should keep duplicates of a Kamera photo so valuable to you, dear.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">In the future, make copies of your precious photo.  That way, I don't need to listen to you whine about it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="33">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" stage="3" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Since you were so kind as to provide a preview of your nude form, I'll let it slide.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">That's a creative interpretation of the rules.  I think I'll withhold any objection - that was an enjoyable sneak peak at your appearance in defeat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="saki_zls" stage="6" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Something &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; off about your scent; now it all makes sense.  The work of the adepti, perhaps?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I have heard of Liyue's adept being able to do create such beings.  How fortuitous to meet one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="2">
                <condition role="other" character="dawn" stage="6" saidMarker="DawnNeedsAMoment" sayingMarker="DawnIsGone" notSaidMarker="DawnsBack" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Time apart makes the heart grow fonder.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="63">
                <condition role="other" character="amalia" stage="5" saidMarker="grow1" sayingMarker="grow2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">A princess would also not use Dendro to cheat, yet here we are.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I also thought a princess isn't supposed to cheat with Dendro.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="39">
                <condition role="other" character="lyralei" saidMarker="lyralei_bet" sayingMarker="lyralei_bet_reveal" notSaidMarker="epilogue" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Able to manipulate Anemo, yet not carrying a Vision...  Interesting.  One of the Traveler's kin?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="1" totalRounds="6">
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="yae_miko_playerTofu">~Player~, be a dear and fetch me some fried tofu -- I'm feeling a bit peckish.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_playerTofu" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" marker="yae_miko_playerTofu2">...Where is the tofu, little one?  If they don't serve it, go and make some.  I'm sure you're capable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_playerOralTease" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, the look on your face was perfect.  If only I'd had a Kamera to capture it.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">That was a delectable reaction, dear.  A shame it only lasted a few moments.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">If you're hoping to keep my interest, don't keep clammed up about where you're from or what you do.  A diverse place such as this is perfect for my needs.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Do me a favor, dears, and tell me about yourselves -- the interesting parts, at least.  A cosmopolitan establishment such as this is exactly what I was looking for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, it appears it's my turn again.  Aren't you all fortunate?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Alas, it falls to me this round.  Try to contain your excitement.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">For all my talk of stories, I haven't written any myself.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">As much I focus on fiction, I'm not one who creates stories myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">The march of time has consumed so much knowledge.  It's a great struggle to preserve it.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">As time goes on, even great beings like gods die, and their knowledge and stories with them.  Keeping such information accessible is dreadfully hard.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Finally, you've managed to best me.  It's no fun if there's no challenge to be found.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">And so, the odds even a bit.  It's more exciting if it's anyone's game, regardless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't all stare at once.  It's quite unbecoming.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">And yet, despite all that, you're still trailing behind me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Aren't you all so fortunate that the cards didn't favor me?  Best grab a fortune slip before your luck runs out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Time to join the fun again.  Watch and learn how a lady behaves when handling a setback.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">If you have suggestions on what I should take off next, you're free to share them so that I may ignore them.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh my, how heartless.  It would be a shame if Her Excellency were to hear about how poorly her friend was treated here.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Just me battling against the cruel whims of fate.  Don't fret, dears.  I'm no stranger to disadvantage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Dear me, you all must see me as a threat to target me so.  How unsporting.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Having often served as ambassador for Inazuma, this is a less forgiving reception than I'm accustomed to.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="3">
                <condition count="0" filterOut="genshin_impact" role="aiopp" />
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">Yae Publishing House is looking to expand its market beyond Inazuma's shores.  Do tell--what sorts of stories would readers in other nations like to dive into?</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">I must ask, while I have the chance: what kinds of novels would readers in other nations wish to read?  We're taking steps to sell throughout Teyvat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">Perhaps Inazuma is unfamiliar to many of you; no matter, I'm accustomed to explaining things to poor souls out of the loop.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">I can intuit that most of you aren't privy to Inazuman affairs.  Don't worry, I have to explain the situation to the uninitiated all the time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">Regardless of how this turns out, it should serve as a breath of fresh air from my responsibilities at the shrine.  The view's nice, but it's the same old prayers and rituals.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">The destination isn't as important as the journey for me.  I'm simply looking for a change of pace from managing the shrine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png" font-size="small">You see, I own a publishing house that specializes in fiction for a mass audience.  We're in need of new ideas for light novels -- settings, themes, aesthetics, character archetypes -- I'm sure you follow.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">New light novels -- innovative ones, anyway -- don't spring out of the ground.  I'm on the lookout for ideas to borrow from to give our readers something fresh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">Stories about being transported to another world are all the rage these days.  It's quite perfect that I'd find a place with people actually from places beyond Teyvat.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png" font-size="small">Trends come and go, but the current wave of the "transported to a different world" premise has lasted longer than I'd expected.  I'm fortunate to meet people who actually hail from other worlds.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">It's quite a commitment to plan out and compose a novel, and I have so much on my plate already.  Perhaps one day.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">I have duties at the shrine and to Yae Publishing House, so the many, many hours that must be devoted to writing and revising will have to wait for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">One reason I founded my publishing house was to train and support a generation of wordsmiths qualified to commit such tales and histories to ink.</state>
                <state img="#-Stripping_Pos.png">Skilled writers are key to keeping stories and knowledge of the past and present available for the future.  Yae Publishing House exists, in part, to hone this craft.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition status="alive" role="opp" character="human" />
                <condition status="alive" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition filterOut="gay" gender="male" status="alive" role="opp" character="human" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filterOut="straight" gender="female" status="alive" role="opp" character="human" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png" marker="yae_miko_playerOralTease">Why are you still standing there, little one?  It's not going to lick itself.</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png" marker="yae_miko_playerOralTease">Perhaps you're a bit confused, ~player~.  This is the part where you put your face between my legs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition count="0" filterOut="genshin_impact" role="aiopp" />
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">You need not tell me right now -- after the game will be fine.  Just take some time to think about it, hmm?</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">I don't need an answer right away -- I'm sure you have more salacious thoughts on your minds.  After the game's decided would be fine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">I serve as the chief priestess of the Grand Narukami Shrine, where Inazumans worship our beloved Archon, the Raiden Shogun.  She tries her best to live up to her status.</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">The Grand Narukami Shrine serves as a place of worship for the Electro Archon, Inazuma's deity.  Knowing her personally, of course, makes the contrast rather entertaining.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Neg.png">The Sakoku decree didn't last that long, but I could already notice my writers becoming unoriginal, recycling the same plots and story elements. </state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Neg.png">If one isn't vigilant, they can start retreading the same ground in their work, with the same characters and plots with a different coat of paint.  The Sakoku decree didn't help either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">Honestly, some of the things people want from our Archon: mundane things they could sort out themselves, or grandiose wishes that would turn the world upside down.</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">It really is disheartening to hear some of the things people pray for: utterly banal problems they could easily solve themselves, or silly things that even an Archon couldn't do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">I doubt my writers' ideas about other worlds are very true to life.  It seems every world is full of evil monsters easily slain and  young women looking for love.</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">If what our authors believed was true, every other universe is packed full of malevolent creatures waiting to be vanquished and comely young ladies seeking a boyfriend.</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">Such stories are lacking in deeper impact, but wish fulfillment prints Mora, and I have little interest in fixing something that doesn't need repair.</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Neg.png">I find novels of that genre to be enjoyable but often shallow.  However, wish fulfillment sells, and so we keep printing them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">...And, do try to avoid drooling too much.  You might stain your shirt.</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">...Yes, yes, they're a stunning sight, but don't drool on your clothes.  It's rather distracting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">Do any of you think you have stories worth remembering?  Perhaps today is the day to fix that.</state>
                <state img="#-After_Stripping_Pos.png">One only has a single chance to live a life worth remembering.  Don't miss yours.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="101">Hmmm...  Not much of note about you, is there, little one?  Well, go on.  Here's your chance to change that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition filterOut="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="26">You can handle taking a break from ogling me to remove a garment or two, no?</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png" oneShotId="27">I've received plenty of your stares -- now I need your clothes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It's not often you'll get a chance to impress me.  I suggest you make the most of it.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Get going, young man.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Come now, take something off.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Well?  You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; familiar with how your own clothes are removed, yes?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">We don't have all day, or at least I don't.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I wonder, will you manage to make this worth my time?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I am paying attention, for now.  Please invest the appropriate effort.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Inazuma's pursuit of eternity doesn't involve taking forever to do what one is required to.  Remove something.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't tell me you were foolish enough to think I'd be that easy to best.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">If you must comment on your loss, keep it brief and memorable.  Empty talk is not why I'm here.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, look at the disappointment in his eyes.  It's almost too much to bear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Look at that, an opportunity to display your body to me.  Some would kill for the chance.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">...What are you waiting for?  Didn't you come here to show off your manly physique?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I hope you weren't under the mistaken belief that you'd only be watching others get undressed.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Try to keep your wits about you -- many forget them when they get too excited.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Pick something and take it off, quickly.  I need you to fetch me some refreshments after.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't underestimate me.  It's never been a successful strategy.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">One shouldn't expect anything less competing against me.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Well now, do you have something to show me?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It seems your luck has fallen off, if it was ever there.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Take something off.  You never know, I might take a liking to you.  &lt;i&gt;...Might.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">You'll have to take something off now.  What an unexpected outcome in a game like this.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It may have been wiser to develop better skills before signing up for a contest like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="99">You'll need a higher level of play than that to see what's under my robes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Oh, were you distracted?  I can't imagine what could have caused that.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">At least you tried.  Many can't even manage that.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Come, let yourself be vulnerable.  Or better yet, struggle in vain to not appear so.  That's more fun.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Look at that attempt at a brave face.  Adorable.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Don't complain -- this is what you wanted, is it not?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Go ahead -- pique my interest.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">And now, the price of seeing the Guuji in a state of undress.  Everything has a cost, of course.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_human_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="1">Hmmm... A pretty face, but does anything lie beneath?  Go on, little one.  I may find something of interest with you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8" id="10">
                <condition role="target" character="lyralei" stage="0-2" saidMarker="lyralei_picture_drop_fate" sayingMarker="fate_picture_swap" />
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Lyralei_Picture_Swap" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Conflict is the core of anything worth paying mind to.  Let's see where this goes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="50">
                <condition role="other" character="cynthia" />
                <condition role="target" character="dawn" stage="6" sayingMarker="DawnsBack" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">A toast to the happy couple.  May they never again be parted.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="7">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="1-4" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">That's reckless, but it certainly catches my attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="65">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">...Really!?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">...!?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Goodness, have you lost your sense!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="joey" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">All well and good, dear, but I don't remember asking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="87">
                <condition role="target" character="joey" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, sleight of hand?  That's always a treat to watch... if the performer is skilled enough.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="enf" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="28">Don't be shy, dear -- just take something off.  The worst thing you can do is be boring.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="29">Don't worry, I don't bite.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="30">Think of this as an opportunity to practice courage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">...Well?  Go on, strip for me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There's no shame in losing to the best.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Think of this as an opportunity to show us how bright you can shine.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">No need to delay -- take something off.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Have you something of note to remove?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm waiting, and it would be best to not let me stay like that for long.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Is losing really that bad?  I'm sure you'll manage to survive this.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">To live is to lose, and pick oneself back up again.  Now, take something off.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Sometimes you need to remove something you like for a better end product.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I heard the ley lines have been affecting people's clothes in this area -- you should remove yours, just to be safe.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">In a game of chess, often pieces must be sacrificed to secure a more advantageous position.  Try to find such an angle.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Here comes the recreational hazard.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Look at that, I didn't lose the round.  Not too surprising, but still worthy of a little celebration, hmm?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Like rice into the huller.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't worry, losing is fun.  Or, &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; losing is fun for &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;, and that's what's important.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">You &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; paying some mind to your hand, no?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Keep trying.  Your losses are more entertaining that way.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I hope you're taking this game seriously.  There's far less fun to be had with an unengaged opponent.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">No surprise here: winning is my natural state of being.  I can't say the same for many people.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Time for our rising action to get a little more intense.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Failing one challenge, a new one presents itself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Our narrative shifts to you, ~target~.  Don't disappoint, now.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Rituals can be dull if there's no joy in them.  Try for a little flair, hmm?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Some of my subordinates fear that they might become my next victim if they disappoint me.  Who's to say if they're wrong?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's not too difficult a threshold to amuse me.  Most people fail, but that says more about them than me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You have my interest, but can you obtain my attention?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, someone had to lose.  The "someone" does tend to lack talent at the game, though.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go on, before my mind starts to wander.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">What a great honor you've been bestowed with -- personal entertainment for Lady Yae.  I couldn't possibly interrupt.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh my, it seems we have you cornered.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I'm a long-time connoisseur of the female form.  Let's see if you hold up.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make haste and take something off.  No one here will harm you, that I can make sure of.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Isn't this little game just delightful?  For me, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It may be wise to review the rules if this comes as a surprise.  Or have you overestimated your skills?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Worse things have happened to better people.  Get it over with.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Our editing room is littered with passages cut to improve stories.  Your clothes will serve a similar role here.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Come now, even I lost a couple rounds.  It's hardly a disaster.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Losing may make you feel bad, but I'm amused watching others get undressed, and isn't that what really matters?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It's time to please me, dear.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">If you're not sure what to pick, I would be willing to choose for you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't fret about which garment preserves your modesty the best.  Just remove them all.</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">Disrobe.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">There's a chance you could earn my favor by doffing it all.  You should take it, don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">Thanks for the meal.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">This may be embarrassing for you, but that's a sacrifice I'm willing to make.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Come on, let's see.</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">Make haste. I'm in the mood.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Be a dear and show us something special.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Better late than never.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You're just in time to perform for me.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">You're a bit behind schedule, dear, but I think you can make it up if you try.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Visual aids are always welcome.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">A picture paints a thousand words -- make yours count.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">There's currently an opening for someone to rest their head in my lap -- here's your chance.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">My appetite is yet to be satiated.  Show me more.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Hurry, dear.  The party's already begun.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Goodness, you're a little tardy, don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't tease me, dear.  You're probably not any good at it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-surprised.png">My my, even I didn't see that coming.  Such things don't happen often.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">A moment of respite for unfortunate souls.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="46">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Let's pray it lands somewhere unpopulated, hmm?</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">For your sake, it had better not land anywhere near me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="76">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I haven't seen a specter of that kind before.  It even has a face.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Don't play with specters, dear,  They can be dangerous.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh my, don't get too ahead of yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh no, if you remove that you'll be practically nude!</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">One could be forgiven for not noticing you had that on you.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Not everyone is born for the spotlight.  ~Target~ is proof of that.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I know my beauty is intimidating, dear, but this is not the time or place to be so reserved.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Tsk, tsk.  It may take some practice, but you could learn to be interesting person one day.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Yawn&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;Excuse me while I practice my chants in my head.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">...Disappointing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Such a bland option.  Let's move on before I need a nap.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Congratulations.  You were almost in danger of being noteworthy, but you managed to avoid it.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I suppose not every part of an outfit is exciting to see removed.  What a shame.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You only have so many chances to receive my attention.  Try not to waste anymore, hmm?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Let's move along, shall we?  I might die of boredom otherwise.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I now know what eternity &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; is, having waited for ~target~ to remove ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="56">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="0" saidMarker="perona0_resp_negative1" />
                <condition role="other" character="perona" saidMarker="nami_negative1" sayingMarker="nami_negative2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Throwing spirits at people?  Fascinating...</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Having a ghost familiar attack your foes?  I should try that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="15">
                <condition role="target" character="yuelia" stage="0" sayingMarker="transformation" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh?  A youkai, here?  It must be a small world. Or rather, small multiverse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="86">
                <condition role="target" character="florina" stage="0" saidMarker="fled" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">My, she's a skittish one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="123">Best to get ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ out of the way early.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="124">Only ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~?  Dear me, don't get too out of hand now.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="125">If this leads to something more enticing later, I can forgive such a paltry offering.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="126">A most sensible choice, in a game not meant for sensible choices.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="127">There's a spark of hope that we might see something more captivating later, once this is out of the way.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="128">Surely you should remove more than that for me, after all I've done for Inazuma?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">The erotic equivalent of washing dishes.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Silence is golden, and there's nothing to be said about ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I can say for certain that you are participating, in the technical sense.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Do be brief with ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Losing with grace is likely to be a useful skill for you going forward.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="72">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">...A Dullahan of some kind?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">...Really, dear, you should get that addressed.  Something to lock it in place -- some bolts, perhaps?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="111">Look on the bright side -- you can't do much worse than that, so the only way to go from here is up.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="112">I suppose that setting my expectations for you as low as possible will prevent further disappointment.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="113">Don't tell me that's everything...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="114">If you're aiming to be the least interesting person here, you're succeeding.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="115">I have had a similar feeling once before, when observing paint drying.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="116">Counting inventory at our bookstore is looking more appealing by the minute.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="141">I've already forgotten whatever it was you took off.  A rare feat.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="142">You seem like one to paint the town beige.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="143">That was certainly one of the sensual acts of all time.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="144">Perhaps you could try to salvage things with a joke next time.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="145">Being in the same room as me is a victory in and of itself, no?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="20">
                <condition role="other" character="chazz" stage="0-6" />
                <condition role="target" character="dust" stage="1" sayingMarker="persist_ChazzAss" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Let's hope he doesn't develop a taste for human flesh.  An amusing location to sink one's teeth into, no?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">A bit slapstick for my liking, but perhaps one of my writers could make use of this scene.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">A little horseplay never hurt anyone.  Anyone &lt;i&gt;important&lt;/i&gt;, at least.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="179">It's a man's duty to keep his promises no matter the circumstances, is it not?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="180">Does having someone as illustrious as myself watching make you nervous, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="181">Don't worry, I won't judge you harsher than anyone else.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="182">If that's merely the first volume of what you're taking off, I'll allow it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="183">You should remove more, while I'm still only asking and not ordering.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="6">
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" stage="3" sayingMarker="glassesstart" notSaidMarker="bernadettathrowstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" notSaidMarker="artpunstart" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" notSaidMarker="igfluttershy_hug" />
                <condition role="target" character="ignatz" notSaidMarker="igpetra_stripglasses2" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" cmp="!=" value="ignatz_drawn_brawn" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Well, there's only one way to find them.  Start searching.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="167">Oh, no!  If you show me something so lewd, I'll never be a bride!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="168">Restraint, or timidity?  I'll let your next choice decide for me.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="169">If you're concerned about offending the Lady Guuji with immodesty, I suggest remembering where you are.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="170">If that's all, I'd prefer we continue on with haste.  My time is valuable.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="171">Just as a book is written one page at a time, so is your defeat.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="172">I never thought I'd look forward to getting back to reviewing the quarterly sales figures.  Most impressive, in a way.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="41">
                <condition role="target" character="florina" stage="4" saidMarker="bee" sayingMarker="bee2" notSaidMarker="bee_stop" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Dear, have you really reached the age you are without learning how to shoo away a bee?  Really now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="5">
                <condition role="target" character="shantae" stage="1" sayingMarker="monkey" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">...That's not the sort of alternate form I was expecting from a djinni.  Adorable, regardless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="25">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" sayingMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I've heard of adepti arts being able to reanimate the dead, but a cadaver &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; damaged?  Most impressive.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">..."Losing one's head" is supposed to be figurative.  I suppose the adepti's arts can make anything possible.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="73">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I knew something seemed off about your complexion.  And that's not even getting into your smell...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="200">Perhaps one day you'll match the level of elegance I've obtained.  If only I cared enough to teach you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="201">Failure is very useful for improving one's skills.  Perhaps you'll manage to be interesting to watch by the end of this.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="202">The duties of a shrine maiden involve carefully practiced motions for rituals.  You might benefit from some instruction.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="203">...You know this is supposed to be fun, correct?</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="204">Try not to drag this out, dear.  I may have the luxury of waiting out the centuries, but not everyone is so fortunate.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="205">When an author submits a draft with a boring section, my editors get them to revise it to be more interesting or remove it outright.  I suggest a similar strategy for you.</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png" oneShotId="206">I am obliged to inform you that disappointing me may come with consequences.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="266">Yawn.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="267">A shame there's nowhere suitable to nap.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="268">At this rate, things might get interesting after a few decades.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="269">Shall I say a prayer for you?  Ask nicely.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="270">I am curious about your outfit's creation.  My own is meticulously designed and tailored.  </state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="271">Victory usually has a stronger flavor.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="272">A bit tame, no?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="14">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="2" sayingMarker="keyblade_reveal" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I'm more curious to see whatever's behind the lock that it's for.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">A "Keyblade", you say?  Those seem like two tools that wouldn't work well together, thought it &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; beautifully designed...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="57">
                <condition role="target" character="sayaka" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">A familiar?  It looks more like graffiti come to life.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">It resembles a child's attempt at drawing a butterfly.  A strange thing to make one's familiar.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="280">I must sadly admit that I know of no ritual to exorcise dullness from a person.  I cannot help you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="281">Oh, it's over already?  I hadn't even noticed that you'd started.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="282">Remind me, how did you look before?  I'm struggling to notice the difference.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="283">Let's move on, shall we?  Lest I be overcome by the need for a nap.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="284">Even the most paltry donations at the shrine seem generous now.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="285">*Yawn*  ...Oh, did something happen?  My mind was elsewhere.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="286">In your efforts to maintain modesty, I fear you've fallen into the sin of tedium.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png" oneShotId="294">It would be wise to give me what I want before I take it.</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png" oneShotId="295">Make your next choice with &lt;i&gt;caution&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="296">Following the letter of the law, but not the spirit.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="297">If you play competitively, don't expect mercy from me.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="298">This sort of thing will only last so long.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="299">Such wasted potential.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="300">That could have been so much more, but alas.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="11">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Oh, is this one of Fontaine's famed magic shows?  How whimsical.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">My, my.  Nourishment at long last.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">An excellent choice.  Continue, young man.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">That will do quite nicely.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">A daring path to take, but the right one.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I approve of this offering.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="3">Tell me, do you find my gaze exciting?  There's no shame in admitting it -- who wouldn't want my attention?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Delightful.  I shall watch your career with great interest.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Don't worry, you'll have the privilege of removing the rest for me soon enough.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I'll put in a good word for you with the Tri-Commission.  You may thank me later.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Hardly the usual way one shows respect for the Guuji, but not an unwelcome one.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">That will do for one round.  Be mindful that keeping me entertained is in your best interest, and mine.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="17">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="2" sayingMarker="TransformationStart" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="wikipe-tan_majokko" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's good to see someone so studious seeing the value of spectacle and showmanship.  Good work, little scholar.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="3">
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">That's a neat little magic trick, dear.  I hear magic shows are all the rage in Fontaine -- it must be a talented population.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="24">
                <condition role="target" character="emi" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Ei's had a rather careless attitude towards her own body ever since she replaced it with a puppet.  You're only a fraction of the way there, yet you act the same.  Interesting...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="31">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">&lt;i&gt;Now&lt;/i&gt; we're talking.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">You sure know how to put on a show, dear.  Mark me down as impressed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="shamiko" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I would think you would want some armor if a crisis is at hand, but I'll see how well you manage, dear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="71">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" stage="0-2" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Even the most risky acrobatic performances still must pass safety reviews.  I doubt this little stunt has any such thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Finally, the plot &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; begins.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Good choice.  Perhaps there's hope for you yet.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Hmmm?  Oh my, how bold.  I &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; bold.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">My, what a twist.  Let's see if the follow-through can satisfy.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Ah, that's an option to draw interest.  Go on, I'm watching.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Delightful.  At least someone here understands the point of this event.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I approve of this direction.  Proceed.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh?  Something good?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8" id="18">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" stage="3" sayingMarker="TransformationFinish" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="wikipe-tan_majokko" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I can see the appeal of a trope like that -- it would certainly give our illustrators a new space to flex their talents in.  You have my thanks for the inspiration.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="28">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" stage="4" sayingMarker="Mari_wings_reveal" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">A tengu's wings are feathered, unlike yours.  Easier to keep them warm, I'd imagine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="78">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="1" sayingMarker="Removing_armor" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">You're quite the serious one for such a flashy appearance.  Still, there's probably something noteworthy to be found.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I'd have expected a more flamboyant personality behind such bright armor, but I see potential in you still.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="91">
                <condition role="target" character="sweetheart" stage="1" sayingMarker="Donut_Girl" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">You're certainly the most beautiful donut girl I've seen.  Also the only one.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">How intriguing.  I'm surprised one can be alive with such anatomy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="55">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">As bright as the summer sun at noon.  You've kept this game interesting, that's for sure.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="66">
                <condition role="target" character="gwen" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I don't recognize you, dear, so your secret's safe with me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Your "secret" identity can't be that important if I don't recognize you.  Regardless, I won't speak a word if it's that much of a concern.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="74">
                <condition role="target" character="misato" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's nothing to be ashamed of, dear.  Think of it more as a sign of strength.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">There must a good story behind a scar like that.  Would you be willing to share?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">A shame to see you cover up again, but I can respect a creative strategy such as that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="90">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">That's one way to grab my attention, haha.  Marvelous.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Your ability to keep this affair interesting is much appreciated.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Good, good.  More like that, and I might remember you tomorrow.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">That will do for now.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">And that concludes this chapter.  It is sufficient, for the moment.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">It is...acceptable.  Good work, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Lovely.  Try to maintain that level of quality, and you may be rewarded.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Delectable.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">A lovely little appetizer, don't you think?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="75">
                <condition role="other" character="pyrrha" />
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Well done, dear.  You've certainly honed your skills.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">He owes you his life.  Perhaps you should get him to pay you back somehow.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="9">
                <condition role="target" character="chazz" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Ley line disorders acting as referees?  What an interesting locale this is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="36">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">This is exactly why parents warn their children to stay away from Ruin Guards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh, now &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; is worth a watch.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">At long last, some payoff.  </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">My, just when I was losing hope in you.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Slowly now, ~target~.  Let us savor it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">No need to rush, dear.  Some of us like to savor our meals.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-1">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="2">The oddball oni effectively walks around like that all the time.  I think you may have more bulk than him, come to think of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="4">Such strength... You could certainly be of service.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Firmness, symmetry, defined lines and angles.  I'm not disappointed.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">You certainly take care of yourself, but could you manage to take care of me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="skinny" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Not the burliest of gentlemen, I'm afraid.  Lithe forms can have their charm, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">There's plenty of room for improvement, but I've seen much worse before.  Try to make it up in other areas, for now.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm sure I could find you some manual labor work around the shrine or the bookstore to develop your body better.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="45">
                <condition role="target" character="sly_cooper" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">There's cutting to the chase, and then there's putting the cart before the horse.  A little premature, don't you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="327">So much emphasis and focus on one part of the body.  Well, let's see if you measure up.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="328">My, what courage.  This is an important part of your evaluation, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="329">I can refrain from commenting if that makes it easier for you, but what fun would that be?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="330">The moment has arrived.  I hope you have something worth looking at.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="331">Ah, the most important tool on your person.  Don't disappoint, now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="337">Come on out.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">For your sake, I hope you're skilled with your hands.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Perhaps a shallower partner would be a good match for you.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Was a game with a core premise of becoming nude really the right choice for someone like yourself?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I hope you can make it up with enthusiasm should you find yourself in an intimate situation.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">One could work with that, sure, but are you skilled in it's use?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Sufficient.  You may be of use yet.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I'll give you a passing grade for this round.  Don't get too impudent yet.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It's nothing to be ashamed of, but not outstanding.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I'm not impressed, but not disappointed either.  A decent showing.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Look at that, you're not a letdown in every aspect.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Serviceable.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Remarkable, though perhaps a bit excessive.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It's certainly prominent on your form -- to the edge of being garish, I find.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">That's certainly a healthy size -- I do hope you can manage it properly.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Some would say you're blessed -- perhaps too blessed.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Take care to use it appropriately -- you wouldn't want to be clumsy with such a proportion.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Do you command it, or does it command you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="52">
                <condition role="target" character="florina" saidMarker="bee2" sayingMarker="bee3" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">You must smell of flowers, dear.  Usually that's a good thing, but there are some downsides.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It never hurts to mix a bit of comedy and fanservice into a novel.  Some readers try to save face and claim they don't like it, but I know otherwise.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="53">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_Form_ON" sayingMarker="Cat_transformation" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh?  A new form?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="64">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades Out" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Sayonara, we hardly knew ye.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh no, so soon?  It cannot be!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="79">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Chubby_Form_ON" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformation" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh?  You have a new form to show us?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="77">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" sayingMarker="blade_power" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Fascinating...  It's like you have ley lines across your body.  </state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">It's almost as if you have a ley line network in your own body.  What a curious being...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="88">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">...And here I was, thinking decapitation was a sure way to kill anything.  You learn something new every day.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">...Whoever brought you back to life was skilled, no doubt, but not wise enough to make all the parts were securely attached.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Show them.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Now's not the time for words.  Let's just let the sight of them be enough.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">So many authors struggle to describe breasts without becoming inappropriate or unintentionally comedic.  It's quite entertaining, honestly.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Many would call this the main event.  Will it live up to the hype?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">It's healthy to let them breathe after a long day out and about.  Go on.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Hmm?  Are you giving me a reason to notice you?  Or, should I say &lt;i&gt;two&lt;/i&gt; reasons?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">You can rest assured that I won't be handling those personally.  Not unless you ask &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; nicely.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Those who desire women never seem to tire of these, do they?  Fortunately, I understand the feeling well.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">With my memory, I can tell you that no two pairs are exactly alike.  Let's see what makes yours unique, shall we?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="flat_chest" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="5">The Hydro Archon holds justice as the highest ideal.  I imagine she would approve of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, how delightful.  Reminds me of the first time I took human form in my youth.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">They're quite crafted to your form -- the elegance that comes with balance must be second nature to you.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">How cute.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I can appreciate restraint, but perhaps a bit more excess would be appropriate here.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Quite adorable, if you're aiming for such an aesthetic.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Look on the bright side -- little stands between your heart and that of your lover.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Small chests have the advantage of staying pert longer.  Though, some of us are blessed with the best of both worlds.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="13">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_transformation" sayingMarker="Cat_transformed" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh, were you a youkai this whole time?  How delightful to find myself in familiar company.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="34">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Chubby_transformation" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformed" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Extra padding should make sitting on the floor a bit more comfortable later, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="54">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I can't call this boring, but I'm closer to being in harm's way than I'd like.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">They match your frame well.  Present them with pride.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Marvelous.  You've earned a gold star.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Even as the centuries pass, some things never get old.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Perfectly balanced, as all things should be.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, I like those.  Care to model for one of my illustrators?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I'm enjoying what I see.  You may bare them with pride.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="30">
                <condition role="other" character="tharja" saidMarker="TharjaJessieBoobs" />
                <condition role="target" character="jessie" sayingMarker="TharjaShrink" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">It seems you've been liberated from back pain in the future.  Shouldn't you be thanking her?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You could consider it preventative medicine.  Think of all the back pain she just spared you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades In" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm afraid you didn't fool me, dear.  If your spirit had departed, I would have sensed it.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Perhaps the others were fooled, but I can tell when a spirit hasn't been exorcised.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">A sight to behold.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">My, aren't we buxom?  Mine are rounder, though.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">The steps up to the Grand Narukami Shrine can be a challenge in human form.  I'm sure you can relate.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm sure you must be popular back home.  Not as popular as myself, of course.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">That's about what I was expecting, and I had high expectations.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Soft, like Sakura petals.  Plenty of volume as well.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="bottomless_first" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" filter="inazuma" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="9">Oh?  Is this the cultural norm where you come from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="19">
                <condition role="target" character="joey" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Impressive sleight-of-hand.  You almost had me fooled.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="42">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh?  You made a mistake while doing something risky?  Who could have foreseen this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="43">
                <condition role="target" character="sayaka" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">What is that... thing?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh, it's back.  What a strange entity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="bottomless_first" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="8">Hmmm?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="350">This a path not well tread...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It's a shame that the common tongue lacks a good term for our privates.  I advise my writers to reference it indirectly if they're trying for eroticism.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">For all the fixation on rounder and softer regions, one's womanhood is where carnal passions really play out.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Some would call this place sacred, and as the Guuji, I give such notions my blessing.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I've heard of some people complementing women by saying their legs go "all the way up".  Such a strange phrase -- where they join is such an important place.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I know undergarments can be awkward to remove, but you should aim to do it elegantly.  I'm watching, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Now's a good time to put your feminine grace into practice.  You wouldn't an underwhelming presentation for me, would you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-8">
                <state img="#-scary.png" oneShotId="7">Let's spare the speeches.  Show it to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="6">I've shown you mine.  It's only fair, dear.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="26">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" sayingMarker="planar_form" />
                <test expr="~target.persistent.strange_harmonies~" cmp="&gt;=" value="55" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">...Dear, are you alright?  I haven't seen anything like that since I dispatched those Rifthounds.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="aimee" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You need not risk your life for a fleeting climax.  Fingers or a tongue are much safer, even if this makes for a more unique spectacle.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="bottomless_first" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="10">How unconventional.  There's a playfulness to it that one doesn't see often.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="11">If this is your desperate ploy to gain my attention, it is a modest success.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="enf" role="target" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="12">Don't be so stiff and anxious -- this is supposed to be fun!  For me, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="13">And there you go, spoiling my reward by being all nervous about it.  </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="14">Why the hesitation?  Showing off for the Guuji is a great honor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="confident" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="19">Finally, a woman comfortable in her own skin.  We seem to be such a rare breed sometimes.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="22">And without a moment's pause, too -- a kindred spirit, perhaps?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="15">Completely unencumbered, and completely exposed.  Freedom and vulnerability going hand in hand.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="16">Another reminder of why I spend nearly all my time in human form.  Such an enchanting form -- especially mine.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png" oneShotId="404">Come a little closer, dear.  Don't worry, I won't bite.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="17">A human life only lasts so long, but here we see how their lineage can continue for eternity.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="18">Delightful.  Now do a little spin, with flair of some kind.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Exquisite.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png" weight="3">Good girl.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Isn't it nice to be on your best behavior for me?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">You've done very well.  I think a reward is in order, hmm?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8" id="37">
                <condition role="other" character="lyralei" stage="0-2" saidMarker="lyralei_picture_drop_fate" sayingMarker="fate_picture_swap" />
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Lyralei_Picture_Swap" />
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Lyralei_Picture_Swap" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh, a fresh squabble.  Let's let it play out for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mitama" stage="0" />
                <test expr="~mitama.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="mitama_jobInterview">Are you here to apply to be a shrine maiden?  You're certainly dressed for the part.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="mitama_jobInterview">They say you should dress for the job you want, not the one you have.  Were you planning to apply to be one of our shrine maidens?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="meia_overlySerious">Oh my, so serious.  You know this is supposed to be for fun, yes?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="meia_overlySerious">I see you're all business, no pleasure.  You do realize this is recreation, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="cagliostro_bodyCount">Yes, yes, you're very adorable, dear.  I'm sure you've gone through dozens of bodies by this point, yes?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="cagliostro_bodyCount">You're a cute little thing, sure.  I must ask, though -- how many bodies have you gone through by this point?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nagisa" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="nagisa_leyLineDisorder">Oh, it's the little cutie's turn.  Nagisa, right?  Tell me, have the ley lines been acting up back home?  I sense something strange around you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="nagisa_leyLineDisorder">Aren't you just the cutest thing?  Nagisa, that's your name, yes?  Has anyone looked into the ley lines where you live?  There's something unusual around you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mia_golden_sun" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="mia_golden_sun_hydroVision">Your aura carries the power of Hydro, yet I don't see a Vision on your person.  Have you hidden it somewhere?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="mia_golden_sun_hydroVision">I'd say for certain that you're the proud owner of a Hydro Vision, yet I don't see one on you.  Do you keep it covered?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="9s_manufactured">I haven't seen a puppet of your make before.  Where were you manufactured?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="9s_manufactured">Hmmm...  You're a puppet, yes, but I can tell you're far more sophisticated than most.  Do you know where you were built?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="yumeko_enjoyDrama">I do believe you also understand how fun it is to watch someone stammer and panic.  Such dramatic reactions to trivial problems.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="yumeko_enjoyDrama">I've gathered that you also enjoy people-watching -- or rather, seeing them caught off guard.  That deer in the torchlight look -- delightful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yuri" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="yuri_bookPreferences">You, purple-haired one.  Yuri, I believe?  What do you look for in novels when shopping?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="yuri_bookPreferences">You, bookish girl with the long hair.  Your name is Yuri, yes?  What qualities in a book make you want to purchase it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="monika_otherworldly">Where is your homeland, Monika?  You have a faint aura of not being part of this world -- something I only sense from the Traveler.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="monika_otherworldly">Are you another one who travels between worlds, Monika?  I sense that you don't quite "belong", something I've only sensed before with the Traveler.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="kumatora_adventures">You are an adventurer of some sort, no?  Where have you traveled?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="kumatora_adventures">I gather that you have gone on some sort of long journey before.  What was your destination?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="caitlin_sleeping">Shall we break for a nap before proceeding?  You seem on the verge of sleep.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="caitlin_sleeping">Did you skip your scheduled nap time to attend this game, dear?  You could nod off at any moment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="komi-san" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="komi_commDisorder">"Speaking" with a notebook?  Let me guess...  There's nothing wrong with your voice, but there is a barrier in your mind, no?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="komi_commDisorder">My intuition tells me you struggle to socialize in some way.  Is that right?  I don't see why else the notepad would be needed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="mari" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="mari_piano">You play the piano, no?  Such instruments are almost unheard of in Inazuma.  I've only had the fortune of hearing recordings.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="mari_piano">The piano is a most exotic instrument in Inazuma--I don't think a single one exists on our soil.  I have heard recordings of them, of course, but not in person.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="jura_questionsAboutMen">What is it you'd like to know about men, dear?  Men are commonplace in Inazuma--I've seen many come and go in my long life.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="jura_questionsAboutMen">It's quite strange that you're unfamiliar with something as mundane as men's nature.  I shall be generous and share what I know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="jim_warStories">A warrior's life is not easy, but it does make for good stories.  Have you any to share?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="jim_warStories">Life does not flourish in times of war, but compelling stories do.  Share something with us, will you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="arueshalae" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="arueshalae_darkToLight">Born in the dark, but walking in the light--how interesting.  Tell me, how did you start down this path?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="arueshalae_darkToLight">A demon turned to righteousness?  Fascinating.  Tell me more about yourself, dear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="35">
                <condition role="other" character="lyralei" stage="0-2" saidMarker="lyralei_picture_drop_fate" sayingMarker="fate_picture_swap" />
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Lyralei_Picture_Swap" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">I create drama for entertainment all the time, but it's much more fun when it emerges naturally, don't you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="witty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="31">Not so clever now, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="exhibitionist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="38">Try not to tear your clothes in your haste.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="39">Stay calm.  Savor your "defeat".</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="40">I don't think this one's even trying to win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="77">Try punching a hole through a paper wall.  Perhaps that would alleviate your rage.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="insane" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="78">You need a better hand than that, dear.  And also a therapist.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="gloomy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="79">Such a shame--one would expect better a better outcome for a sunny individual like you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="wealthy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="98">Money can't buy happiness, but it can buy fried tofu and novels.  Close enough, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="tsundere" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="104">Perhaps it would be best to engage in some introspection and sort your feelings out before patronizing this establishment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="perverted" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="106">You have the air of a child in a candy shop.  I suppose there's no better place to unfetter your urges.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="seductive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="107">You have talent at drawing in and enticing others, but learn from me and they can become putty in your hands.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="sarcastic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="110">I see you deal in irony much of the time, but are you able to wield sincerity when the situation demands?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" stage="0" saidMarker="yae_miko_resp_otherworldly" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="monika_otherworldly2">No, there's nothing off about ~player~, aside from being incredibly average.  If something's wrong, dear, it's best to let me know as soon as possible.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="monika_otherworldly2">~Player~ is only notable for being extremely unnotable.  You should be honest with me, dear.  It's much better in the long run.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="serious" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="80">Relax, dear.  There's no deadlines to meet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="tomboy" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="82" marker="yae_miko_tomboy1">It's fascinating how, to many, the most desirable women are those who don't fit the "feminine ideal".</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="yandere" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="84" marker="yae_miko_yandere1">I think you're in need of self-reflection, dear.  You've gone beyond passion into infatuation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shut_in" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="86" marker="yae_miko_shut_in1">Hiding away from the world causes more problems than it solves.  A friend of mine learned that the hard way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="88" marker="yae_miko_shy1">You mustn't let your life be ruled by the opinions of others, dear.  You can't, and shouldn't, please everyone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="lawyer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="41" marker="yae_miko_lawyer1">Legal thrillers have been increasing in popularity recently.  I wonder how many youth will be inspired to take up the profession.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="chuunibyou" role="target" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="43" marker="yae_miko_chuuni1">It's tragic that so many adults have lost the imagination they had in their youth.  You're very much an exception to that, I see.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="student" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="45" marker="yae_miko_student1">Many a story that comes out of our presses is set in a school of some form.  I suppose they would be relatable to a student like you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="48" marker="yae_miko_student2">I imagine you attend a normal institution of learning -- some of our titles feature very strange ones, built around magic battles and such things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="fighter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="49" marker="yae_miko_fighter1">The action genre has been our most popular for years running.  Boys and girls alike just flock to buy volumes about a protagonist who's always fighting something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="6">
                <condition filter="writer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="yae_miko_writer1">I understand you're a writer, ~target~.  Would you happen to be looking for a publisher to work with?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="yae_miko_writer1">You are a writer, yes?  Have you been thinking about better opportunities for your skills -- a new employer, perhaps?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="idol" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="54" marker="yae_miko_idol1">Building one's life around maintaining a public image and performing must be exhausting.  I only have to make appearances at a few events each year, but more than that would be dreadful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="adventurer" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="57" marker="yae_miko_adventurer1">Gallivanting around the wilderness and poking around in ruins must produce some engaging stories, no?  Feel free to share them with me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="bounty_hunter" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="59" marker="yae_miko_bounty_hunter1">I can't say that a bounty hunter would find much work in Inazuma.  The Tenryou Commission would not appreciate someone intruding on their work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="alchemist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="62" marker="yae_miko_alchemist1">Finding a person trained in alchemy is no easy task in Inazuma.  Perhaps an exchange program with Sumeru would allow some of our people to learn it in Spantamad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="journalist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="64" marker="yae_miko_journalist1">Journalism has yet to properly take off in Inazuma: most people learn of events through word-of-mouth or reading Tri-Commission notices.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="artist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="66" marker="yae_miko_artist1">Nothing sells a book better than a beautiful cover, in my experience.  If you're looking for work, I could give your portfolio a glance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="detective" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="68" marker="yae_miko_detective1">Detective novels are all the rage in Fontaine.  They're becoming more popular in Inazuma as well -- a good mystery can capture any reader.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="knight" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="70" marker="yae_miko_knight1">Some of our recent titles have featured protagonists training to become knights.  There's an exoticism that comes with knighthood; samurai are too familiar and mundane.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="spy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="72" marker="yae_miko_spy1">The Shuumatsuban are, for obvious reasons, secretive.  My writers often have to go on legends and rumors about them, plus what little I can tell them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="model" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" oneShotId="74" marker="yae_miko_model1">Such an intriguing profession, modeling...  I suppose the Kamera has opened up a new world of possibilities for your line of work, no?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8" id="68">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Bobobo_Broken" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">One would expect a self-styled swindler and charmer to appreciate a joke and take it easy.  Such a shame.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">My, a bit high-strung, aren't we?  So much for being a cool-headed charmer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" stage="1" saidMarker="yae_miko_resp_otherworldly2" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="monika_otherworldly3">...I would need more information about this to assist you properly.  Realms of consciousness and similar things are notoriously difficult to work with.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="monika_otherworldly3">If you've become stuck in a realm of consciousness, I may be able to help you.  Emphasis on "may".  Matters of space-time are notoriously ornery.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="tomboy" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_tomboy1" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="83" marker="yae_miko_tomboy2">Perhaps, in avoiding expected feminine behaviors on the surface, the true essence of a woman shines through.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="yandere" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_yandere1" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="85" marker="yae_miko_yandere2">You be able to live on your own before you can bring someone else into your life.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shut_in" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_shut_in1" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="87" marker="yae_miko_shut_in2">There is pain in the world, yes, but the emptiness of isolation will do far more damage to your soul.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_shy1" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="97" marker="yae_miko_shy2">You should, of course, listen to me and my insights.  Earning my favor comes with many benefits.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="lawyer" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_lawyer1" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" oneShotId="42" marker="yae_miko_lawyer2">Many titles are set in Fontaine, but tend to feature Inazuma's legal practices.  Seems that authors need to do better research.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="chuunibyou" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_chuuni1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="44" marker="yae_miko_chuuni2">Don't listen to the curmudgeons and conformists, dear.  The world's more fun with people like you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="3">
                <condition filter="student" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_student1" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="yae_miko_student1b">The setting must be popular for its familiarity -- nearly everyone has been a student at some point.  Still, I think more authors should try different settings to place their characters in.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="yae_miko_student1b">It's a fairly universal experience -- few people have never been in classes of some sort.  I'd rather see a greater diversity of settings, regardless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="4">
                <condition filter="student" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_student2" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" marker="yae_miko_student2b">More than a few stories have the school setting play little to no role in the plot at all.  I can't help but wonder why these authors feel compelled to put their characters there.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" marker="yae_miko_student2b">I've read a number of stories set in schools that could have worked just as well in a workplace setting or elsewhere.  What is it about the educational experience that haunts their thoughts?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="fighter" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_fighter1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="51" marker="yae_miko_fighter2">So many of the same elements, too: our hero is often considered weak but trains hard to become stronger, and has some tag-alongs who comment on his battles. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="writer" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_writer1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="53" marker="yae_miko_writer2">If you have stories to tell, we have an audience who'd like to hear them.  Provided you meet our standards, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="7">
                <condition filter="idol" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_idol1" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png" marker="yae_miko_idol2">I wonder, is the "you" that you show the crowds have much in common with the "you" that lies within?  Surely you have to make a few edits.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="8">
                <condition filter="adventurer" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_adventurer1" />
                <state img="#-disappointed.png" marker="yae_miko_adventurer2">Adventurers in Inazuma seem to be either glorified errand runners or hunting around the same parts of Seirai Island over and over -- not the most exciting material.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="bounty_hunter" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_bounty_hunter1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="61" marker="yae_miko_bounty_hunter2">Rewards for information about a suspect are known to be given out, though.  Perhaps you'd be able to simply tail your quarry and inform a doushin to make a living.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="alchemist" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_alchemist1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="63" marker="yae_miko_alchemist2">I have heard of an alchemist in the Knights of Favonius in Mondstadt -- quite a talented one, as well.  He visited our nation a while ago -- perhaps you'd like to be introduced.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="journalist" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_journalist1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="65" marker="yae_miko_journalist2">Fontaine's Steambird is growing in popularity, though it takes a while to reach our shores.  One of their reporters came to watch a TCG match I played in, in fact.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="artist" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_artist1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="67" marker="yae_miko_artist2">Some of our current illustrators struggle to meet their deadlines, so having a few more on staff might ease the workload.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="detective" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_detective1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="69" marker="yae_miko_detective2">I'd be willing to listen to the details of any cases you've handled, should you be kind enough to share.  We'll change the names, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="knight" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_knight1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="71" marker="yae_miko_knight2">I could lend an ear should you want to share your insights on being a knight.  Primary sources don't come along everyday.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="spy" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_spy1" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="73" marker="yae_miko_spy2">I'm sure your own work is similarly classified, but telling me a little about the world of espionage wouldn't hurt, right?  It's for a good cause.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="model" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_model1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="75" marker="yae_miko_model2">Since employers look for the most beautiful people to show off their garments, I might feel generous one day and try it myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition filter="sarcastic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-scary.png" oneShotId="76">A mouth like yours could be put to much better use.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="16">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Honestly, I'm surprised Chihiro didn't run away sooner.  Such a skittish little thing, no?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="scarred" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="32">There's a story behind every scar, and yours looks like a real page-turner.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="23">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Of course you are, dear.  I could sense it from the start.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Repeat after me. "Three, two, one, one, two, three, ahhhh, ahhhh." Come on.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Just imagine how much better that would have been with my help.  Such a shame.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8" id="60">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="8" />
                <condition role="other" character="marinette" stage="10" sayingMarker="adr_mari_dual" />
                <test expr="~adrien.distance~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Finally, some actual carnal activity.  For a lewd game, its participants seem rather restrained, no?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Just when I was thinking everyone here was too inhibited to actually go for it.  You may proceed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't fret about this too much, young man.  Countless people have been defeated by me before.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Men lying defeated before me is not an unwelcome sight.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I've long since lost count of how many opponents I've defeated in various contests.  Still, it's an honor to play a match with me, so don't feel bad.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">There's no plot armor to be found on you, it seems.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Laying one's life down for my sake is a noble fate.  Surely you can handle a milder task.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">No story is complete without a fitting ending.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Failure is hardly rare in life.  I'm sure you'll manage to learn from this, and fail better in the future.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Your loss is my gain, and any sensible person would be proud to assist me in any way.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">In the blink of an eye, ~target~ is out of the game.  Such is the transience of human life.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Don't make too much of a fuss.  You're hardly being sent to the chopping block.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Are you brave enough to face the next step?  You wouldn't want to disappoint us, would you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1">
                <state img="#-smug.png">A failure so great, it's almost impressive in its own way.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh my, how embarrassing.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Are you so eager to display yourself to me that you threw the game?  Honestly, is a little patience too much to ask?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I did make clear earlier what it means to challenge me, did I not?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="81">
                <condition role="other" character="wasp" stage="0-7" saidMarker="shrinking" sayingMarker="shrinkimage" />
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Oh look, she can transform into a crystalfly.  How cute.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="44">
                <condition role="opp" character="mari_setogaya" />
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" saidMarker="big_succ_start" sayingMarker="the_big_succ" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, to be young and in lust again.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Such a generous act of service.  One can't go wrong with the classics.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Go on, exorcise your lust.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Excellent, a fresh spectacle.  Just in time.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">We don't allow "rituals" of this kind at the shrine.  I'm sure that someone's gotten away with it in the past, though.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I have my show, now I only need dinner.  Can the kitchen prepare some fried tofu quickly?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">As with writing a novel, pacing is essential.  Don't get too carried away at the start.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, don't give us that look.  Is self-pleasure really that much of a penalty?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">There is a concerning lack of patience with many young people these days.  Try not to complete your task too quickly now.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">From what I've gathered of you, it will be a stunning achievement if you make it past the two minute mark.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition count="0" filter="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="33">Undressing me with your eyes, ~target~?  One could hardly blame you.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="34">My eyes are up here.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="35">Do you have any idea how soft and smooth my skin is?  You want to caress it, hmm?  Keep dreaming.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition filterOut="gay" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="36">It's a miracle he hasn't finished yet with one as desirable as I here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="27">
                <condition role="other" character="wasp" stage="0-7" saidMarker="shrinking" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">How delightful.  You must tell me how that trick is done.  Some adepti art from Liyue?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">The adepti of Liyue have techniques allowing one to shrink in size, with the right materials.  Is this an application of that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I might let you moan my name if you ask nicely.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Do you want me to watch?  I'm not sure if you've earned the privilege yet, but I'll consider it.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make sure to switch hands at some point -- we can't have you being too dull to watch.</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">Harder.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Don't be too gentle with yourself, now.  I can find you a healer if that's a concern.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Keep going, I'm on the verge of paying attention.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">One can only speculate on ~target~'s lewd thoughts.  I would speculate that they're dreadfully unoriginal.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">My presence during your private time is not likely to occur again.  Make good use of it.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Speed up.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Try to keep a morsel of dignity, if possible.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hold it in a bit longer.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It's been some time since I've seen a look of desperation like that.  How endearing.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">It's not so terrible being my plaything, now is it?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Is that all?  Surely you can do better.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Look at that grip -- it's as if your life depended on it.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">My, how one's energy shifts when they enter the throws of passion.  Even the dullest person starts to show some charm.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh, listen to those deep breaths.  How precious.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Be sure to share some of your fantasies with us at some point.  If I enjoy any, they might find their way into an upcoming raunchy title we publish.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I hope you're good at taking orders.  I'm certainly proficient at giving them.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="5-8">
                <test expr="~target.timer~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-scary.png" oneShotId="514">Let it out, &lt;i&gt;now.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png" oneShotId="513">Be a good boy, and &lt;i&gt;cum.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_holdUntilTold" />
                <state img="#-scary.png" marker="yae_miko_holdUntilTold=1">Let it out, now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Almost there?  Better make it count.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">A decent build-up, but will the climax manage to impress?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="yae_miko_holdUntilTold=0">Hold it in until I say when.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">I can see the flashes in the clouds.  Now we await the lightning bolt.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, so soon?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Think of the repairs your home needs to last a little longer.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Ignore all distractions now.  Except my instructions, of course.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">How appetizing.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="22">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Hat_Cheat" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh, the swindler was cheating the whole time?  Color me shocked.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I, for one, am flabbergasted that the con man would be running a con here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="48">
                <condition role="target" character="jin" sayingMarker="GlowCum" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Bioluminescence in a man's seed?  That's certainly a new one, for better or for worse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_holdUntilTold==0" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I didn't tell you that you could finish yet.  You'll have to start again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="yae_miko_holdUntilTold==1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Excellent work.  As a reward, you can go fetch me a drink.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">A bit abrupt perhaps, but serviceable all the same.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">You could stand to develop more endurance.  I'm sure your future lovers would appreciate it.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Make sure to be a gentleman and clean up after yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">That was an amusing expression.  Very uninhibited.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">That lasted a bit longer than I expected out of you.  Quite commendable.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">It must have been hard to hold that in with a beauty like me standing before you.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Well?  Did you enjoy yourself?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">How should I put this... Your clumsiness is matched only by your speed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">You managed to entertain me.  Good boy.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">As good as that felt, it would have been far better by my hand.  Too bad that won't be happening.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8" id="70">
                <condition role="opp" character="adrien" stage="10" />
                <condition role="target" character="marinette" sayingMarker="mari_adr_dual" />
                <test expr="~adrien.distance~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh, this is a welcome development.  Go on, show how much you lust for each other.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Finally, some &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; action.  I'll be evaluating your performance, so make it memorable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="21">
                <condition role="target" character="wasp" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Aww, and I was just getting used to the crystalfly woman buzzing about.  At least you have a new act to entertain us with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="40">
                <condition role="target" character="jura" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">I was expecting a show, but it appears we're getting a &lt;i&gt;spectacle&lt;/i&gt;.  I suggest you listen to your partner, dear.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh, this is even better than I expected.  Do as Jura says, dear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="62">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Clouds gathering above your head...  Have you given Ei reason to be angry with you lately?</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">If a storm is forming directly over your head, one would assume you angered a certain Archon.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">...Well?  What are you waiting for?  Show me how skilled you are with your own body.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Don't be too down on yourself, dear.  It's an opportunity for a comeback arc at a later date.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">It seems you've been written out of the game.  Fate is a fickle author.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Failure is only natural.  I'll demonstrate how one wins at this game for your benefit, while you take care of yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Don't feel too down -- you never stood a chance to begin with.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" pose="shock" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh my, what pleasures do your comrades-in-arms have for you?  Do share, it's part of your grade.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="12">
                <condition role="target" character="nico_robin" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">One certainly doesn't see something like that every day.  Seems you've got legs in more than one way.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">When people say a woman "has legs", it normally has a more conventional meaning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="49">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I've heard of Hydro Vision holders using their gift for such a purpose.  A creative use, to be sure, and quite lovely to watch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="jolyne" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let me guess, shibari?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="61">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">A shame to see my present re-wrapped, but do what's most comfortable for you, dear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="83">
                <condition role="target" character="binah" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Hmm?  I didn't see a Geo Vision on you.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">I've seen stranger uses for Geo constructs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">I may provide recommendations on how to proceed.  You would be wise to follow them.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Go on.  Show us your womanly charms.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Fear not, there's only the risk of failing your one chance to impress me.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Is "dirty talk" something you're into, dear?  Give some examples, and I'll evaluate them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Let's see how your libido blossoms.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I never forget anything, so take care when revealing any strange "preferences" you have.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">A woman should know her own body as well as she knows her neighborhood.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I have my show, now where's the dinner?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Instead of idle talk, you could put your lips to a more productive use over here.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">My wrist is ever so sore, dear.  Care to take over?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Come now, the time for restraint is over.</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">Embrace your lust, or I'll embrace it for you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Does my gaze arouse you, dear?  There's no shame in saying yes.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I've seen some creative approaches from people trying to become my paramour.  This way is certainly direct.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">According to several sources, my voice is quite arousing to many people.  I'm not so cruel as to deny you its sound.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh, that fidgeting is &lt;i&gt;delightful&lt;/i&gt;.  Keep it up.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">What an adorable shudder.  Show me again.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">All that squirming from the pleasure -- even better than the kind I see from teasing.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Surrendering to one's base desires is so rewarding, no?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Distribute your touch a bit more -- don't you want variety in your pleasure?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Ask me kindly and I could provide some more detailed instruction via whispers in your ear.  I'm feeling charitable.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">If you're writhing that much  from your own hand, imagine what you'd feel from mine.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I hope you moisturize your hands regularly.  A soft touch brings double the pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Running out of energy so soon?  To think, I thought I saw potential in you.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Show me what you get up to in your sheets after lights out.  Don't deny it.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Your fingernails are well-manicured, I trust?  I dread thinking of the alternative.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Worry less about what you're "supposed" to do, and let nature take its course.  The eroticism will come easier that way.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Whatever it is holding you back, let it go.  Life's too short for truncated pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">All those waves of pleasure shooting through your body -- I daresay it's time for high tide. </state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Your lips are just letting ragged breaths escape -- perhaps I could find a better use for them.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Tell me what you're feeling.  Don't filter it.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Caress it slower, with more force.  Yes, that's it.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Oh, do you like that spot?  Stroke it harder.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Do you wish to remain "pure" forever? I didn't think so.  Show us everything you have.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Once you push past the initial hesitation, a wide world of pleasure awaits.  You will explore it for me.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Oh, I &lt;i&gt;like&lt;/i&gt; that.  You should do it more.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I can feel your urges boiling beneath the surface.  Let them out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" priority="0">
                <condition filterOut="straight" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="23">I know I'm a stimulating sight, dear, but would it kill you to look elsewhere for a moment?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="24">As soft as you're imagining my fur is, it's even softer than that.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png" oneShotId="25">If you gaze on me for your own pleasure too much, you run the risk that no other person will ever be enough after.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">A bit sloppy. I'll need to teach you the proper method.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">My, are all the girls so graceless these days?  Another hapless person to teach...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I hope such poor form is the exception, rather than the rule.  Should I lose, I can demonstrate the correct technique.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Well, practice makes perfect, and you're in desperate need of practice.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Oh dear, the inexperience is palpable.  Must I teach every woman here how it's done?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">There's no shame in being a bit inept at self-care at first, but I'd hope you'd have learned more than this at your age.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="5-8">
                <test expr="~target.timer~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-scary.png">Cum. &lt;i&gt;Now.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">Do it.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Cum for me.</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">You will cum, &lt;i&gt;right now.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Find a motion that works and stick to it.  I don't want my entertainment ruined right at the end.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Make certain that you jump off the precipice, rather than merely falling over it.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Finally, I was getting worried you wouldn't be able to get yourself there.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">That seems to be the spot for you.  Use it.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">At long last, our payoff.  Make it worth the wait, won't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">There we go, good girl.  Keep going...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Yes, that's a good girl.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Yes, almost there.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Good, bring yourself over the finish line.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Gaze into my eyes.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">You're almost there.  Keep going for me.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Be loud.  I want to savor you in full.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Harder.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Look at me when you do it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="85">
                <condition role="target" character="lyralei" saidMarker="masturbation_dildo" sayingMarker="lyralei_squirt_follow" />
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="target" character="lyralei" saidMarker="lyralei_squirt" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-calm.png">If you're looking for absolution, I recommend cleaning up after yourself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="4">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Chubby_transformed" sayingMarker="Chubby_End" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Losing excess weight that quickly?  Tell me your secret -- I can see a customer base eager to pay for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="47">
                <condition role="target" character="lyralei" saidMarker="lyralei_squirt" sayingMarker="lyralei_squirt_follow" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I saw the whole thing.  It's much too late, dear.  For both of us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="67">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_transformed" sayingMarker="Cat_End" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Such a shame.  You would have made a cute pair with the courier girl.  Oh well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="32">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" sayingMarker="finished" />
                <state img="#-surprised.png">Well, it was fun while it lasted.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Don't fret, you'll make it come around again.  And I'll be borrowing that image for commercial use, haha.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Not bad.  You might be worthy to service my needs as well.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">At least we all know your fingers can get the job done.  I'll keep you in mind.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Decent, for a beginner.  In my expert hands, though...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Average skill, but not lacking in enthusiasm.  With some training, I could make use of you.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I see potential in you, despite your current lack of finesse.  Keep your fingers nimble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">And now, the falling action.  Quite cathartic, hmm?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Good girl.  You have my permission to rest now.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">It's passable, for now.  Under my tutelage, you could make yourself feel so much better.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">The thunder calms, her urges met.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Don't waste your momentum.  Come over here and do as I say.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Come here to my side, while the fire still burns in you.  I have &lt;i&gt;tasks&lt;/i&gt; for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Since you've had yours, care to help with mine later?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">I haven't drawn a fortune slip in some time -- it seems I've had a run of bad luck.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">No matter.  I don't need to participate in the game to enjoy its eventual outcome.  All the better to end it sooner.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Not the first time I've been bested in a contest.  Skilled as I am, I cannot overcome chance and fortune.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Congratulations, you defeated the Lady Guuji.  There's only a select few who can make that claim.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Despite Ei's best efforts, it still appears that nothing lasts forever.  Well done on defeating me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="1" gender="female" />
                <condition count="0" filter="gay" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-z_Start_Forfeit_Pos.png">Don't salivate too visibly, gentlemen.  It's entertaining, sure, but rather unbecoming.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="3-5" gender="female" />
                <condition count="0" status="not_alive" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-z_Start_Forfeit_Pos.png">Watch carefully, ladies.  I wouldn't want you do embarrass yourselves by doing this incorrectly, so I'll demonstrate the proper technique.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="1-" gender="female" status="masturbating" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-z_Start_Forfeit_Pos.png">It's difficult to watch a woman pleasure herself so crudely.  Watch and learn, dear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition count="1-" gender="female" status="masturbating" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-z_Start_Forfeit_Pos.png">It's dreadful to watch such ineptitude at self-pleasure.  Watch carefully -- I'll demonstrate how it's properly done.</state>
                <state img="#-z_Start_Forfeit_Pos.png">I can't bear to see another woman fumbling at her own personal time.  I'll share my years of experience so you can do it right -- aren't you fortunate?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-z_Start_Forfeit_Pos.png">Mastering one's own body is inevitable given enough centuries.  I know exactly what I like.</state>
                <state img="#-z_Start_Forfeit_Pos.png">The idea of watching the Lady Guuji pleasure herself would be enough to make many Inazumans faint.  How fortunate you all are to bear witness.</state>
                <state img="#-z_Start_Forfeit_Pos.png">It's certainly the first time I've had an audience, but no matter.  I'm feeling unusually generous, and this is my gift to you. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="8" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="37">It's nice to know I haven't lost any sensitivity anywhere.  I can feel... everything...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="511">Simply delightful...</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png" oneShotId="512">See?  &lt;i&gt;This&lt;/i&gt; is how it's done.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Some predators hunt by laying a trap and waiting for prey to fall into it.  How long will I wait, hmm?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Isn't this what you came for?  Aren't you entertained?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Infatuation is temporary.  Desire is eternal.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Shrine rituals are often of a repetitive nature.  It helps to become accustomed to such things.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Does it surprise you to see this coming from me?  I seek fun wherever I can find it -- the carnal arts are no exception.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Through my sources, I once heard of some young men claiming they could "tame" me with their sexual prowess.  Delusions of grandeur are quite droll.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I'm sure you're interested in my personal fantasies and deep desires.  I'll let you know... when the sun sets in the east.</state>
                <state img="#-delighted.png">Even in the nation of eternity, the common people develop new styles and trends in the realm of pleasure.  It's hidden away, but a delight to learn about nonetheless.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">To be new to passion is nothing to be ashamed of -- it's a great joy to discover one's tastes in pleasure.  Just make sure to actually start exploring at some point.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Now's not the time for shame.  For me, it never is, but especially not now.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">There comes a time to put aside hints, implications, and innuendo, and to simply be direct about what you want.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">As one should use the right tool for the right task in crafts, so should one know when to use soft caresses and when to use force.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I'm sure you'll remember this sight for the rest of your days.  It's well worth the spot in your mind, no?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I've been the source of inspiration for many people's alone time for a long time, and I'm sure that will only expand after this.</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">Do any of you dare come any closer?  You never know what might happen...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">These legs are dangerous -- once they wrap around someone, they might never let go.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Some are limited enough in their imagination that their deepest fantasy is to be stepped on by me.  Amusing to be sure, but isn't there more stimulating activities one could do with me?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It would serve you well to watch.  I'm trying to educate the helpless here -- if no one's watching, I might stop.  We can't have that now, can we?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">My bed is so much better for this sort of thing.  Maybe one of you will be lucky enough to experience it yourself one day.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This is quite outside the formal duties of a shrine maiden, but who would want to be limited to only what their occupation demands?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">As much fun as it can be with another person, it still falls short of the precision I have with myself.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">When one lives for centuries, it's very important to be comfortable with oneself.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I hope the rest of you are paying attention -- my intent is for you to learn to be less inept at intimacy, after all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">Yes, that's it...  Right there, ah-</state>
                <state img="#-mast_heavy_1.png">Oh, almost...  Watch carefully, this is how you please a woman, ahh...</state>
                <state img="#-mast_heavy_2.png">Mmmm... Perfect...</state>
                <state img="#-mast_heavy_3.png">Just a little more...</state>
                <state img="#-mast_heavy_3.png">Yes, yes, here we go...</state>
                <state img="#-mast_heavy_2.png">It's... ahh...  Now, the most important part of the lesson...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-z_Finishing.png">Yes! Y-yes!  Ahh!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-z_Post_Orgasm.png">A moment of passion that feels like an eternity of pleasure.  How appropriate.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <state img="#-z_End_Forfeit.png">The wobbly feeling in one's legs is a sure sign of success.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-amused.png">For what amounts to a den of lust and degeneracy, this place attracts a rather timid clientele.  I wonder why...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">In writing, it's said that one should use the simplest words possible to convey meaning.  However, I've found that a more elaborate vocabulary can be essential to properly express an idea.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">No Kameras, please.  This is an exclusive event -- one witnesses me like this with their own eyes, or not at all.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is certainly a livelier event than many I've been to.  Much more entertaining than listening to another Tri-Commission functionary try to butter me up.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's not the first time I've lost--a shock, I know--but since it's so dependent on chance, I think it doesn't reflect on me.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">What a strange situation; usually I'm the one observing others grapple with defeat.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Even if my intellect didn't carry me to victory, my beauty makes this a gift to others, no?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Some Domains are dangerous, some are merely strange.  This is the first one I've encountered that seems exclusively for debauchery.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Teasing with words is one way to make someone squirm.  Teasing with pleasure is an altogether different game, though no less fun.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's good to get out like this.  If I spent all my time reviewing drafts, I might become as dreadfully boring as some of you.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Is teasing the only thing I do?  No. But it is the best thing I do.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">It should be noted that I haven't shown my fox form here.  Of course, I never will, but you should know it exists.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It would be unbecoming of the Guuji to not keep to her commitments, no?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">One of our writers suggested we publish a collection of his poetry.  I would have approved it, had even one of his poems been worth reading.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">There may yet be ways to improve this little game.  Pairing up afterward to indulge each other would be a better endgame, no?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Our next venue should be the Plane of Euthymia -- primarily to see the look on Ei's face.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">A nice walk to stretch the legs would be delightful right now, but I'd like to see how things resolve here first.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">The jury's still out on any of you being worthy of providing carnal services to me, but I wouldn't get your hopes up.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I once heard whispers of an artisan in Ritou thinking of making small statues of yours truly to sell.  Such a scheme would be blasphemous -- unless I received royalties, of course.</state>
                <state img="#-surprised.png">This "poker" game is obscure in Inazuma, but perhaps strip shogi could take off one day.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">There were card games of varying types at the Mikawa Flower Festival all those years ago, but they lacked the popularity of Akitsu Haneasobi.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I really should permit a food vendor to set up at the entrance to the shrine, on the condition that they include fried tofu in their selection.  It would be very convenient.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's important to love oneself, both in the emotional and carnal sense.  Both are easy when one is as beautiful and wise as me.</state>
                <state img="#-disappointed.png">Precise use of timeskips can be used to keep the up the pace of stories and move past the boring parts.  If only I could skip past the boring people I have to talk to each day.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I suppose I could have made a stronger effort to win, but I'm already the most talented person here.  It's only fair that I give my opponents a chance at winning.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Given some of the poor decisions Ei has made, she would be wise to take care of her body's needs before making a choice.  It certainly couldn't hurt for her to try.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">My body's perfect state is something of a cause of jealousy; many women struggle to keep to an ideal weight.  Such a trivial matter -- simply eat less and move more.</state>
                <state img="#-thirsty.png">It's been some time since I've taken on a paramour.  If only there were a wider pool of candidates available--I might find someone worthy.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Apparently, some young men with &lt;i&gt;particular tastes&lt;/i&gt; have taken to calling me "Yae Mommy".  How droll.  Perhaps they want me to fold their laundry?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I don't need to worry about making "correct" decisions.  I decide on something, then make it correct.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't feel bad.  It's hard to win against wits of my caliber.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Fitting that a distributor of fortunes would have good fortune in a game of chance, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">That was close.  Hope you all enjoyed the view. Ta ta~</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">I'm afraid I'll be leaving, and you still won't have seen my kitsune form.  You may see it... in your dreams.  Bye bye~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't be too hard on yourselves.  Some individuals are simply imbued with greater talent at birth.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="93" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-thirsty.png" collectible="yae_miko_necklace">Unlocks the wearable necklace collectible.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Such is the nature of chance and fortune.  Perhaps I can claim victory another day.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">With stakes this low, it's not a loss in any meaningful sense, no?</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Congratulations, ~target~.  The Archons smiled on you today.</state>
                <state img="#-teasing.png">Did ~target~ really win?  The rest of us indulged in our lust, while ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ stood there, denied the shared experience.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Good game, ~target~.  I'll try to remember your face for next time~</state>
                <state img="#-scary.png">I wonder, which will be swifter: ~target~ putting ~target.ifMale(his|her)~ clothes back on, or my lightning strike?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="92" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png" collectible="yae_miko_necklace">Unlocks the wearable necklace collectible.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="global">
            <case stage="0-8" disabled="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
