<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.9.2 at 2:02:48 PM on March 02, 2023. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.9.2</version>
    <first>Maria</first>
    <last />
    <label>Maria</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>large</size>
    <timer>35</timer>
    <intelligence>good</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="apron" generic="apron" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="dress" generic="dress" position="both" type="major" />
        <clothing name="boots" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="kerchief" position="head" type="extra" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Oh, what do we have here?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">My, my, doesn't this look like fun?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Ah, what's going on over here? Can I join in?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-delight.png">I'm so excited! I've been so bored with my usual pastimes recently!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's been a while since I played cards. I hope I haven't gone too soft.</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">I've been looking for a little excitement! Things back home are so dull sometimes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-stern.png">Hm, ~cards.text~ will do.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'll have ~cards.text~, please.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">~Cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh, ~cards.text~ I suppose.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">I usually make my own luck, but it's more exciting to just see how things will play out.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">I hope you're all feeling as brave as I am!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Honestly, it might be more fun to lose! Hehe, only joking!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Oh, I'm in no rush. I have some doggies looking after my precious animals. They wouldn't dare let anything happen to them.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Ah, it's so nice to get away from the riverbank every once in a while. So many new faces!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I'll be happy with any result. I'm just here to have a little fun for myself!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">It might be fun to play like this with some of the people under the bridge, but I get bored just playing with them all the time.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Did you get a hand better than mine? I don't think so!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">If you didn't get good cards, maybe you should just get a do-over. It's not like it really matters!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition gender="male" status="alive" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-delight.png">Wow, ~trash~! You're really taking your time! Do you really think we want to stand around waiting for you?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Maybe ~trash~ will do something useful for once and lose this round for us!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Well, I'm waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">~Trash~! Are you ready to lose?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">My, my, I hope I didn't get any of the cards ~trash~ had last round.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I hope a certain someone isn't forgetting their place.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">I can't wait for ~trash~ to look all dismayed when he finds out he lost!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Come one, ~trash~! It's no fun if you just stand around looking like an idiot!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Uh-uh. No turning back now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I wouldn't dream of going down without a fight!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You don't need to tell me not to count my chickens before they hatch. I've raised my fair share of hens down by the river.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">I'm all set to win! He-he, or lose! It's so exciting not to know!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't worry about little 'ol me. I'm ready to go!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I hope everyone is having fun! I know I'm having a blast!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">We played a lot of card games when we were training to go to Venus. I think I got pretty good at them!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You would all fit in just perfectly with us under the bridge. Is anyone looking for a place to live?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It all just comes down to luck, doesn't it? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You have to be pretty brave to stick out this game, or just really horny. Hm, maybe it helps to be a bit of both.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition gender="male" status="alive" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-calling.png">~Trash~! Are your cards bad? Are you thinking about how you're going to lose?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Even if ~trash~ were to win, I wouldn't think he's cheating, no! I'm sure he's nowhere near smart enough for that!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Don't be nervous, ~trash~. It's not like we're expecting anything impressive from you.</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png">Maybe it should be ~trash~'s turn to lose! Can we all just agree on that?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">My, my, ~trash~, what are you doing? Oh, you're so cute. Pretending like you know what you're doing!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">What's the hold up? Let's go.</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png">Is everything alright, ~trash~? You're not having any trouble focusing, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">I hope you don't lose this time, ~trash~. I wouldn't want you to get discouraged and quit like a little crybaby loser before we get to really humiliate you.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Tick tock, ~trash~. Tick. Tock.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-delight.png">Whoops! Well, mistakes happen! </state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Losing is fun too, I'd say. I hope nobody is getting too nervous about it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My, my, now this is the kind of heart-pounding excitement I've been missing.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">I'm not even sure I want to be the big winner, but playing to win is a lot of fun. I feel so invested each round!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Gambling with money is bad and you shouldn't do that sort of thing. You might end up living in a cardboard box  under a bridge!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah, oh well. There is no reward without risk.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Looks like luck isn't on my side this time, but who knows?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I'm not so sure I'm going to come out on top this time around. What a shame!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Don't think any less of me when I lose, okay? I'm only human, after all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition gender="male" status="alive" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm naming this hand ~trash~ because of how it's literally just garbage.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Did you get a good hand, ~trash~? Did you manage to do something right for once?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Don't go getting a big head, ~trash~.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">I don't mind doing lewd things with you here, ~trash~. Why should I care? It's not like you matter!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">My, my, seems like I'm going to lose this round unless some pond scum decides to pointlessly throw the round in my stead!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Let me see your hand, ~trash~. You may have cards that belong to me.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">I'm not going to quit even if my luck is real bad! I wouldn't want to miss it if  ~trash~ completely embarrasses himself!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">I can live with losing, just so long as ~trash~ does too!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Are you waiting for me to lose, ~trash~? Pervert.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="32">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="nickname_prompt" />
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" />
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="KumaKaan" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Now why would we use such an uncute and uncool name for someone so cute and cool?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="34">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="nickname_prompt" />
                <condition role="opp" character="bobobo" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Kumatora_BoboboNickname">You're not thinking of suggesting something weird, are you, Bobobo?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="33">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="nickname_prompt" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Who told you your name is a pain to say? It seems they need a refresher on just what pain is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="31">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="nickname_prompt" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">I'm not so good with naming things. I don't even name my animals! I leave that sort of job to the Chief.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="kum_superpowerA" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">If I had to choose, I would have to say something like the ability to speak with or understand animals. That way it would be easier to tend to their needs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="kum_superpowerB" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Is there a superpower that makes you better at tying knots? Knots so tight even a wriggling little worm wouldn't be able to squirm his way out?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" totalRounds="0">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">My, my, this is so exciting! I wonder what's going to happen!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="35" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="602" marker="ManEating1">Where do you get off anyways, ~trash~? Hm? Speak up and explain yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="603" marker="ManEating2">Do you really think you're worthy enough to be here, ~trash~? Feel free to explain yourself, but try not to waste too much oxygen doing it.</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="604" marker="ManEating3">You seem awfully cagey, ~trash~. What's the matter? Don't like what you see, you ungrateful swine?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="605" marker="ManEating4">Couldn't you have just stayed and home and jerked yourself off, ~trash~? Why come here and bother the rest of us with your disgusting little habit?</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="606" marker="ManEating5">How about you make yourself useful, ~trash~, and buy me something to drink? I'm getting thirstier and thirstier here and you're just standing around like the useless lump you are.</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="607" marker="ManEating6">Hey, ~trash~, be more careful. There was an ant right next to you and you almost squished it. Try and be more mindful of your superiors, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="roll_resp0_1">I wouldn't exactly call it "nature." It's pretty much smack dab in the middle of the city.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="17">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="maria0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">Dressing up all fancy never really suited me all that much. I gave up all of that to live peacefully with my animals. Maybe it's not for you, but I've never been happier.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">Obviously it's not for everyone. I find I prefer the grit and grim to the dresses and fancy dinners. None of that made me happy, but taking care of my animals does.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="4">
                <condition count="1" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Maria_WhySoRude1A" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Mari_resp0_1A">History? Hmm? Have I met ~trash~ before? Have I? I don't recall having met him before.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="12">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_maria_strip0a" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png" marker="aqua_resp0_1">Oh, I just run a little farm raising cows and chicken and sheep. It does keep me busy, but I so enjoy the company of the animals.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="3">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Maria_WhySoRude1B" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Mari_resp0_1B">No, of course not! I have no problem at all with men. Goodness, whatever gave you that idea?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="5">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Maria_Eyes1" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Mari_resp0_1">Goodness, how forward! Could it be you're trying to make me fall in love with you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_JustMetAGirl1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_1">Really, that tough? Hm, big strong guy like you? Sure, I'd believe it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_1">I do get some help here and there from the other folks living on the river from time to time. I even find something useful for the pigs to do from time to time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="kaz_resp0_1">Though my home's a farm, t I'm just a block away from the city proper. I've got the convenience of the city with the solitude of the country. I don't have to deal with those pesky men in the city.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="kaz_resp1_1">But where's the fun in that? Some "number one bachelor" you are if you shrink from a challenge. If there's something you want, why not pursue it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="kaz_resp2_1">Aww, poor Kaz. Are you really gunning for me? Trying to impress me? Think that &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; of all people is worthy of my attention?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="kaz_resp3_1">Oh? You think I don't care? Kaz, I'm a woman just like any other. When I think about bearing myself in front of someone I like... I feel nervous... and excited... and aroused...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="kaz_resp4_1">Is there something else you want from me, Kaz? I'm not unreasonable. Why not ask? Want me to suck your dick? Would you like that? I'll do it if you ask.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_Pointed1" />
                <state img="#-apathetic.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_1">Yes, Bobobo, it's poker. You're supposed to try and beat me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_AnIn1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_1">That's surprisingly straightforward for you; however, even if I told you outright I'm positive you wouldn't be willing to do any of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_APRON1" />
                <state img="#-seductive.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_1">You flatterer, you. I bet you say that to all the girls you see with nothing but an apron on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_TellMeLies1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_1">Well, I would never think of accusing of having something a normal person would have.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_1">Oh, I wouldn't say that. Any man who would run in this situation isn't really worth the time anyways.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_1">Aww, I think it's cute that you're embarrassed. I"m sure you'll find a way to have fun with it too if you just relax a little bit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_1">Oh, of course not. It's always nice to have someone to talk to. Besides, you're so cute and shy that I can't help but tease you a little.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_1">Is that so wrong? You can only stalk the same hunting grounds for so long before your prey starts getting wary.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="roll_resp1_1">Hm, I wouldn't say so. I don't really use money personally.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="roll_resp2_1">Well, I'm not sure if I can provide a useful answer, but by all means feel free to ask. It might help just to talk about it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="roll_resp3_1">Anything less than apologetic groveling wouldn't do. Why, he should probably have to cook for &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; with just an apron on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="roll_resp4_1">You're a smart girl, Roll. I'm sure when you've got a wrench in hand, you'd put even me to shame. I'd have no idea where to start with that kind of thing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="13">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="maria0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="revy_resp0_1">Don't worry, I didn't wander in here by accident. I've already got my chores done for the day and my hands are all warmed up for whatever might come next.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="revy_resp0_1">Oh, I think I deserve a little more credit than you're giving me. I'm not just some blushing milk maid who's only ever stroked a cow's teat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="14">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="maria1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="revy_resp1_1">Oh, now, don't make a face like that. I can tell you've got a bit of a mean streak in you as well. Come on! Come one! You can tell me!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="revy_resp1_1">Believe me, I'm only here to relax! See? I even left my rope at home! It's a bit of a shame too because I think you'd enjoy learning how to hogtie an unruly heifer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="15">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="maria0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">Hm? Is that so? I don't really like the idea of some fat bureaucratic pigs telling me what I can and can't do. I much prefer doing it my way by myself.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">Really? I keep things running pretty much on my own. The last thing I need is some mangy dog from the government sniffing around my animals.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="16">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="maria1" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="meia_resp1_1">My, my, you really haven't had a lot of experience with men, have you? I guess you can't be blamed for that, but there's so much you must not know!</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="meia_resp1_1">Oh dear, I haven't said anything strange, have I? I guess you must have had pretty limited exposure to men given your circumstances. This must all be so new for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="18">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="maria1" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="jura_resp1_1">Oh, you're funny! I'm just an average Earth girl, Jura! An average girl with the heart of a pure maiden inside her!</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="jura_resp1_1">Believe me, Jura, I'm as average as an Earth girl as you'll find around. Just a simple farm girl with a fragile heart...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="19">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="maria01_male" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_1">Oh, I'm sure he's imagined it all before. I suppose after this, just imagining it won't be the same. A real shame about that. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="20">
                <condition role="other" character="felix" sayingMarker="MariaFelix01" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="felix_resp0_1">And pray tell, what are you so afraid I might say to you? What are you so afraid of?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="felix_resp0_1">My, my, there's no need to be worried? What could I possibly say that would be so bad?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="21">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="maria_ms0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="dwight_resp0_1">Angry? What would I possible be angry about, Dwight? Hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="22">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="maria_ms1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="dwight_resp1_1">I hope so, Dwight, because if you &lt;i&gt;did&lt;/i&gt; do something I would find out about it. I would make you tell me. I'll have you confess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="23">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="maria_ms2" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="dwight_resp2_1">My, my, Dwight. It almost seems like winning is causing you emotional distress. Maybe it would be better off if you just lay down and give up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="24">
                <condition role="other" character="cagliostro" sayingMarker="MariaKerchief1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="cag_resp0_1">No trolls around that I'm aware of. We're all fairly average people, I'd say.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="cag_resp0_1">Can't say I've ever run into a troll, at home or elsewhere. We're all just regular people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="25">
                <condition role="other" character="cagliostro" sayingMarker="MariaDress1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="cag_resp2_1">Oh, it's the only decent thing to do, I think. It's just convenient that it's so much fun! Wouldn't you agree?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="cag_resp2_1">To me, it's just simply something that needs to be done, but let's be honest: the necessity doesn't take the fun out of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2-" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition count="1-" gender="male" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="601" set-intelligence="best">I suppose this is my fault for being too kind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="586">My, my, I must be losing my touch.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="587">Me again? Looks like my luck isn't going to carry me through here.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="585">Another loss for me? Maybe I underestimated you all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="591">This is a pretty pathetic showing from me. I suppose I should applaud you.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="592">This streak of bad luck is making me look bad...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png" oneShotId="597">My, my, I continue to come up short...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Look how happy ~trash~ is I lost. Would you be happy if I just got completely naked right now? Is that what you want?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Lucky you, ~trash~! Looks like it's my turn! Should I get completely naked for you now? Would you like that? Hm?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-delight.png">Oh, look at ~trash~ getting all excited again! I'm not getting naked yet, so try not to soil yourself, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Yes, it's me again! Don't get too excited, ~trash~, or you might lose what little control of your body you currently possess and make a mess!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">My, my, ~trash~. I think you'll like this. Get ready to have your tiny little lizard brain blown!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Maybe I should reward ~trash~, even though he doesn't deserve it at all, but I should be nice to lower lifeforms.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Try to contain your excitement, ~trash~. We can't have you slobbering all over the place!</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">I know you're excited, ~trash~, but try to keep your creepy panting to yourself, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">You still with us, ~trash~, or has all your vital blood run to your limp dick instead of your peanut brain where you might actually get some use out of it?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Try to keep your jaw off the floor, ~trash~. It would be a shame if you accidentally swallowed a fly and had to spend the rest of your life atoning for it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-delight.png">Looks like it's my turn! How exciting! It just wouldn't be right if I didn't strip at least once, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Oh no, is it me again? That's fine with me! It's no fun unless you get right down to your bare skin!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">My, my, I really seem to be running out of options. Well, that doesn't mean I can't have a little fun with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Looks like you got me. Now this is where the real fun begins...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-enamored.png">I was feeling a little left out. Now we can all be fully exposed together!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Looks like you got me! Don't worry, I'm a bit eager to get started on this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smug.png">My, my, I'll have to try a little bit harder! I don't want the fun to be over too soon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-delight.png">Oh? Is it me again? Hm, I think I'll have a little fun with this one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Ah, well done! I think you've all earned a reward! I'm sure you'd agree!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-delight.png">My, my! Seems like the real fun might start a little sooner for me than I expected!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">So it's my turn? You won't hear me complaining. It's what I'm here for, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-delight.png">Ah, seems like I might be outmatched! Maybe I should try a little harder. It wouldn't be as fun to lose completely right away.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">My, my, what a predicament I'm in. You're giving me a real run for my money.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Oh dear, things really aren't looking good for me, are they? Well, I suppose you've earned a reward for playing so well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-delight.png">Down but not out, so they say. It might surprise you what I can do when backed into a corner!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_JustMetAGirl2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_2">Okay. Your hair is dumb.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_2">I don't really raise them on the farm; they just live on the riverbank too. They're wild pigs who like to misbehave and get into trouble. I just make sure they all know their place when I have the patience for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp0_2">Not the people, the men. Always coming up to me, asking me dumb question after dumb question. It's &lt;i&gt;such&lt;/i&gt; a nuisance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp1_2">Well, you've got to do something with your life. Might as well take your chances and become a masochist.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp2_2">My, my, you're like a dog chasing a car. Even if you caught me, it's not like you'd even know what to do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp3_2">You see right through me, Kaz. It's so rare for a man to see me... see me for who I am and see me... as I am...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp4_2">I'll do it for you, Kaz, if you ask. My tongue, tracing the length of your dick. My warm lips, wrapped around you. Servicing you with my mouth, my throat. Do you want me to, Kaz? Do you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_Pointed2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_2">Plan? Scheme? Hang on, you've lost me. Go back and start from the beginning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_AnIn2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_2">Bobobo, I'm really not that picky. I want what any woman wants: someone who is honest and kind. Someone who makes me laugh. Someone who makes life fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_APRON2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_2">Oh? "Grill your cheese?" Is that a euphemism for something sexy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_TellMeLies2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_2">Oh? And what exactly would you be referring to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_2">It's not like I'm telling them to buzz off. I just want them to get down in the mud where they belong and show the proper gratitude. If a guy can't even do that, then he might as well scram.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_2">Come now, you're not shrinking violet. I bet when you're really in the mood, you're the one who makes all the bold moves.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_2">I haven't met anyone who can dish it out like I can, but I bet you'd blush if you knew just how much I can take. How much I have taken in the past.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_2">Hm, well, it helps when what you're hunting is prideful and dumb. There's no cure for that second thing, but paralyzing them with fear fixes the first one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="roll_resp0_2">No, you were right the first time. I do live on a farm right on the bank of the river. There was nothing there but grass, so I just came along and made use of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="roll_resp1_2">The community on the river is fairly self-sufficient. We all share what we have and the fruits of our labor. We don't need money because we're paid in the expectation that everyone will pull their weight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="roll_resp2_2">The only way to know for sure, Roll, is to ask them. It takes a lot of bravery to do it, but all the heartbreak in the world can be washed away by just one person returning your affection.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="roll_resp3_2">I think the punishment should fit the crime. Not that I think he could really ever in his lifetime repay you for such a special treat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="roll_resp4_2">My, my, there's no need to thank me. It's just my nature.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_maria_strip0b" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="aqua_resp0_2">What can I say? I can't help but help out when I see a poor, helpless little thing.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="aqua_resp0_2">Oh, it's nothing special at all. I'm like anyone else: I just want to coddle helpless little creatures.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="27">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="maria02_male" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_2">He'll just have to make the most of this opportunity. It'd be a shame if he completely choked and wasted it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You'll just have to be patient. Can you do that? Can pond scum like you hang on that long?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Mmm, no, I don't think so. I'll just take it one step at a time. Think you can hold on for a little while longer? It's not like you have anything better you could be doing.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">My, my, so impatient. I'm going to have to teach you how to be patient and just wait. You can thank me later for elevating you slightly above being complete scum later.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Are you the kind of pervert who gets off on women's feet? Don't be shy, you can admit it. It's impossible for anyone to think any less of you than we already do.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Does the thought of seeing my feet fill you with excitement? Is that what you like? Are you a filthy little pervert who gets off on ladies shoes and feet?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Did you know there are some perverts out there who are obsessed with feet? They get all sweaty and bothered over the thought of a woman taking off her shoes. Kind of like ~trash~ here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Won't you be glad to have this out of the way? Just the flimsy cloth of my apron separating you from a glorious view of my body?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Do you fantasize about women wearing just an apron? Does the thought of it turn you on? Can you hardly stand it?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">How about I take off my dress so it's just my apron? Would you like that? Is that erotic enough for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Don't worry, I always play fair and square. No tricks. I'll strip and you'll get to see my breasts just like you wanted.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">If you're worried I'm going to pull a fast one on you, just relax. I'll show you my naked breasts, just like you want.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">There's no trick, I promise. I really am going to be exposing my breasts. I'd never cheat in a fair game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Are you watching? I'd hate for you to miss a moment of this.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">If a woman is showing herself to you, you'd best pay attention.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Pay close attention because I won't be repeating this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It's nice to get away from everybody on the riverbank for a while. I can't remember the last time I took some time just for myself.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I don't get away from the riverbank too much since the farm keeps me busy. It's nice to get out for a bit and meet some new faces.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I figured i was overdue for a trip outside the riverbank. It's a lot of work running a farm, so it's hard to find time to just get out and socialize.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You might be wondering how I came to live under a bridge, but unfortunately for you that's a secret!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Maybe you're wondering to yourself how it is that I'm living under a bridge, and while you're free to wonder just now that is my business and mine alone.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">If my living under a bridge is of great curiosity to you, I'm sorry to say that I'm not one to speak about how I came to be in this situation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Here, I can slip right out of my dress like this...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">This dress slips off quite easily, you see. Watch, I can take it off just like this...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">This is a &lt;i&gt;game&lt;/i&gt;, right? So I should make it exciting? How about I just, slip out of my dress like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It's been quite some time since anyone's seen me like this. Oh yes, quite some time indeed.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I can't even remember the last person who saw me like this. Guess it's been a while since those hectic years...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I'm not ashamed to say I'm a bit out of practice. I don't think anyone's seen me like this since... well, let's just say it's been some time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">There's not a lot of privacy by the river, so I don't spend a lot of time without my clothes on. I don't even get in the bath without a towel on. I have to since the bath is completely outside.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">The Arakawa River is pretty cold, so it's not ideal for bathing. Luckily, we have a little oil barrel bathhouse with warm water. It is a little exposed to the elements though.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Farming is dirty work, so I do indulge in regular baths. We don't have running water, so we all bathe in a heated oil drum the community shares.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1" id="6">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_JustMetAGirl3" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_3">Now let's talk specifics. You can sit still without speaking for half an hour, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_3">That's right! There are many pigs in the world, but those pigs are &lt;i&gt;my pigs&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-mad.png" marker="kaz_resp0_3">And yet you still keep talking and coming up with dumber and dumber questions.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="kaz_resp1_3">But you have such a naturally gloomy disposition! Ah, and that pathetic look in your eyes when you're feeling melancholy! I think you should reconsider.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="kaz_resp2_3">Don't think too hard about it. I'd hate for you to waste what precious few braincells you still have rattling around up there.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png" marker="kaz_resp3_3">Yes, Kaz, you see right through one pitfall and think yourself so important you fall right into the next. The only transparent one here is you, you shallow, narcissistic crybaby. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Maria_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="kaz_resp4_3">Hm? What's that? You're going to have to speak up, Kaz! I guess you &lt;i&gt;don't&lt;/i&gt; want that. Well, that's okay. You can't help it if you're a spineless little bacteria. Enjoy your blue balls!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="7">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_Pointed3" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_3">No, don't stop there. Keep going! Oh, but first you should face the other way and keep walking until you hear me tell you to stop.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="8">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_Pointed3" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_3">Bobobo, I wasn't finished saying... you know what? Forget it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="9">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_APRON3" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_3">Were you born this stupid or was it something you had to work at?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="10">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_TellMeLies3" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_3">Bobobo, you are a strange, gross, idiotic man-child... but you know the way to a girl's heart.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_3">Men never really know what they want, but thankfully I know what's best for them. It's really no trouble at all to help them out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-seductive.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_3">Well, if you're really a scholar, I figured I should be a better subject for study like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_3">I'm not going anywhere quite yet, Y'shtola. I think there's still quite a lot of fun for us to have.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Maria_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_3">I'm surprised any of them can pop a boner at all without terror pumping their blood, and I find fear of disappointing me gives them the proper desperation needed to be a serviceable lover.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="11">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_Kaz_BeepBeep" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="BK_resp2_3">I'm sure you would, Bobobo!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="roll_resp0_3">So they tell me, but it's hardly been an issue. I've been able to convince any man they send to enforce it to just do whatever it is &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; tell them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="roll_resp1_3">We are pretty lucky! We've had a few leeches here and there, but even a pathetic little leech can find a way to contribute with the proper instruction.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="roll_resp2_3">A cutie-pie like you could have anyone wrapped around her finger if she wanted! Especially a man! They are pretty slow though, so don't be surprised if you have to say it more than once!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-calling.png" marker="roll_resp3_3">Then that Mega Man fellow had better look out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="roll_caskett" sayingMarker="Maria_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="roll_resp4_3">Oh, that's also just part of my nature!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="26">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_maria_strip0c" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="aqua_resp0_3">Though, some little things need a little sterner care than others...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Ah, look at you. So vexed that a woman won't get naked for you straight away. How did a mangy dog like you get so self-important? Honestly, as if I have time to discipline a pervert like you.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I know you're just here to ogle women like the stupid pervert you are. Does it frustrate you that you have to obey the rules? Do you think anyone cares about the opinion of trash like you?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">You can't even manage to wait a little while longer, can you? Practically foaming at the mouth at the thought of seeing a bit of skin. It's so sad to see garbage like you forgetting it's place.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png">If you're so into feet, then why don't you get down with your nose to the ground and stay with all the worms and filth you should rightfully call your betters.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Honestly, it's revolting that the dregs of society like you are allowed to wander the streets and soak up precious sunlight. </state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Don't even think about simpering and groveling at my feet for forgiveness, creep. Don't waste the oxygen it would require and just keep your distance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-delight.png">Here, it's my little treat to you! No need to try and pay me back, it's not like your miserable life is long or consequential enough to ever hope to repay what I've done for you today!</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I know you must feel like you've been blessed by a goddess, but don't try and repay my kindness. Really. Don't. I wouldn't want anything that came from &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">I'm so glad you like it! Don't feel obligated to do anything in return. I mean, you could try, but it seems silly for you to spend the rest of your life in painful atonement!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">After all, who knows how many worms have seen me naked. What's another?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Besides, who cares if you see me like this? Who would you tell? Who would believe you? Like I said: who would care what you said?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I can hardly get upset about every single microscopic bottom-feeding insect that sees my body. That's just the way it is!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-mad.png">What's this? No applause? No "thank you, Maria?" "I am unworthy, Maria?" Have you lost the ability to be grateful? Could a skid mark like you be grateful in the first place? </state>
                <state img="#-mad.png">I'm not seeing near enough groveling right now. Knees, hands, and face should be digging into the ground. No words. Just penitent silence. Don't just gawk, hop to it, you slithering little leech.</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png">Oy, this is your cue to be grateful. To show this much kindness to a lower life-form is practically saintly on my part. But do I get even a crumb of the proper supplication? My, my, what an ungrateful pervert.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I do have fun playing with Nino, P-ko, Jacqueline, and of course little Stella, but their idea of fun isn't always the same as mine. Sometimes I'd like to do something a little more mature.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">It'll be good to interact with some new people for once! It'll give everyone back home a chance to recover too!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">It's not like it's boring back home, but a girl gets curious, you know? Surely there's some fun to be had elsewhere too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">But I can tell you that I stick around there since I'm free to be who I really am. I can just live carefree and take care of my precious animals!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's unconventional, but it is home! I'd rather not dwell on the past. Besides, it's in the past! I've got to live in the present!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">It really is a lovely place, perfect for looking after all my animals. Nobody bothers me unnecessarily and some of my neighbors are lots of fun to play around with!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Ah, the men I've loved. I do wonder what's happened to them. Are they doing okay? Can they think of me without crying? Without screaming?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I've loved many men, but none of them ever stuck around. I guess you can't tie anyone down. Eventually they just chew through the leash.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I was reckless with my heart once. I've had my heart broken many a time. I've also broken my fair share of hearts. And legs. And spines. And wills.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-enamored.png">My, my, isn't it exciting! Standing around in just an apron? Some men go absolutely crazy over it, idiots.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">So, how's this? I never get a chance to walk around like this ever. I think it's pretty exciting...</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Maybe it's a bit much, but when else will I get a chance to do this? So, is it sexy? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, modesty was never my strong suit anyhow, so taking baths outside doesn't bother me. Besides, the other residents know better than to try and take a peek at anyone while I'm on watch.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">The riverbank is pretty far down from the footpath though. From all the way up there, you can hardly tell there's a nearly naked person in an oil drum! </state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Nino used to bath completely naked, but some policemen got upset with her. Now it's a rule you have to wear a towel, even after I took pains to teach those nice policemen to mind their own business like good boys.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="3-7">
                <condition filter="straight" role="target" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Ah, of course he can't focus. Pervert.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Maybe next time keep your hands off your dick and on your cards. You haven't lost yet!</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">What's with this showing? Is your brain really so much mush you can't recognize numbers and shapes.</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png">Are you serious? Shouldn't you be taking this seriously? You're really just going to blow it, just like that?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Loser.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Lecher.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Oh, you're still playing?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Just ~target~? What is he going to do? Disappoint us again?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Haven't you given up already? Why are you pretending to have a spine? It's creepy.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">That's cute, ~target~, but we're all still playing seriously here. How about you go in the corner and we call you when it's time to be humiliated again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="28">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">Still struggling? That's no surprise.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">You must enjoy getting naked if you went and lost a second time! What a filthy pervert you turned out to be.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">You went and lost again on purpose, didn't you? You just get off on making us see your body, you disgusting lech.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My, my, a second loss? I guess you're just as stupid as we all knew you were.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Two in a row, ~target~? Really? I guess you're just destined for failure!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Why stop at two in a row, ~target~? It's not like you stand a chance at winning.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">~Target~? Again? Ew.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">You're not planning on keeping this up, are you? My, you're so pathetic.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Maybe you should try and win one , ~target~. It's incredibly boring just watching &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; strip.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="29">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Oh, how pathetic...</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Finally content to be a failure, I see.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">I'd say don't choke, but it seems like it's a bit too late for that!</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png">Can't you scrounge up one measly win, ~target~? It's no fun at all if you don't at least feign a little competence.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I see you're trying your best. That's the only reason you could be losing so much.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">God you're stupid.</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Could it be you've finally accepted your place on the bottom rung of society and you've decided to give up? Or is it just that you're an idiot?</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png">Are you giving up, ~target~? It would sure be embarrassing if you were losing so much while you were trying your best!</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" font-size="small">... So dumb...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calling.png">Do your best, ~target~! We're all watching!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Did ~target~ lose? My, how utterly unsurprising!</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Oh, did you lose, ~target~? Does the loss sting? Are you sad? You can tell me!</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png">Way to lose, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">If luck is a lady, then she's wise to steer clear of ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">My, my, seems like you could've won that round if only you were any good at this.</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png">Look! ~Target~'s cards are just as worthless as he is!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Have you not figured out what the pictures and numbers on the cards mean yet? Ah, you're so hopeless.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Poor ~target~. He'll never be able to try hard enough to really win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="1" hidden="1" addCharacterTags="dominant,mean" removeCharacterTags="kind">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="SMODE" direction="none">Maria will now act sadistic.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="kuma_dizzy_lose" />
                <condition gender="male" status="alive" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I hardly think it's your fault. I don't see ~trash~ coming to your aid or rolling over to let you win. Honestly, does he have &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; manners?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't get psyched out, ~target~. You can do it if you just focus a little.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't give up, ~target~! If you lose in your heart, you'll keep losing in the game too.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You're not losing faith, are you, ~target~? I still believe in you.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Two losses in a row might be disheartening, but you have to keep your spirits up.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Getting nervous? Need to take a deep breath?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Beating you two times in a row makes me feel a little sorry for you, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Another one? That's some tough luck.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Gotta chalk that one up to just rotten luck, right, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">Are you feeling okay, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I do not envy your luck, ~target~. Sorry about this.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Seems like you might be having trouble concentrating. See something around here you like?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Is this really bad luck? Are you maybe feeling a little naughty, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do you need some help, ~target~? Maybe you should let me pick your cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't sweat it, ~target~. Try and have fun with it!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">How exciting for you, ~target~! Are you ready?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Sorry, ~target~, but fair is fair!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Looks like someone might've made a little mistake! I'm sorry, but it's your turn now!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Okay, it's ~target~'s turn! Should be fun!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Well, well, ~target~. Whatever will you do now?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright, ~target~! Don't bore me! No, I'm only kidding!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Don't lose your determination now! Let's see what you've got!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">If it's ~target~'s turn, then we're all in for a treat!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Oh? Nobody loses? That seems like a waste.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Ugh, what a boring man...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I knew it. No excitement at all.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">If you had any spine at all, you wouldn't be doing this...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Oh, what a buzzkill.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Tch, learn to read a room.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I expected nothing and I am still disappointed.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">Maybe have the decency to just lose and not waste our time, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Honestly, they should give out medals for being this useless.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">What is this? Preening? Literally not one person cares.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Do you think you're funny? Is that it? That's just sad...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-stern.png">Wow, how worthwhile. I know you have the brain of a snail, but let's not move like one, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">It should not be this abundantly clear why no one likes you. It's just embarrassing.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">If you had anything worthwhile to show us, you'd have done so already.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Yes, well done. I'd clap for you, but even wasting the energy needed to talk to you is more than you deserve.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't pay any attention to ~trash~, ~target~. He has no self-control and should be ignored.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Now, don't rush ~target~, ~trash~. I know patience isn't your strong suit.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">There's no need to trouble yourself on ~trash~'s behalf. Just take your time.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How about you just sit patiently and watch, ~trash~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, a pragmatist? I can respect that.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(have|has)~ to come off, ~clothing.ifPlural(don't they|doesn't it)~? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah, it's just good sense to take things one at a time.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">My, my, I think you came more prepared than I did.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-delight.png">I'm glad to see you're not giving up until the very end, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I admire a girl with courage like yours! Still, be careful you don't lose!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">You're a tough one to keep down, aren't you? Well, it does make things fun!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">You just might be in trouble if this next hand doesn't go well for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Try not to lose too much, ~target~. We wouldn't want ~trash~ getting a big head about it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">In the end, that was probably the right move, ~target~. We should probably keep ~trash~'s expectations slow for everyone's sake.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Just remember, ~target~, that no matter how much you lose the biggest loser will still always be ~trash~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Maybe ~trash~ should hold ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ for you so it doesn't have to touch the ground. Then again, having ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ touch ~trash~ might be worse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-delight.png">Looks like somebody is playing to win! I do so admire that spirit!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Bravo! Bravo! I'm sure your courage won't fail you yet!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">I still think you should take off a little more. That's where the real fun begins!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't get too comfortable or you're liable to slip-up!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-stern.png">Is that all your going to be doing? Seriously?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">My interest in you is dropping with each passing second.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">At least be quick about it.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Fine, just do whatever you want, I guess.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="crotch_visible" role="target" />
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Just when I thought you couldn't possibly lose with less dignity.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Next time just accept defeat, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Being stubborn doesn't really suit you.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Maybe quit while you're behind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Is this ever going to go anywhere?</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Do the world a favor and just lose faster.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">He can't even lose right...</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">What a waste.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Look away, ~trash~. This one's not for you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Now, now, ~trash~. You get what you get and you don't complain.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Make sure to thank ~target~ for being so gracious, ~trash~!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Take a step back, ~trash~. You're crowding poor ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Trying not to attract any undue attention? I have a sense that's not going to work.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Are you stalling for time or just trying to seduce us with a slow burn?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You ever think that maybe you're just a bit of a tease, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh? Will you give us a little show?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I'm glad we have you around to keep things lively, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Did you come here just to show off? I don't blame you.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Brave girls like you are so cute. It's almost a shame you may have to lose.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Your company is so invigorating, ~target~. Any chance you want to come live down by the river?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-calling.png">Now let's unanimously agree to let ~trash~ just humiliate himself next round!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I don't think you're being near grateful enough, ~trash~. Do we need to work on that?</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png">Much more than that and I'm afraid you'll break poor little ~trash~'s brain, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">~Trash~. The least you could do is muster a single "thank you."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Those|That)~ ~clothing~ really should be thanking you for making ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ look so good.</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">If you're having fun now, wait until you lose a few more hands...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't be afraid to really get into the spirit of things! Losing is half the fun!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Don't worry, it only gets better from here!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calling.png">Make sure to thank Mr. ~clothing~ for doing such a good job of covering you up!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Are you going to take this one seriously? Do you really think that's smart?</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png">~Target~? What do you think you're doing? Taking your ~clothing~ off in front of us like some kind of pervert?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It's not like we could take you seriously with your ~clothing~ on anyways.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition status="topless" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.position~" value="lower" />
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="2" font-size="small">You look so dumb...</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="3" font-size="small">His... his underwear...</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="4" font-size="small">... What a loser...</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="1" font-size="small">What... what a stupid look...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Ah, that wasn't near as exciting as I hoped. ~Target~ didn't whimper even a little bit.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Why are you stopping? Just keep going.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Over already? Such a disappointment.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">We're going to have to see you lose again if that weak showing was your idea of a good time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Trying to get ~trash~ all hot and bothered? That shouldn't be too hard.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Taking your ~clothing~ off? Did you forget ~trash~ was here? I do too sometimes. </state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't feel like you have to go big just for ~trash~'s sake. In fact, you don't need to do anything ever for him!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Try not to get ~trash~ excited while he's off his leash.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Oh! So bold!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">C'mon, show off a little!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Ah, this should be fun!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Keeping things exciting, I see!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-delight.png">Maybe you should up the ante next time, ~target~! I don't think we've tortured ~trash~ quite enough yet!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">~Trash~, would you kill you to try and look even slightly less perverted?</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Do you think ~trash~ deserves to see more, ~target~? Hmm, what to do?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Try looking respectfully for once, ~trash~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">And you have such a great body, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Anyone with a body like yours should be more than confident enough to play with us.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">How did you end up so beautiful? Came by it naturally, I would assume?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Ah, it's such a waste for you to dress modestly.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Maria_ImpossibleBattle2" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_2">O... kay...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="16">Alright, let's see what we're working with here.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="13">Let's get the ~clothing~ off so the ridicule can begin.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="14">My, my, so brazen. As if we even really care what you've got going on under there.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="15">Is this your attempt to impress us? That's so cute and pathetic!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" oneShotId="25">Oh, what a big dumb brute you are? Sorry, I should have really been talking slower this whole time.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="26">Wow, look at those muscles! It's incredible that someone could be so strong and so useless at the same time!</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png" oneShotId="27">You've got such big muscles, but what are they even for? Seems like a bunch of wasted effort on your part!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="28">I think it's adorable that you're not afraid of people seeing your weird muscly body.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="hairy_chest" role="target" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="29">If I wanted to see a hairy animal, I would have just stayed home.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="30">So scruffy and dirty. Who'd be interested in a man with zero sense of hygiene?</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png" oneShotId="31">Do you think having a hairy chest makes you look manly? It really just seems like you're trying too hard!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="32">If you need to borrow some scissors, I've got some. I'd be more than happy to help you with this furry little problem you seem to be having.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-apathetic.png" oneShotId="41">Hm, nothing I haven't seen before.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png" oneShotId="42">Really not worth waiting around for.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png" oneShotId="43">Ah, I was hoping for something at least a little nice. My mistake for getting my hopes up.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png" oneShotId="44">Oh, just another useless male specimen.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="76">Oh, so the pervert wants us to see his dick? Very well. Let's have it.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="73">Such a desperate attempt to impress...</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="74">Don't pretend like you weren't eager to whip it out this whole time.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="75">It's your funeral...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="86">A pathetic showing for a pathetic man.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="87">What else could I have expected from such a sniveling, sweaty little worm?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="88">What's this useless thing? What good is that even for?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="85">Aren't you ashamed for being so woefully inadequate?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="100">So am I supposed to be impressed? By that? In what possible reality?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="101">I guess that's all we can expect from a lecherous pervert like ~target~. What a let down.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="102">Are we supposed to scream in terror or start drooling over it? All for that? Hardly.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="103">What am I supposed to be getting excited about here? A bit of degenerate scum with his little dick out? You thought somehow that would be exciting?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="93">Ew, it's grotesque. Who would want that sort of thing near them?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="94">Don't tell me you're boldly overconfident because your gross penis is grosser than usual?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="95">What a disgusting thing. You should be barred from public places.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="96">That's not normal. Are you sure you don't have a disease of some sort?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="181">~Trash~. Eyes. Closed.</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="180">I don't know if ~trash~ has really earned it, but it's your call, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="182">Hold on, ~target~. I want to hear ~trash~ say "please" first.</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="183">Seems like a waste for ~trash~ to see...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="172">Come on, let's see that lovely figure of yours!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="173">So bold!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="174">My, my! Trying to make us fall in love with you?</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="175">I knew playing with you would be fun!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="196">You wouldn't dare say anything untoward, ~trash~, would you?</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png" oneShotId="197">You're far too cute for ~trash~, ~target~. You should have someone who isn't such a disgusting, sweaty pervert!</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="198">Is this the sort of girl you're into, ~trash~? You don't have some sort of problem with girls like me, do you?</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png" oneShotId="199">Look out, ~target~! ~Trash~ has that patented pervy look on his face!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="208">You're such a cutie, ~target~! Like a precious little lamb.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="209">~Target~ is so cute all around! Being around her just makes me feel so light!</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="210">She might look innocent, but I can tell you've got a naughty streak inside you.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="211">So cute and petite! So, do you have to beat the men off with a stick or do you use something sharper?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="216">I don't even have to guess what sort of filth is going through ~trash~'s mind.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="217">Try and keep your gross cloud of perverted thoughts to yourself, ~trash~!.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="218">Maybe it's time we put ~trash~ back on his leash.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="219">Well, ~trash~? Aren't you going to say "thank you?" I think it's only appropriate for you to kowtow.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="269">Feeling a bit more liberated now?</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="270">I hope you're not too nervous now! There's still more fun to be had!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="271">I bet you break a lot of hearts back home, don't you?</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="272">I think it doesn't hurt to be free and easy every once and a while. Doesn't it feel nice?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="252">Is this your type, ~trash~? Is that why you're here? Wow, what a stereotypical pervert.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="253">If you're into women with large breasts, ~target~, it's possible you may have some sort of complex. Don't bring other people into it, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="254">How much is ~trash~ allowed to drool, ~target~? Best to set a hard limit now before his little peanut brain shuts off.</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="255">Time to prostrate yourself, ~trash~, like the boob-crazed pervert you are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-startled.png" oneShotId="264">Where is it you get your clothes? I should probably strong-arm Rec into going there to get me some that'll actually fit...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="265">Always nice to meet someone who understand the struggle.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="266">Do men bother you a lot? I feel like I could have a lot of fun if I stick around you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="267">Can I really say anything about this type of body without sounding conceited?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="337">Wow, ~trash~! And to think that before today you'd never seen a girl's pussy in real life!</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="338">So, ~trash~, think you can behave yourself?</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="339">Today is turning out quite educational for you, isn't it, ~trash~? Maybe you should stop gawking and take some good notes!</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="340">If I catch you staring too perversely, ~trash~, I'll drag you out of here by your neck.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="389">Well, I hope it won't make you too self-conscious.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="390">Oh! Lucky us! Or, maybe, unlucky you!</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="391">Now, who wouldn't admire a girl with this sort of backbone?</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="392">There's nothing to be embarrassed about! You can do it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7" id="2">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Oh, that's hot...</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Veeery interesting...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="353">~Target~ has been so nice to you, ~trash~. It's a shame you'd never ever be able to even come close to repaying her in your lifetime.</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="354" font-size="small">... ~Trash~ looks so nervous...</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="355">I think you've been far too lenient with ~trash~, ~target~. He was already lacking in basic manners. What a shame. I'll just have to discipline him properly.</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="356" font-size="small">... ~Trash~ is... he can't even...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="381">It is a little exciting to see you like this in this context...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="382">Maybe you can spin around and show us that butt of yours!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="383">My, my, isn't this intimate...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="384">So brave! So serious! So cute! Shall I go on?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp4_3" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_1a">So exactly how much flirting goes on between you and this "Warrior of Light" guy you like so much?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="0" />
                <condition gender="male" role="opp" character="human" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Nagatoro_s0_1">So, I take it this &lt;i&gt;thing&lt;/i&gt; belongs to you, Nagatoro? Hm, my condolences.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png" marker="Dunban_s0_1">Goodness, what a handsome gentleman! Though, you are a little scruffy looking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Kaz_s0_1">So you're a top bachelor? Is that really true?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_1">Oh, I hope this game doesn't turn out to be boring.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="steve" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Steve_s0_1">My, my, I was really hoping there'd be some handsome men here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Jim_s0_1">Hm, I do have a soft spot for big, strong, rugged men like you, Mr. Raynor...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Adrien_s0_1">Oh? A black cat in a mask? How mysterious and romantic...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="twisted_fate" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Fate_s0_1">My, what a dashing rogue. I didn't think to meet a man like you here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="eichi" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Eichi_s0_1">Well, aren't you just adorable? I've had a few lovers with blonde hair and blue eyes like yours.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_1">Honestly, the thought of meeting a spell-casting cat woman wouldn't have even crossed my mind just a few days ago.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Roll_s0_1">Pilot, mechanic, inventor. Seems like there must be something you're not good at. Please tell me you're a bad cook or something.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-apathetic.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_1">Okay, so now what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_1">I have this nagging feeling you're plotting something...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_1">My, my, you're doing such a good job of making a fool of yourself I barely have to lift a finger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_1">Bobobo. If I find out you're wearing &lt;i&gt;one more pair of underwear&lt;/i&gt; I'm going to shave every hair off your body!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_1">Do you intend to waste more time with this utter farce or can we finally get back on track?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Kaz_s1_1">So, Mr. Bachelor, are you here looking for a new girlfriend?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Kaz_s2_1">Well, if nothing else, you at least know how to dress yourself properly, Kaz.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Kaz_s3_1">I do so enjoy your company, Kaz. The tired, resigned look in your eyes is so satisfying.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Kaz_s4_1">Kaz, tell me honestly: what do you think of me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Kaz_s5_1">What's the matter, Kaz? You look a little uncomfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_1">So, what brings you here, Y'shtola? It's certainly hard to believe you'd have any trouble finding someone you'd be interested back at home.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_1">Am I supposed to believe in all your travels nobody has tried to pick you up even once? Surely the men can't be completely useless.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_1">Are there really no men in your little band of heroes worth getting even a little excited about? Seems like saving the world might kindle some warm feelings.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_1">So, who's the head of your merry little band anyways? Could it be that you're the brains behind the whole operation?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_1b">This whole "save the world or die trying" schtick has to be tiresome. It's no wonder you need a sexual outlet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_1">So, when's the last time you got laid?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_1">Feeling more relaxed yet?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Roll_s1_1">What's your friends name? "Mega Man?" Seems a bit presumptuous for someone to call themselves that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Roll_s2_1">Sounds like you do a lot for this Mega Man character. Honestly, seems like you're maybe too accommodating to him. What's he ever done for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Roll_s3_1">Hanging around your grandpa and Mega Man all the time must get old after a while. Don't you have any girl friends you can relax and spend time with?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Roll_s4_1">Come on now, Roll, don't be shy. I'd hate to see you lose your pep now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Roll_s5_1">My, my, you don't look too worried about losing. Do you have a secret, Roll?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Jim_s1_1">I can tell you're a soldier without you even having to say it. You've got that military dog stench about you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Kumatora_s0_1">I see a lot of myself in you, Kumatora. It's not just the hair color I'm talking about.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" saidMarker="Maria_Choices" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_2">Oh? That's not very exciting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" saidMarker="Maria_DDew1" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_2">Oh, you're serious. You've actually gone and done something stupider than normal to try and win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" saidMarker="Maria_FriendlyFire1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_2">Oh no, I'd rather not interrupt while you're doing such a good job of it. Go on. Let's see what you've got!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" saidMarker="Maria_PlanD1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_2">&lt;i&gt;Dumb Pervert&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" saidMarker="Maria_ColdCocked1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_2">... Proceed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="0" saidMarker="maria_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Kaz_s0_2">Wow, that sounds so impressive! You must have worked really hard to get to where you are!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" saidMarker="maria_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Kaz_s1_2">That attitude just won't do, Kaz. You can't be lax and just expect good things to come your way. You need be serious about it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" saidMarker="maria_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Kaz_s2_2">I'm being completely honest! All the men back at the river dress so strangely all the time. It's actually very refreshing to be around a man who knows the proper way to present himself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" saidMarker="maria_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Kaz_s3_2">It's not often I meet someone I feel so strongly about. I think maybe we could have a lot of fun together...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" saidMarker="maria_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="Kaz_s4_2">I'm just looking for an honest answer, Kaz. I thought someone with all your experience would have some insight. And since it's &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt;... I'm interested... in you---your thoughts.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp5_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Kaz_s5_2">What could I possibly be angling for, Kaz? No matter what you or I say, you're going to have to take off ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ridiculous ~clothing~ and show us your little penis.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="0" saidMarker="maria_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_2">I've met my fair share of odd characters back home. Compared to some of them, you're downright mundane.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" saidMarker="maria_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_2">Well, obviously you have a little time to have some fun on the side. If you're using that time to come here, I can only assume you're in a bit of a dry spell or you're bored with whatever you have at home.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" saidMarker="maria_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_2">What, like a marriage proposal? Wow. Was this someone you knew well?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" saidMarker="maria_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_2">Forget romance. You've got desires that need tending to. You're telling me you've never felt that itch and looked around to consider how any of them might be in the sack?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" saidMarker="maria_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_2">Oh? "Warrior of Light?" ~human.ifMale(He|She)~ definitely sounds important. So, what is ~human.ifMale(he|she)~ like? Do you two get along?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp5_1a" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_2a">Please, he's a man trying to save the world. I'm sure he wouldn't bother if he didn't think it would get him laid. Besides, you've been extra antsy since you mentioned him. It's very cute of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp5_1b" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_2b">There's always time to take care of ourselves. You're not going to save anybody if you're stressed out. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" saidMarker="maria_resp6_1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_2">Two weeks ago. Your turn.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" saidMarker="maria_resp7_1" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_2">No, thank you! I've had so much fun playing with you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="0" saidMarker="maria_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Roll_s0_2">My, my! You must get people telling you that you'd make a good housewife someday!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="1" saidMarker="maria_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-startled.png" marker="Roll_s1_2">You named him? He didn't already have one when you met him?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="2" saidMarker="maria_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png" marker="Roll_s2_2">It wouldn't be reasonable for him to expect you to put yourself in danger. If he wants to play around with his life, that's on him. What has he &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; ever done for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="3" saidMarker="maria_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Roll_s3_2">If you don't get along, why did she help you build the rocket? She must like Mega Man and awful lot.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="4" saidMarker="maria_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Roll_s4_2">Roll, of course that's not true. We might be different, but that doesn't mean you aren't beautiful. You've got to know that you're a sexy little number all your own.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp5_1" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="Roll_s5_2">Oh? Seems like you're getting into the spirit of things here. I take it the game has been stimulating for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="0" saidMarker="dunban_maria_self0a" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="Dunban_s0_2">I'd be more than happy to help you with that and give you a little trim. Let me borrow that sword and I'll clean up your face and take the top off for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="0" saidMarker="Maria0a" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Jim_s0_2">Well, I'm not really one to shy away when I see something I like, and I think you just might be &lt;i&gt;exactly&lt;/i&gt; my type.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" sayingMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">Goodness!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">... Unexpected...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">It was over before it had a chance to be good. Typical behavior...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Oh... don't tell me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">... If what I think is about to happen is about to happen... it better not.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">... Where'd he get that from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" font-size="small">... Good riddance...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">What in the world---?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp4_2" />
                <condition gender="male" role="opp" character="human" />
                <state img="#-mad.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_3">He sounds annoying. Nothing but an overconfident muscle head that punches first and asks questions never.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp4_2" />
                <condition gender="female" role="opp" character="human" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_3">Well, with a woman that confident spearheading your operation, I'm sure you'll find success.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" saidMarker="Maria_ImpossibleBattle3" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_3">Bobobo. What the heck? Why would you waste it all on one big burst at the beginning? Now what are we supposed to look forward to?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" saidMarker="Maria_Choices2" />
                <state img="#-mad.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_3">No, no you don't have many choices. And who do we have to blame for that, do you think?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" saidMarker="Maria_DDew2" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_3">Is your plan just to make a huge mess? Don't you realize someone is going to have to clean all that up?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" saidMarker="Maria_FriendlyFire2" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_3">Aren't you supposed to be funny or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" saidMarker="Maria_PlanD2" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_3">This is your plan? Being stupid in stereo? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" saidMarker="Maria_ColdCocked2" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_3">It's always such a shame to see boys fighting over me. It's not like I'd ever be interested in either a violent ape or a tattered weakling!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" saidMarker="maria_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Kaz_s0_3">Well, I think this bachelor ranking system is pretty useful. Now that I've seen you, I can be sure the rest of the men in your city must somehow be even more of a let down than you are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" saidMarker="maria_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Kaz_s1_3">Oh, I don't think there was any hope of you being taken seriously in the first place!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" saidMarker="maria_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Kaz_s2_3">And each time you lose you dress more and more like every man should! You're so much better now than when you first got here! No comparison!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" saidMarker="maria_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Kaz_s3_3">Don't worry. They all learn to love it eventually.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp4_2a" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png" marker="Kaz_s4_3a">Wow, pervert. That was so superficial. Is that all you care about you shallow little man?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp4_2b" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png" marker="Kaz_s4_3b">What sort of pansy-ass answer was that? Don't you have the balls to compliment a woman's appearance at all? What a spineless little worm.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="6" saidMarker="maria_resp5_2" />
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" marker="Kaz_s5_3" font-size="small">I would... and it is...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" saidMarker="maria_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_3">So sorry, Y'shtola. Last thing I'd want to do is offend you. I was hoping you and I could be friends!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" saidMarker="maria_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_3">Hm, I've touched on &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; haven't I? Come on, you can tell me! I'm just dying to know!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" saidMarker="maria_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_3">Interesting. Any chance he's still single? Still proposing to random women he meets?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" saidMarker="maria_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_3">I'd encourage you to be a little more imaginative. God knows they've probably all imagined you with your legs over your head with their dicks in hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" saidMarker="maria_resp5_2a" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_3a">Maybe I'm wrong, or maybe I'm right. I do know that if you climb into his bed, ride him until he breaks, and whisper there's more where that came from when the demon lord or whatever is defeated, it'll get done.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" saidMarker="maria_resp5_2b" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_3b">Hm, you strike me more the type who has to be reminded to eat and sleep when she's hungry and tired. I'm absolutely sure nobody is reminding you to seek pleasure when you're horny.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" saidMarker="maria_resp6_2" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_3">Ah, so it's been more than a few years for you. It's nothing to be embarrassed about. I imagine you take that sort of decision as seriously as you take everything else. There's nothing wrong with that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="8" saidMarker="maria_resp7_2" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_3">Sure, but I really think you should just lose! You really seem like you could benefit from an orgasm.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="1" saidMarker="maria_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-unamused.png" marker="Roll_s0_3">Ignore them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="2" saidMarker="maria_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" marker="Roll_s1_3" font-size="small">... He's like your dog...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="3" saidMarker="maria_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-delight.png" marker="Roll_s2_3">Oh! I'm glad to hear he's willing to do work fitting of his station!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="4" saidMarker="maria_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png" marker="Roll_s3_3">Hm, sounds like she might have a little thing for your boy. You don't think they're a &lt;i&gt;couple&lt;/i&gt;, do you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="5" saidMarker="maria_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Roll_s4_3">I'm sure men don't mind that you're dirty. They love filth. They love being filth. They probably fantasize about breathing in the smell of oil and sweat as they fondle your tight, petite body.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="roll_caskett" stage="6" saidMarker="maria_resp5_2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Roll_s5_3">Now that you've made it this far, you're horny.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="1" saidMarker="dunban_maria_self0b" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Dunban_s0_3">Don't think I don't know my way around a blade? If I just wanted to hurt you then I'd just do it, furball. Fine. Be a coward. What more should I have expected?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jim" stage="1" saidMarker="Maria0b" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="Jim_s0_3">I'm your type? Of course I am. Big dumb gorilla like you would probably try to mate with a pile of manure if it was still warm enough. Being "your type" isn't any sort of compliment, you oaf.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="4" saidMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">You really need to get that checked out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-startled.png">My, my!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">You're a special breed of idiot. Just one of many reasons you belong locked in a zoo.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Yes, yes, let's get on with it. No point in delaying your humiliation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">That's it. I'm shaving him.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">It's incredible. Every time I think he's hit rock bottom stupidity, he digs himself even deeper.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Wow! All that fanfare for that? What a let down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-delight.png">That can't be comfortable, right? C'mon! Tell us how it feels!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">That can't be healthy...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="no_genitals" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">I feel somewhat cheated...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="joke_forfeit" role="target" />
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Is... whatever this is, going to go on much longer?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Oh, what a bore...</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Not what I came here for.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="2" priority="1">
                <state img="#-startled.png">Oh, so ~target~ is out? Now he has to...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-calling.png" oneShotId="421">~Target~ is the big loser! And not just in general anymore!</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png" oneShotId="422">~Target~! It's time to do what you do best!</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png" oneShotId="423">Poor ~target~ has to humiliate himself in front of us! How terrible for him! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition count="2" gender="male" status="alive" />
                <condition count="3" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="OneOnOne" set-intelligence="best">And then there were two...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="3" priority="1">
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" font-size="small">He... he has to... what a loser.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="427" font-size="small">... Do your best...</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="428" font-size="small">... So pathetic...</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" oneShotId="429" font-size="small">... Stupid idiot...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" font-size="small">... ~Target~ looks so pathetic...</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Keep going, ~target~! You couldn't possibly hope to be any good in bed if you run out of steam now!</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Ah... those desperate eyes...</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">If I have to tolerate your presence, ~target~, you should at least do me the courtesy of putting on a good show.</state>
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" font-size="small">He's trying so hard...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Come on, ~target~. I need to know how much you can take.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Do it properly now, ~target~. Don't hold back.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">~Target~ in his natural state: with his dick in hand.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">It's so shameful how horny you got, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calling.png">Oh, ~target~. Tell me what you like...</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Show me all your desperation, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Is that enough to satisfy you, ~target~? Aren't you yearning for something more?</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">If you're begging for it... then beg for me.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Don't look away, ~target~. I want to see every pathetic twist of yearning on your face...</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png">A little louder now, ~target~. Let us really know what you're craving.</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">You're disgusting filth, ~target~. You know that... right? Right?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Come now, ~target~. Let me hear you beg for someone else to attend to your cock.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Stroke that filthy cock of yours. Show me what it's worth.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">What depraved thing is going through your tiny little pervert brain?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Ah, I want to see your final humiliation.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Throwing in the towel already? You really are worthless.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">Don't stop now. Not when I still want more...</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Yes, show your last, most pathetic face...</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Let's see just one last sad, pathetic whimper.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" oneShotId="4">
                <state img="#-unamused.png">You wouldn't dare think of cumming before me, would you, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Oooh, I got a chill...</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Ah, that look in your eyes...</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Hm, I think I have your measure now...</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png">Maybe you are worth remembering...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="439">Sorry, ~target~, but it looks like you're out.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="440">Well, ~target~, I do hope you're prepared.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="441">And with that, your streak of bad luck has come to an end.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="442">That's too bad, ~target~. You gave it your best shot.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="SMODE" />
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="482">Of course, ~trash~ will be on his best behavior throughout. I can guarantee that.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="483" set-size="small">Don't worry about ~trash~. He's completely harmless.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="484">~Trash~ shouldn't bother you one bit. He knows better than that by this point.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="485" set-size="small">Just say the word if you need ~trash~ tied up for any reason at all. He might be more useful that way...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition count="2" gender="female" status="alive" />
                <condition count="3" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="OneOnOne" set-intelligence="best">And then there were two...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="460">Winning is overrated anyways. You'll have a lot more fun this way.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="457">I wouldn't worry to much. Just try and have fun with it.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="458">It's only masturbation though. Hopefully it'll feel nice and relaxing.</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="459">At least now you're free to indulge in whatever sultry thoughts you've been having.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dreamy.png" oneShotId="452">Well, I hope you don't think you'll be in bad company for it...</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png" oneShotId="451">Looks like we'll both just have to make the most of it!</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png" oneShotId="453">You can believe me when I say losing isn't so bad once you get started.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5 7">
                <state img="#-startled.png">I never gave much thought to how other women might do it...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Was this something you needed, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Remember, ~target~, gently. It's about speed, not power.</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">~Target~ looks like she's having fun. Makes me a little jealous...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Care to share your naughty thoughts with us, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, aren't we lucky to see you make a face like that?</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">My, my...</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Just focus on your own pleasure...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Is this going to be enough for you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">I hope you're enjoying yourself too, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Isn't it strange to have ended up like this? Although, it's not so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I can't just let ~target~ have all the fun...</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">What could be going through her mind now?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">That look of desperation in a woman's eyes... hm, it's not quite the same.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">So strange, but somewhat thrilling...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Is this the face you only show to your lovers, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">We're only all to lucky to see ~target~ in the throes of pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Where's your head gone, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="517">Need a minute still?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="518">We could all do with just a little bit of that.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="519">Feeling better now?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="520">Now that looked like it was nice and healthy.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Well, fair is fair. I'll concede my defeat. Well done.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Ah, what a shame. It is a little disappointing to lose, but when I think about what comes next...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition count="2-" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-lost.png">I'd better get started. It's not like I can count on anyone else here to make me cum.</state>
                <state img="#-lost.png">I suppose I have some work to do, unless one of you limp dicked slugs thinks you can help? No? Thought so.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-lost.png">Might as well get comfortable, right? Isn't that the whole idea now?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-apathetic.png" oneShotId="526">What a useless man... leaving me on my own...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="527">Do you long for me, ~trash~? Does it frustrate you that you can't have me?</state>
                <state img="#-calling.png" oneShotId="528">Oh, ~trash~. Oh, ~trash~! Oh! ~Trash~! He he, not really...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="529">Are you watching, ~trash~? It's okay if you're afraid. I want to see...</state>
                <state img="#-enamored.png" oneShotId="530">Useless... pig smelling... heap of... slime...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="525">Are you getting shivers, ~trash~?</state>
                <state img="#-mad.png" oneShotId="537">Hm, he so clearly doesn't know how to please a woman.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="538">Come on, ~trash~. What would you like? Tell me so I can deny you it.</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png" oneShotId="539">If only ~trash~ had any guts, we could be...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="540">Come now, ~trash~. Won't you show me your yearning eyes?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="541">Is it everything you hoped, ~trash~? Does it frustrate you to no end?</state>
                <state img="#-unamused.png" oneShotId="542">~Trash~. Make yourself useful, for once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">Ha, that's what I need...</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">This is much more exciting than being on my own.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Ah, ha... gently...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Hm... god, it's been too long...</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">I still need more...</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Aaah... feels so good...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Oh... ha... if only...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Hm, I got so aroused...</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">This... this is what I was waiting for...</state>
                <state img="#-delight.png">Oh, it only gets better...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Aaah he he... wow...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's nice, but it's a little bit lonely.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-heavya.png" oneShotId="579">Pervert... slime... lecher... moron... rodent... scum...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png" oneShotId="580">Are you... watching... you pig-brained, bottom-feeding... ha... useless loser...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyc.png" oneShotId="581">You... disgust me...</state>
                <state img="#-heavya.png" oneShotId="582">I'll do... what your dick could never do...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png" oneShotId="583">Should I tell you... just how wet I am now? I'm sure a pervert like you... can imagine...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyc.png" oneShotId="584">I'm cumming... see... see how it's done!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Hm... not yet... can't...</state>
                <state img="#-seductive.png">I feel it... I'm almost there...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Ah... ha... hm... ooh...</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Ngh... it feels... I'm just...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-climax.png">Ngh---hmm! Haah! Ah... aaahn.... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">Ha... ha... who needs a man anyway?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">Hm... I should've taken more time.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I want to know how this all ends. You're not getting rid of me that easy.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Any chance we could hurry this along just a little?</state>
                <state img="#-dreamy.png">I hope everyone is doing well back on the farm. I'm rarely gone for this long.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">It's okay if I don't put my clothes back on quite yet, right?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hm, still got a bit of that afterglow coming through.</state>
                <state img="#-apathetic.png">I guess I'll need a bath when I get back.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't let the excitement wane now.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Hmm... maybe I should just leave...</state>
                <state img="#-startled.png">How long have we been at this exactly?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I'm not in a rush, but I'd rather not be here forever.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My, my, still so lively.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition count="1" filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" var="trash" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Not so fast, ~trash~. You still owe me a great deal after everything that's just happened.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition count="2-" filter="straight" gender="male" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Oh, boys! Don't leave quite yet. There's some manners I still need to beat into you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">It's a bit of a shame that I won. You all looked like you were having such a pleasant time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition gender="male" role="target" />
                <state img="#-chuckling.png" font-size="small">... ~Target~ didn't cum...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Congratulations, ~target~. Though, I hope you're not left feeling unfulfilled.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
