<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.8.2 at 10:30:56 PM on June 07, 2023. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.8.2</version>
    <first>Sweetheart</first>
    <last />
    <label>Sweetheart</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>20</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="thigh highs" generic="socks" position="legs" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="wrist bands" generic="armbands" position="hands" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="dress" generic="dress" position="both" type="major" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="sweetheart" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now neither of us will be virgins! Ohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="1">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">OHOHOHO! It is I, the one, the only, the most beautiful princess of all, Sweetheart!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="sweetheart" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">My own clone!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Rejoice, peasants! Though none of you are worthy of being in my presence. I have come to grace you all! Also, I expect to be greatly entertained while I'm here, so don't disappoint me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Perfect! I have no desire to change anything.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">A perfect hand for a perfect princess!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">For once, the dealer didn't disappoint me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Give me ~cards.text~!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Remove these ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~ from my sight.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I demand ~cards.ifPlural(these|this)~ ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~ to be switched.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't need these, give me  ~cards.text~  better ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">These ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~ can go away.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmmm...Take these ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I only want the cream of the crop!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png"> ~cards.ifPlural(These|This)~ ~cards.text~ ain't good enough. Change them!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">What are you waiting for, Dealer? Remove ~cards.ifPlural(These|This)~ ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Chop-chop, Dealer. Bring me my ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~ already.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="29" marker="violins">Perhaps this place could be elevated if it had some... violins playing in the background.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">OHOHOHOHOHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">It's only natural that my poker skills match my beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What was it again that was considered the best hand to have? A royal flush? Well, why haven't I gotten that yet? </state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">As royalty, it's a simple fact that I deserve the best of the best -- from clothes, to jewels, to even something as meaningless as cards.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Only the best for a captivating princess like me! </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It sure is tiresome being so &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt; at everything. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="13">BWAHA- Oh wait, wrong laugh. OHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="17">Mirror mirror, on the wall, who's the prettiest of them all? Why, me, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="212">Like swimming in my vault of Clams! Hm?... What are Clams? Ugh... do you even use that bird brain of yours? It is what you peasants call "Money".</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="30">Finally! After many weeks of my &lt;i&gt;worthless&lt;/i&gt; servants failing, they've managed to capture the most beautiful planet of all, Pluto! Dare I say, he's now one of my finest statues.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="213">Aren't these fingernails just gorgeous? Castella has done a wonderful job painting them. One of the only worthwhile servants I have.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="252">Afraid of falling in love? Don't be, &lt;i&gt;nobody&lt;/i&gt; can resist me, and I could always use more fans.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Perhaps next time... I will bring a mirror, so that I can adore myself while waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I have never once shown mercy to my enemies, and I'm not about to start either!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Gaze upon all that I am, ~player~. You won't find any lady half as beautiful as I am.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="11">I do so despise these kinds of hands. They keep you guessing if you might win or lose! Such stressful situations aren't good for a lady of my caliber, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="12">Hmm... Perhaps I should have brought Sprout Mole Mike with me. He could have entertained me in between rounds. A bored princess is an angry princess.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="216">Let us make one thing very clear. None of you are allowed within my personal space, too often do zealous fans try and get a handful of me. Which I do not tolerate!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Excuse me, dealer. It seems you have given me a commoner's hand. I hope I don't need to explain why this shouldn't be the case, right?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Hmm... This hand &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; give me inspiration for my next movie.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">There is &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; glamorous about these cards... How utterly dull.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I've seen commoners with more personality than these cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="23">This is not the first time that I've played poker. I have played plenty of rounds with my servants. However, they kept complaining about having no arms or hands to hold the cards with, but the only thing &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; heard was them making up excuses.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="26">All servants and visitors that enter my castle must obey the dress code. Either you wear pink, or I will have you thrown off the roof!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="27">Hmph! What a waste of time, none of you are worthy of becoming my suitor. I mean, do you all see how magnificent &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; look? How can you all compare?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="214">Despite you all being utter clowns, you have failed to entertain me! Even a Sprout Mole could do better!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">At such dull moments, I often have my servants play theatrics to get rid of the boredom.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">All of you simpletons should be honored to be able to bask in my glory. Most don't even get a glimpse!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hard to care about what my hand is when I just look &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; desirable.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="6">What ugly cards. The ones I've got at home are much better. Why? Because they have my face on it, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="25">I rule my castle with an iron fist! Those that serve under me must perform at the absolute highest level. If they don't? Well, the deepest parts of my dungeon will be the last thing they will ever see!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="28">Hmph! Had it been one of my servants giving me this hand, I would have had them thrown into the dungeon!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="217">I better not catch any of you cheating. If I do see you doing it, I'll have a special place in my dungeons just for you!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">These cards… their very sight makes me want to shred them!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">This is no hand worthy of a princess! I demand new cards!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Preposterous! </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmph! No matter, I bet you peasants don't even have a pair! Ohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1">Ugh, I just remembered. I have to do a photo-shoot later today. Sigh... It's just so hard being a princess!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="3">Someone! Get me a fruit juice! I'm thirsty! &lt;br&gt; ...Helloooooo!? Are you deaf?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="9">If I find out that any of you have been conspiring against me, I shall bring you to my dungeon and torture you personally! This isn't a threat... It. Is. A. &lt;i&gt;Promise!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">The nerve of you lot... Giving me this horrible hand just because you're jealous of &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph! This is &lt;i&gt;blasphemy!&lt;/i&gt; Blasphemy, I say!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">How utterly frustrating! I feel a conspiracy afoot!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is outrageous! This is unfair! What kind of monster would give a princess like me this hand!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" oneShotId="3">
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Hmph, my delicate feet have been standing on the cold floor for far too long. You! ~player~! Get on your hands and knees. I need a place to sit on.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" id="2" oneShotId="6">
                <test expr="~background~" value="paris rooftop" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="24">What beautiful and stunning scenery! This would be the perfect place for someone to declare their love for me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="18" oneShotId="7">
                <test expr="~background~" cmp="!=" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">Hmm...This place is way too &lt;i&gt;dull&lt;/i&gt; for my liking. In my humble opinion, pink would suit it better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="8" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="violins" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">I have the most magnificent idea... Guards! Bring me the orchestra. This would greatly improve the atmosphere.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="6" priority="0">
                <condition status="alive" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="18">Hmph, I don't have all day, ~player~. Pick already!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="19">My patience runs thin, ~player~. Get to it!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="253">I know you've never seen a lady quite as stunning as me, ~player~. But I have other things to do after this game, so get moving!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0" id="45">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="sweetheart0" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" marker="Sweet_Meia0">Silly low-born! A princess like me doesn't need the validation or praise from commoners. But I still deserve it all the same.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Sweet_Meia0">Is it not natural to praise those that are superior to you? Though I do not need the admiration of those beneath me, it is still the right thing for them to do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="46">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="sweetheart0" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweet_Jura0">If you were even half as pretty as I am, you would understand the desire to flaunt your beauty everywhere you go.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Sweet_Jura0">How absurd of you to think that I am anything less than &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; most elegant and pretty princess that has ever walked the earth. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="47">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="sweetheart0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Sweet_Revy0">Me? Ending up creamed? Oh please, leave it to the serf to not understand that a princess always wins in the end! </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="Sweet_Revy0">I can hardly take the comments of a lady that smells of cigarettes and cheap booze seriously. At least it's clear who is going to end up "creamed" in the end! Ohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="51">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="sweet01" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" marker="Nagatoro0">Something wrong, &lt;i&gt;peasant?&lt;/i&gt; Can't handle the beauty that is I? Sweetheart?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="52">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_royalty1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="Aqua_Royality0">It's not my fault that you're too stupid to realise how a proper princess is supposed to act. I'm simply better than everyone else.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Hmm... It seems I'm not getting the attention and adoration I deserve. This can only mean one thing: you don't know who I am. Impertinent, but I suppose it cannot be helped. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="21">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" font-size="small">Unbelievable! after I put in all that effort in telling you why I am the most desired princess of all, you all &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; aren't giving me the praise I am due! Perhaps you imbeciles need to hear more examples of why &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am the greatest princess that has ever lived!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="22">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Hmph, though I find it absurd that I lost again, I do not shy away from my body like other princesses. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="26">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Ohohoho! Do you think I feel ashamed having to show off my beautiful figure to the world? No, of course not! The world should be grateful for having me on it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You lucky fools don't know how good you all have it! For you all will witness the full beauty of the most elegant, attractive, stunning, brilliant, and most gorgeous princess of all!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Not one of you is worthy of what you are about to witness. This kind of beauty is one of a kind. There is no other princess... no... there is no other lady alive who compares to me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Fufu~ One more measly strip won't change the outcome of this match.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Struggle all you like, peasants. It won't change the outcome of this match.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You will &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; and you will &lt;i&gt;fail&lt;/i&gt; trying to beat me! One more loss means nothing to the mighty sweetheart!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't get too cocky, losers! Sweetheart has never &lt;i&gt;ever&lt;/i&gt; lost in &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Don't get too comfortable now. I am still destined to win and see you all grovel before me!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Ohohohoho! Your struggles to beat me are meaningless! Attempt it all you want, but you will not succeed!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Hmph, I might not have any big things left to take off. This doesn't make my stripping any less important! So keep your eyes on me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-upset.png">They say that you can't always win... Which is utter nonsense! I &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; win! But... ugh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You should &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; count yourself lucky that I am such a delicate princess. I can accept this loss, even if it was totally undeserved! But...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Alright, which of you losers decided to cheat to make me lose? ...Not going to talk, are we? I'll be sure to remember that.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Impudent! Cheating against a princess is punishable by death! But if the one who cheated comes forward about it, I might just lower the sentence to community service... Not going to speak up now, are you? Tsk.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Ugh! Princesses aren't supposed to lose! Which of you vermins caused this? Was it you, ~player~? That guilty look on your face says enough!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Cheaters! Every single one of you! Once I find out how you are all doing this, you will be toast! You hear me? Toast!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I am &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; close to summoning my flail and starting to bash all your heads in, you cheaters! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="5" id="28">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" font-size="smaller">Do you have any idea how hard it was to find these immaculate shoes? Within and around the castle, I am the only proper lady within my kingdom. While everyone else is but simple Sprout Moles, who have &lt;i&gt;tofu&lt;/i&gt; for feet. Which is, of course, not appropriate for a lady of my caliber.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="29">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" font-size="small">I cannot believe that you dirty perverts managed to undress me all the way. Here I am trying to be a good sport and play along even when I unrightfully lost a few rounds. But every single one of you misused my generous gifts! Despite this, you &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; demand I take everything off...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" font-size="smaller">I am none other than the most wealthy, charming, and alluring princess that has ever walked the Earth! I have hundreds of fans throwing themselves at me every day, statues of myself in every corner of my castle! The name Sweetheart must forever be branded on those feeble little minds of yours!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="23">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" font-size="smaller">I am also incredibly humble and give a lot to the poor. Who else would let her underlings live inside of her castle? And the only thing I want is their total obedience and loyalty. It is hard being this generous. But it is just one of the many good deeds I do as the most captivating donut princess of all time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="24">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png">Kneel, all! You are about to witness the best pair of breasts you will ever witness in your lifespan!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="25">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png">My ever adoring fans would kill for a chance to see me, Sweetheart, in her full unfiltered glory! Though you troglodytes don't deserve it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="31">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png">Though these might just seem like simple wrist bands to the untrained eye. Like everything else that I wear and own, it is of the highest quality. Made from the most expensive of threads, and made by my servants to fit my elegant figure.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1" id="43">
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Donut_Girl">I am the cutest, sexiest, most earnest donut girl that has ever existed! There is no-one in the world who can even come close to how desirable I am!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="27">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Now that you know why &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am the most important lady here, I expect every single one of you to shower me with your affection from here on out. A princess deserves nothing less, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="20">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Rejoice! As the most benevolent and wonderful Sweetheart has given the peasants a sight they won't ever forget! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="19">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Here it is! Sweetheart in her purest form! Bask in the glory that is I, Sweetheart! Cry, for you will never ever have a figure more unfathomable than mine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Those wrist bands are worth more than your entire life, ~player~. So don't try and touch them with your filthy hands. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Don't even think about touching those wrist bands, ~player~. They are far too expensive to be touched by &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; hands.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Hmph, why am I even trying to tell you these kinds of things? I doubt peasants like you even understand the value of a good set of shoes. I bet that you get all yours from the garbage bin! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">...I just got &lt;i&gt;irritatingly&lt;/i&gt; reminded that there used to be weirdos within my castle that kept asking to be "stepped on". At first I thought that they simply enjoyed being tortured... How wrong I was.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="30">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" font-size="smaller">However... Ohohoho... How could you all not? With my dazzling looks... My charming smile... My gregarious personality. It must be so difficult to even stand in my presence! Like everyone else I have ever met, you are just jealous of me! And wish to be all that I am! Unfortunately for all of you, that will &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; happen!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Foolish boy! Did you really think you would last long against the phenomenal Sweetheart?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">OHOHO! Is that the best you can do, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Disgraceful behavior, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmph! Child's play! You never stood a chance against the lustrous Sweetheart! </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Ohohoho~ How unsurprising.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">It doesn't seem like you know how to impress a princess. I suppose I'll keep my expectations low for you. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Leave it to someone like ~name~ to not know how to play a simple card game.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Being a loser fits you well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Submit to me, ~name~! I, Sweetheart, demand it!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Make your choice, ~name~. Either you take off something good, or I will make you regret it.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Please your princess, ~name~! Bare your body for me.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Grovel before me, ~name~! Worship your princess!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't just stand there like a doofus, ~name~! Your duchess is awaiting your attention and obedience!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Go ahead, ~name~. Embarrass yourself for me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My radiance is everlasting. It's only natural for you to strip and &lt;i&gt;bask&lt;/i&gt; in my heavenly radiance.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nothing you could do would ever compare to my status, ~name~. However, perhaps you might yet surprise me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">You cannot match what I am, ~name~. But if you're that confident to try, then go on. Impress me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">OHOHOHO! Silly boy, how could you ever hope to compete against me?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I will spare but a single moment for you, ~name~. Don't waste it!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">A real knight in shining armor wouldn't have lost this round. Which says enough about what kind of person &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; are, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Oh, it's just ~name~ who lost. Nothing of interest.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Choose wisely, ~name~. A bored princess is a dangerous princess.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Better start stripping, peasant. Best not to keep me waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I can already hear your excuses coming out of your mouth about why you lost, but please, spare my ears the trouble.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh my, it seems that there is something you &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; good at, ~name~. Losing!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Don't be a wimp, ~name~. No-one cares what you strip as long as &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am here.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Something wrong, ~name~? Afraid you're getting overshadowed by me? The most adorable princess of all time? Well, you are, so stop whining and start stripping.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You had better pick something worth my time! I won't stand for it if you pick something boring while I'm here in my full glory!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Hmph! You get an important chance to impress me right now, ~name~. Give it your all! Or else you're going to regret it!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Why would anyone care that ~name~ has to strip? While I'm here showing off just how amazing I truly am?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Something wrong, ~name~? I'm not distracting you, am I? Ohohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You lost on purpose, didn't you, ~name~? Don't try to lie your way out of it, I just know you did it to show yourself off to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Foolish girl! Did you really think you would last long against the phenomenal Sweetheart?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Like taking candy from a sprout!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Yawn&lt;/i&gt;. Too easy!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Get used to this feeling of losing, peasant.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">A loss for you, means victory for me. As it should be! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh no, ~name~ lost. Who could have&lt;/i&gt; ever &lt;i&gt;seen that coming?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Try not to make this &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; boring.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-amused.png">As I am &lt;i&gt;royalty&lt;/i&gt;, this tie should be a win for me and a loss for all others!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bored.png">That better not be all that you strip, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Your accessories are but naught compared to mine, commoner. Now remove them at once!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Don't waste my time with idle chit-chat, ~name~. Your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural( are| is)~ hardly deserving of any attention.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Like a pebble trying to outshine a ruby. How pathetic.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I have never met a man that knew how to properly accessorize... And I still haven't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Nngh... Huh? ~name~ is taking something off? And why should &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; care about that!? Don't you see I'm busy spoiling myself? Ugh, &lt;i&gt;fine&lt;/i&gt;. I'm paying attention.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Think...&lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; carefully about your next move, ~name~. It's a decision between life and death! </state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I don't care about your silly little story, ~name~. What I want is for you to be on your hands and knees before me!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hnngg... Stop trying to get my attention while I'm busy with myself!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Oh, &lt;i&gt;yay&lt;/i&gt;. I'm missing &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; time because some douchebag over there has to try and get my attention!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Why even waste your time with such horrid-looking accessories? Keep them home next time. I don't want to see them again.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What an eye sore. Better to get rid of it.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I have met many bachelors that think they could impress me by giving me some cheap baubles. They remind me of what you are taking off, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">You have too many insignificant pieces of baubles for my liking, ~name~. Yes, I have those as well. But I'm the prettiest girl there is, so I'm allowed to have them. Besides, they look amazing on me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Is this your attempt at trying to tease me? Ohohoho! I'd suggest becoming a jester. It would suit someone as silly as you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Ugh, it reeks of being cheap.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">If a bachelor ever did dare give me something so horrid looking, I would answer back in kind. By crushing his family jewels. </state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Words fail to describe just how utterly disappointing you are.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I should be insulted by the utter lack of respect that you are showing me, ~name~. But perhaps I'm being too harsh on you. Can't expect pigs to have good manners now, can we?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I wouldn't want to be found dead wearing that!... Unless you got it from your grandmother... That would be the only good reason to wear it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">If this doesn't end with you kissing my feet and worshipping me, it's not worth my attention.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Do you simpletons know nothing about satisfying a princess?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Move along, I have better things to spend my time on, like loving myself!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph. And to think I gave you a glimpse of my attention, only for you to waste it!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Some people say not to judge a book by it's cover. But if the book had a picture of ~name~ on it, I can assure you I would never read it in my life!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Disturbing a princess while she is touching herself should be a bannable offence!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good riddance!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">&lt;i&gt;Just&lt;/i&gt; your ~clothing~? That's not good enough! I demand you take off more!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">May I never see something so ugly ever again.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'm going to pretend you took off something more interesting...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Throw it into the trash bag. Where it belongs!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-amused.png">I can't even &lt;i&gt;imagine&lt;/i&gt; wearing something &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; ugly. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I don't have all day, ~name~. Chop-chop!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm certain it took all your brain power to come up with &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; as your choice of item to strip.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I doubt that this will prelude to something more interesting. But I'm willing to give it a shot, so you had better be grateful.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">​Why delay the inevitable? We &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; know that I'm going to win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Can't you just skip the prelude and get to the final part of your performance? I'm getting rather bored waiting for such insignificant strips.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Those idiotic fans of mine had better be preparing for the next part of "Sweetheart's Quest For Hearts" while I'm away.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">You aren't impressing &lt;i&gt;anyone&lt;/i&gt; picking &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; boring small thing. </state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Uninteresting and unneeded. Remove what needs to be removed and let us pick up the pace.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Every trinket has its own story. This doesn't mean I'm interested in hearing it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Nothing you do will take away from my intense self-loving, ~name~. So make it quick.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">​Make it quick, ~name~. I desire all eyes to be me, not you.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Don't talk too much, I'm trying to enjoy myself!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Bla bla bla!&lt;/i&gt; I'm ~name~, and I'll talk about totally unnecessary things while a beautiful princess is touching herself!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">&lt;i&gt;Hmm... I'm amazing&lt;/i&gt;. I- Huh? Oh, it's just ~name~ being a dissapointment again.  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="12" priority="0">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Bleh, this girl barks too much for my liking, someone put a collar on her. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="49">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">Just when I thought you couldn't be any weirder, freakshow.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I didn't think you could disappoint me more than you already did, ~name~. But here we are.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Don't expect me to comment on each and every insignificant strip you do, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This only further cements the fact that you have no taste.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Is that all you will strip? Do you think you can just waste &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; time like this? Disgraceful!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Commoners do so enjoy ugly baubles. It's something I will never understand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Remove as many baubles as you need, commoner. It won't stop the inevitable.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">It's almost impressive how someone can be so mind numbingly &lt;i&gt;unexciting&lt;/i&gt;. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What a mundane choice. Are you always like this in your daily life? Don't answer that, I already know what you're going to say.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Who even wears such an ugly trinket to begin with?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">​May I never see anything so ugly ever again.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">​Smart move, ~name~. No-one would care what you would take off while I'm showing my passion.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Your attempts at trying to take the spotlight from me are nothing more than irritating, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">All that attention hogging just for you to take off a bauble, bleh.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Back to what is really important, me!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Don't disturb my self-loving for something so measily ever again!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">I wouldn't want to be found dead wearing something like that.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">You aren't important enough to be talking so much, ~name~. Proceed without further delay.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I'm sure that whatever you're talking about is very important to you, but I couldn't care less.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">What is this insufferable noise I'm hearing? Oh... it's just ~name~ talking.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Your ~clothing~ look~clothing.ifPlural( like they belong|s like it belongs)~ to a vagabond. Ew. </state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Boooooooooooooring&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Ugh, hellooooo? ~Name~? The most charming girl you have ever seen in your life is already showing off her alluring body. Take something better off!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Could you be &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; less interesting? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Time is of the essence, ~name~. If it isn't going to be interesting, don't waste my time on it.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Boring your princess deserves punishment, ~name~. I'm merciful enough to let you know beforehand.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Aren't you supposed to try and woo the pretty princess? It's not that you have a chance with me, I just want to see you try and fail.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh, wow. You picked your ~clothing~. How daring, really. I'm tingling with excitement.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">No romance has ever started by taking off something dull! Just something to keep in mind.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">You won't sweep a princess off her feet by choosing the safe option, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Sigh&lt;/i&gt;, you really are hopeless. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">It's quite miserable that even my stupid fans have better taste in fashion than you do, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Why not just strip it all off at once? Spares me a lot of time that I can spend pampering myself.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">That was a waste of my time. Let us continue before you arouse my anger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">A peasants prelude is hardly worth my time.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I shouldn't forget to get through all that fanmail I got earlier today.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">It is but all too clear to me that you lack the flair to properly entertain me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I will never understand a commoner's fashion.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let us continue before I lose my temper.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">~Name~ truly is a shining example of not knowing how to impress.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="single" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="221">And that is why you're still single, ~name~. Why would anyone be interested in someone as dull as you? Ohohoho! Hm? How do I know that he is single? Well, just look at him!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'd rather watch paint dry at this pace.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hurry along, peasant. You're not waiting for your harvest to sprout. You're here to &lt;i&gt;entertain me!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">My servants are either on time, or end up somewhere &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; dark. Just a little something to keep in mind, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Me, being the most astounding princess to have ever walked the earth, has better things to do than wait for you to strip, ~name~. So, hurry up.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">While you are doing your... thing. I'll be standing here, showing off my magnificence.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Only a fool would throw away this golden opportunity by choosing something so insignificant.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">That... &lt;i&gt;thing&lt;/i&gt; you're taking off looks like you got it from the garbage can... in other words, it's utterly worthless! </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Name~ clearly doesn't appreciate theatrics.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">What is this... overwhelming feeling of dread and sorrow I'm feeling? Oh... it's just ~name~ taking something off.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I'm at a loss for words. ~Name~? Taking off something unexciting? &lt;i&gt;Say it ain't so!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Bah! Is that all you will be taking off? Disappointment must be your middle name then.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hmph, not pink enough.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Any lady worth her salt should know how to stylize, ~name~. I'd suggest you look into it for your own sake.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I would have picked something more exciting. But then again, I am the most &lt;i&gt;dazzling&lt;/i&gt; princess there is!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's not as if I expected more from you anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">...Are you &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; talking? Ugh, what nonsense.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmmm... I could really go for a massage. It's been too long since I last had one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-bored.png">I could be betting on horse races, or be dining in the most luxurious of establishments. But no, I'm doomed to spend my time with Lady &lt;i&gt;Tiresome&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Had you been any more interesting, I wouldn't have minded waiting for your measly little strip, ~name~. But you are as interesting as watching grass grow.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Could you at least &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; to not bore me? I know that might seem hard for a neanderthal like you, but I'm sure even you can figure &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; out.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">At least I don't have to worry about ~name~ trying to steal the spotlight from me. Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">...It is a good thing I didn't need to pay to attend this table... I would have demanded my money back by now.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Boring, boring, boring! You're all so boring! You should be banned from playing strip poker ever again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="single" role="target" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="211">And that is why you're still single, ~name~. Who would anyone be interested in someone as dull as you? Ohohoho! Hm? How do I know she is single? Well, just look at her!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Well, look at that. So you &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; know how to be interesting. It took you long enough.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">This is much more entertaining than seeing useless baubles coming off.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">With your beloved princess watching, there is no way you would disappoint her, right? Right!?</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Don't make me regret giving you my divine attention, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I doubt this is going to be any more interesting than when you take off an accessory.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">It seems that losing has been the only way for you to get my attention, ~name~. I understand you want to impress me, but you will have to do better than that! As I am not easily impressed!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">So, you believe your body is of adequate quality for it to be laid bare before me? The one, the only, magnificent Sweetheart? I shall be the judge of that!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hey! ~Name~! You're supposed to entice me with your stripping skills! And sweep me off my feet! You can't afford to be lazy while performing for a princess!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Go on, ~name~. Impress your dazzling princess.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let us see if this raises your attractiveness by any significant amount. I wouldn't get your hopes up, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">For once you didn't disappoint me, ~name~. A rare occurrence that I hope you can maintain.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">And another step closer to my glorious victory! Ohohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Rarely do I find myself entranced by someone else's body. Yours... doesn't change that fact~</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't you feel any shame? Showing off your perverted body in front of a princess?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hardly worth the time of a &lt;i&gt;delicate&lt;/i&gt; princess like me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Your efforts to entertain me are not going unnoticed, ~name~. That's not to say it's good enough, but it is being seen. Ohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">But even now, you aren't showing anything truly worthwhile. Such is the life of a plebeian, I suppose.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Took you long enough! Don't you know it's rude to make a princess wait? You should grovel for my forgiveness!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Keep this pace up, peasant. I have waited long enough for my entertainment. </state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">​It doesn't matter how hard you try to impress me, ~name~. At the end of the day, you're just a pleb to me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Don't try to outshine me, ~name~. Well... not like you ever &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; outshine me!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmmm... not the &lt;i&gt;worst&lt;/i&gt; thing you could have chosen. But hardly the best either. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">How silly of you to think that something so &lt;i&gt;meager&lt;/i&gt; can impress me.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Put your back into it, ~name~. This is supposed to be your big moment! It won't ever be as big as mine, but you should at least try and entertain me by trying!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">How joyous to see you strip your ~clothing~, ~name~. I was getting tired from looking at it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">&lt;i&gt;Could it be? ~name~ picking something interesting to take off? My oh my, the world must have gone mad!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">It takes a lot of money, skill, and knowledge to properly know how to dress yourself. The three things you don't have!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Keep striping for your princess, ~name~! Grovel and humiliate yourself for me!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Ugh... Could you stop talking for a moment? You are not &lt;i&gt;nearly&lt;/i&gt; interesting enough to talk that much.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Have you learned &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; from my amazing performance, ~name~? At this point, I'm just surprised you even know how to bathe! Ohohoho!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Was that supposed to be some kind of big reveal? I found it to be hardly entertaining.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">A whole lot of noise for a whole lot of nothing.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Congratulations! You still look as uninteresting as before.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Next time, I'd suggest going on your knees and begging for my help. It's quite clear that you don't know a single thing about being &lt;i&gt;alluring&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I guess your choice wasn't... &lt;i&gt;horrible&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Hmph, you have no flare for the dramatic, ~name~. This would be the moment for a lady to entice all those around her. But it seems you couldn't even do something as simple as that.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh my, what is this? has ~name~ finally managed to sweep the oh so charming Sweetheart off her feet?&lt;/i&gt; Pfffft... as if.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Only ~name~ could manage to be dull while taking something big off.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">For something that was supposed to be a &lt;i&gt;big&lt;/i&gt; reveal. You once again managed to bore me, ~name~. It's almost as if you have a natural talent for it. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Have you seen how amazing I look? How am I ever supposed to care about someone like you when I'm right here?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="46">Moment of truth, ~name~. Let's see if you have the kind of body that will make me swoon.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="45">A rare moment in which I will share the spotlight. Don't disappoint.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="93">Let's see if you are worthy of becoming my servant~</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="94">​A man's chest is one of the few things that can still impress me, go on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="99">I don't &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; your chest to enjoy myself, ~name~. But I still welcome it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="100">This is the moment to impress me, ~name~! I might just look at you in a different light after this.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="101">Enough diddle-daddle! Show your princess what you're made of!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="102">A dreamy chest is all I desire. You wouldn't disappoint me, right, ~name~?"</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">What a pleasant surprise. At least you have something good to look at.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good! Servants should look their best when they serve me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="41">It's... serviceable. I had high hopes it would be better.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="42">It's not... terrible, but it's not great either.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="43">It was a bit presumptuous of me to expect your chest to be as great as mine.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="44">​Nothing to write home about, but alas. Not everyone can have a chest as perfect as mine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="95">That's more like it! Bare your everything for your princess!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="96">You should have done that once I started touching myself, ~name~. But I will let it slide... this time!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="97">Ugh... I wish I had more servants like you to look at. The current ones have no chest to speak of.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="98">Not nearly as fulfilling to look at compared to my own chest, but it will do.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="195">You've been a bore from start to finish, so I have no high hopes that this will be any better.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="196">Nothing that you are about to reveal will be good enough for me, ~name~. Don't get your hopes up.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="197">Here comes the part in which I will endlessly shame you for being too big, too small, or too average! OHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="198">It must be exhausting being that bad at the game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="194">And how is this supposed to be a punishment? Do you know how many men try and fail to get my attention on a daily basis? They would love the chance to show their puny cocks to me.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="199">Oh? You're going to show off your manhood? My, that's perfect. I was about ready to crush your balls if you didn't hurry up.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="200">You've done nothing to deserve my attention, so I have no desire to give you any now that you desire it.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="201">You're no prince charming, ~name~. Nothing you have between your legs will change that fact.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="31">Mmm... Is that even three inches tall? My, that is much too short!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="32">...Bwhahahahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="33">That wouldn't even be good enough for a peasant, let alone a princess of my caliber.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="34">Fun-sized? It's not even bite-sized!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="35" marker="chastity">I don't even know if I have a chastity cage that small in my dungeon...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="39">Bleh! I should kick you between your legs for showing me something so pathetic. But you would probably like it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="40">Oh, I'm sure you have a &lt;i&gt;great&lt;/i&gt; personality, ~name~. Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="142">It's about the size of my pinkie finger. How do you even find that thing when you try to touch yourself?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9" id="9" oneShotId="4" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="chastity" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="37">I don't think we even have a chastity cage &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; small. I'd have to get one custom made. That's just how small it is! Ohohoho!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="38">&lt;i&gt;Yawn&lt;/i&gt;. How utterly uninteresting...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="131">Average... I don't &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; average! The biggest, or the smallest--it doesn't matter to me, I demand perfection and that is all I will accept!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="132">Well, would you look at that, ~name~. It's as boring as you are! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="133">Hope you weren't too proud of that thing of yours, ~name~. It's nothing special.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="135">All that build up... for this? &lt;i&gt;Really?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="136">I would have preferred it to be smaller. At least then I could have had the joy of laughing at you.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="137">I had no expectations and I'm still disappointed. </state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="143">I wouldn't sully my hands for something &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; mediocre. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="138">A tool fit for a mindless barbarian such as yourself, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="139">Maybe you do have some use, ~name~. Instead of using my flail, I could just use that oversized cock of yours instead!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="140">Perhaps that would impress a commoner. But it's too big for me to find useful.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="141">Bigger isn't better, ~name~. Unless it's a statue of me, of course! OHOHOHO!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="146">I suppose you have to compensate for your monotonous personality in someway.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="147">&lt;i&gt;Sigh&lt;/i&gt;. Do I seriously need to buy a bigger chastity belt just for you? What a pain.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="144">The bigger they are, the more pain I can give it!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="145">That &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; fit in between my divine bosom... Ha! As if I would let someone like &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; touch them!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="120">We already know what you have, ~name~. Everyone can see beforehand what you are trying to cover up, you aren't impressing anyone with it.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="203">Oh? Is it time already for me to mock your inferior breasts? How delightful.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="202">Go on, ~name~. This is the perfect moment to show why I'm better than you!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="204">It's hard to get excited about another lady's breasts, when mine are perfect.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="218">An ordinary commoner might be interested in what you are about to reveal, ~name~. But a lady of my caliber is not so easily impressed.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="219">&lt;i&gt;Oh, I get to see a commoner's breasts. How delightful.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="220">If I may suspend my disbelief that you had some kind of dignity before you came here. I'd say this is the moment that you lost what little remaining dignity you had left! Ohohoho! </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="248">Watch out everyone! Prepare yourself for the disappointment ~name~ is about to bring us!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="48">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Megumi_nobra">All that bombastic behavior of yours really amounted to nothing when it really mattered! Ohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="103">Oh dear. Those are just pitiful.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="104">Small, in both status &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; size!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="105">Those wouldn't even count as proper opening acts!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="106">Is that what a commoner's chest looks like? Ohoho~ ... So puny and immature compared to mine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="107">It is often said that a maiden's chest is pure and sizable, but yours strays far from that compared to mine.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="108">I doubt you get &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; suitors with a pitiful chest like yours. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="109">There truly is &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; worthwhile about you now, is there, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="110">I suppose you deserve some respect, ~name~. I wouldn't have played strip poker if I had your chest size.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="7" priority="0">
                <condition filter="wealthy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't understand. Why haven't you bought yourself a less disappointing bosom?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="119">If you were pretty enough, those medium-sized breasts could have been worth something! Ohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="123">Mediocre breasts for a mediocre woman. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="148">It seems that we do have something in common, ~name~. We are both blessed with the perfect chest size, even if &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; didn't deserve it.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="149">&lt;i&gt;Hmph!&lt;/i&gt; You think your breasts measure in comparison to mine? Yours are saggy and deflated--mine are basically &lt;i&gt;perfect&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="150">Don't think you can compare your breasts to mine, ~name~. Mine are elegant, perky, soft, in other words, &lt;i&gt;perfect&lt;/i&gt;! Yours are just okay at best!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="151">Medium is too good for a lowborn such as yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="173">No need to be jealous of me, ~name~. Your chest size is perfectly fine... for someone as ordinary as you!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="174">Nothing noteworthy. The impact of you showing your bust to us will be forgotten in mere moments.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="111">Big lumps of fat, nothing more.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="112">Commoners do seem to prefer bigger for some reason... &lt;i&gt;bleh&lt;/i&gt;! They have no taste. </state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="113">Those look quite fitting... for a cow!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="114">Some say that having such absurdly large mammaries is a gift. I say, they make you look like you belong on a farm.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Look at them being all saggy, there is no grace to be found.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="115">Those seem like perfect stress balls after a hard day of being a princess.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="116" font-size="smaller">Your breasts are a harrowing reminder of a piece of fan art I received. I had double D breasts, black lipstick, and I was missing my donut hole. As you can imagine, my reaction to this vile abomination was nothing short of being justified, as I threw the creator of such vile art into the dungeon!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="117">Can you imagine? Having your own body hurt you by its size? Well, I can't. But I'm sure you do, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="118">Oh, I'm sure you have a lot of people that like you for your &lt;i&gt;personality&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" stage="1" />
                <condition count="1" status="chest_visible" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">You act as if you are nothing more than a common concubine. Please, have some dignity while in the presence of a princess.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="pubic_hair_peek" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I wonder if your crotch will be visible behind that curtain of unkempt hair! Ohohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="slutty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="247">Oh great, the local town bicycle is going to reveal her used vulva. &lt;i&gt;How joyous&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="92">Oh no, you have to show your mediocre snatch to the world. I am &lt;i&gt;certain&lt;/i&gt; people would want to see that.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="152">Let's just get to the point, ~name~. You aren't nearly attractive enough for people to stare at it for long.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="205">If I seem disinterested in seeing how your groin looks, ~name~. It's because I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; disinterested.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="207">You don't look like the type that would groom themselves down there, ~name~. So I doubt we will get something entertaining to look at.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="209">You don't have the necessary flare to make this exciting, ~name~. Let us get to the point -- where I will laugh at how insignificant you are!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="208">Why not get down on the ground and start masturbating right after revealing yourself, ~name~? That way you might have a &lt;i&gt;chance&lt;/i&gt; to impress me. </state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">We have all seen how perfectly crafted &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am, ~name~. Do you think you can compare? Or is it going to be unsightful like the rest of you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="83">Not nearly as cute as mine, hmph.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="84">With your back against the wall, will you make a comeback and win it all? Or succumb before me?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="85">Were you hoping to get laid when you came here, ~name~? As you seem so desperate to show your womanhood off.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="86">I've never really looked at another woman's public area too closely.  The only one that is worth my gaze is my own.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="87">Mine looks better, no questions asked.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="88">I expected nothing more from a low-born like you.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="89">Hmph, decent at best. But none compare to my beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="91">Just surrender already, ~name~. Accept your fate!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">...Barbaric.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I knew you had no decency the moment I laid my eyes upon you. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-9" id="50">
                <condition role="target" character="petra" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Sweetheart_petra_talk0">You, girl with the purple hair that speaks weird... What was your name again? Peta? Pera? Petra?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-9" id="35">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh... My poor beautiful eyes! Why did you need such a light show? Just for you to dye your hair yellow? You look ridiculous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="37">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Cat_Noire_Reveal">Why do I suddenly have the feeling that I'm about to be disappointed?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="34">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades Out" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good riddance. Who would ever want to play this game with a drug addict? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="32" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" sayingMarker="COCK" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="COCK_Sweetheart1">Please hurry up, peasants. I doubt that what you two are about to show is going to be int-... Huh? W-what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="39">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" sayingMarker="blade_power" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">As if my ears didn't suffer enough from your obnoxious behavior, now you're going to blind me too? Had this been my castle, I would have thrown you into the dungeon the moment you spoke!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-9" id="40">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">It seems my thoughts were correct, you do belong in a freakshow.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="41">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="2" sayingMarker="keyblade_reveal" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">So what? I can summon my weapon out of thin air as well. You aren't as special as you think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="36">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">Leave it to the &lt;i&gt;lowborn&lt;/i&gt; to make a big fuzz about something as silly as dying your hair. And it's the wrong color too! Everyone knows pink is the prettiest color of them all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="42">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" sayingMarker="planar_form" />
                <test expr="~target.persistent.strange_harmonies~" cmp="&gt;=" value="55" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Stop screaming you weirdo! Or did you just realise how ugly you are compared to me? If so, I understand. I wouldn't be able to stay calm either if I were you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="38">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades In" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">My disappointment is immeasurable, and my day is ruined.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="33" oneShotId="8">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="COCK_Sweetheart1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="COCK_Sweetheart2">Well, at least you two managed to be interesting. That is more than I can say about ~Player~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="67">It's only natural for the riff-raff to lie down before nobility such as I.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="68">You were barely entertaining while playing. I hope you're more &lt;i&gt;engaging&lt;/i&gt; while &lt;i&gt;performing&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="69">And just like that, the game is over for you, ~name~. The only thing that's left, is for you to put up a good show for me. Don't disappoint. </state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="70">Absolutely pathetic, ~name~. I cannot even entertain the idea that you've been anything else than soul-suckingly dull.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="73">Perfect. I was about to get bored before you lost, ~name~. Make it a good show, or else. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="71">​Just the person I wanted to see fail, good job pleasing your princess, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="72">This is the only time in which I'll accept failure around me! OHOHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="81">I demand to be entertained, ~name~. Don't keep me waiting.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="74">Chop-chop! ~Name~. You're humilation cannot wait!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="76">No time to waste, ~name~! Your princess desires a show!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="75">Be sure to grovel before me as you humiliate yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="77">I don't want to hear any blether from you, ~name~. You lost, your opinion is invalid... Not that it has ever been valid! OHOHOHOHO!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="78">You put up a valiant effort, ~name~. But everything and everyone will end up beneath me! One way or another!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="79">For putting up such a &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt; fight, ~name~, I will bestow upon you, my heel grinding your member to dust! No need to thank me, I always look out for my sla-... I mean subjects.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="82">Yes, ~name~. You may look at me while doing your dirty deed, but if you even think about doing something with me with that obscene thing, there will be hell to pay. </state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="124">Don't enjoy this &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; much, you pervert. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="11" oneShotId="5" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Didn't you want to humiliate yourself? Too bad! Get to it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Don't blame yourself for losing, you never stood a chance anyway! OHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">I look at you because I find your struggles amusing, ~name~. There is no other reason.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">The sight of seeing those beneath me struggle is something that will never get stale.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">You really aren't any different from an animal in heat, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Me? Embarrassed? Nonsense! I quite enjoy seeing the riffraff humiliate themselves before me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Plenty of fans that would want me to look at them while doing such obscene things, ~name~. So be grateful that I'm even giving you the satisfaction of my gaze.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="168">Someone should put a leash on you, ~name~. It would be fitting for a barking dog like you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Could you be a little more quiet, ~name~? You're ruining the atmosphere.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I do so enjoy the pitiful cries of a man that knows his place.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You lost on purpose, didn't you, ~name~? Given how much you seem to enjoy yourself. Though, I suppose no man can resist being near me for long before giving into their carnal desires.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">There is something strangely amusing seeing a man surrender himself to me like this.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">You try so hard... but it's still not good enough!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You are enjoying this humiliation too much for my taste.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Like an animal in heat, fitting for a dirty pig like you.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Just admit that this was your plan all along, ~name~. Rubbing yourself while looking at the one and only dazzling Sweetheart!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Go ahead, ~name~. Gaze upon my glory as you squirm around!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="16" priority="0">
                <condition filter="small_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="175">I understand that beauty such as mine is a once in a lifetime occurrence. So I will allow you to look at me as you flail around with that little stick of yours.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="176">I'm surprised you could even find that puny little thing down there! Ohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="177">I would never take someone like ~name~ as my groom. He wouldn't know how to satisfy a princess like me with that tiny pecker of his.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="178">No microscope in the world big enough to see what's going on down there!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="179">You must have wanted me to put you in your place, ~name~. Why else would you play strip poker with such a microscopic penis? At least you already know that you're beneath me. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="180">I feel bad for anyone you would convince to share a bed with you, ~name~. They would pull your pants down only to be greeted with a tool that can't do its job! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="181">I've got an important question to ask you, ~name~. Did you ever need a toy to please your partner? Given that what you have between your legs could never please anyone but yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="182">You seem to be struggling, ~name~. Perhaps you should use some tweezers to help you out. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="17" priority="0">
                <condition filter="medium_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="186">Your princess desires to be entertained, ~name~. And given how mediocre your shaft is, I expect you to give it your all to compensate for it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="183">Come on, ~name~! Go faster! Compensate for that average prick of yours by going all out!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="185">If you do a good enough job with that boring knob of yours, you might even keep &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; of your pride after this. Well, as little pride as you had in the first place.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="190">Even your performance is average. Pick up the pace or something! You have royalty looking at you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition status="chest_visible" role="self" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="122">Remember what I said about avoiding "cream-filled" jokes? A "glazed" donut will not do either! Point that thing away from me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Nearing your limit already? Pathetic.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I pity those that would be foolish enough to share a bed with you, ~name~. No-one wants someone that can't even last one minute.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Finishing so soon? Who said you were allowed to do so?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">If only you had someone to use that filthy rod on! </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah, nothing more amusing than seeing a lowborn grovel before me! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Perhaps a muzzel would suit you. ~name~. Just think about it, you finally get to be the dog that you really are!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-amused.png">...What a pathetic look on your face. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It seems you can't hold out for much longer, ~name~. Unsurprising, given you have someone as drop-dead gorgeous as me to look at. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="187">Don't point that ugly thing at me, ~name~. I am so far out of your league, even the idea of your filthy seed going near me makes me want to kick you between your legs.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Ugh. I hate how that &lt;i&gt;thing&lt;/i&gt; pulsates in your hand, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="188">Nearly done already? But I'm not done mocking you yet! Hold it in until I say you can cum, or else there will be consequences!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="51">​Ugh. Clean yourself, serf. You got it all over yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="52">Watch where you aim that thing!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="59">That's it? That's all you had? &lt;i&gt;Sigh&lt;/i&gt;. I guess it can't be helped. Common laborers like yourself have never managed to impress me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="58">If that's as long as you can last, you can kiss your love life goodbye! Ohohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="53">Tsk, and here I was enjoying myself watching you humiliate yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="54">Your pathetic squirms were delightful, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="55">Hey! Who said you were allowed to finish already!? </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="56">I'm expecting a beautiful bouquet from you right after this game, ~name~. Why? ...Because you were allowed to look at my stunning figure while doing it! That's why!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="169">I don't like sharing the spotlight, ~name~. So don't dilly-dally too much.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="170">Your best was never good enough to win from me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="171">Took you long enough! Don't you know it's rude to make a princess wait? </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="172">Ohohoho~ Are you prepared to be looked down upon and become ashamed of your actions? No? Too bad!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="243">We all have our place in the universe, ~name~. Yours is firmly underneath my feet!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="246">Finally! I've been waiting for you to start giving me a &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; show.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="254">Ohohoho~ This will be most entertaining. Seeing a low-born getting exactly what she deserves!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Remember! You are here to entertain me, so I don't accept slacking! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="239">Be sure to squirm plenty as I laugh at your pitiful display!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="240">Be delighted, ~name~. You get to look at the most stunning woman in the entire &lt;i&gt;world&lt;/i&gt; while doing your dirty deed. You may now praise me for it. Come on, don't be shy!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="241">Perhaps I should make a film out of this moment. "Sweetheart Puts A Servant In Their Place". Sounds like a lovely title, doesn't it? I bet I'd be praised for my ingenious idea.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="242" font-size="smaller">Well now, this is the perfect moment to ask this. But do you have any kind of special skill, ~name~? As I am sure your measly little performance is going to be anything but entertaining, if you have any kind of hidden talents, now would be the perfect moment to display them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="244">Some of my... &lt;i&gt;weirder&lt;/i&gt; fans have expressed a desire for me to sit on their face. You wouldn't happen to be that much of a weirdo, right ~name~? Right?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="245">If you need any kind of convincing, ~name~. I can always just summon my royal whip and whack you till you do it!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="265">Go on your hands and knees, ~name~. A princess such as myself shouldn't be standing all day. I deserve to sit on your back while you humiliate yourself beneath me, got it?</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="272">You should feel honored being allowed to do such a dirty deed while I'm here. And yes, you are allowed to look at my perfect body. Why? So that you can imprint my superiority into that little brain of yours!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hmph, how ungraceful. You don't know a single thing about loving yourself, do you? ~Name~?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Eyes up here, ~name~. If you're going to embarrass yourself, you might as well look at the prettiest woman of them all while you do it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You're in the presence of greatness! ~Name~. You had better show your appreciation by looking at me when you are being so unsightful! </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You're going way too slow! Pick up the pace, peasant!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Your moans are distracting me, ~name~. Put a plug into it or something. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Just because you're pleasuring yourself, doesn't mean you can stop praising me!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Failing to amuse me comes with a heavy price~</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Tick tock, tick tock. I don't have all day, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Name a better combination than ~name~ looking pathetic. They fit perfectly together!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't blame me for losing, ~name~. You should have played better if you didn't want to get humilated.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I would step on you to show my dominance! But a pervert like you would probably like it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">If you're going to embarrass yourself like this, you might as well make that mouth of yours useful.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="48">Ugh. You're hopeless, ~name~. After we're done here, I'm taking you with me to my &lt;i&gt;special&lt;/i&gt; dungeon, so I can show you how to properly love yourself. No need to say thank you, I know I'm a kind woman.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">If you aren't moaning my name, ~name~. then just shut up and keep going. </state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">You can still kiss my feet while you're doing this, ~name~. Don't keep me waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Your humiliation is supposed to be amusing for me, ~name~. Stop being so boring and do a handstand or something!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="193">What an amateur, how are you supposed to bring yourself to a climax with such pitiful movements?</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Seeing you flail around like an idiot almost makes me want to pity you... &lt;i&gt;almost.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I'm not hearing you moan my name, ~namer~. Try harder!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9" id="14" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="130">I'm here in all my beauty, so I don't accept the excuse of it being difficult for you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png">I had hoped you would have been more... enjoyable while touching yourself. So you better not climax until I'm satisfied, got it?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Do I dare say it? That your face looks cute in a pathetic way? Well, it does.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Though you and your performance were hardly worth my time. You might just save yourself from an endless amount of ridicule if you end it well. So look me in the eyes and moan my name like the good little servant you are.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I know you want me, ~Name~. Everyone wants me, but no-one can have me. You will just have to finish knowing you will never be worthy of Sweetheart's love.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I bet that the only reason you're enjoying yourself so much is because of me. What else could be the reason? Your own skills? I highly doubt that~</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I've never met someone quite as pitiful looking as you, ~name~. I love it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Almost done, huh? Tsk, leave it to someone like ~name~ to disappoint me until the very end.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Though I am happy to see you following my advice to not bore me, nobody said you were allowed to climax! Keep it in until I say you can!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This better end with you moaning my name and having learned your place, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Who said that you could climax already? I said you had to speed up, not that you were allowed to finish! That's for me to decide.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I'll be sure to savor every single pathetic moment of yours, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You can look at me with those puppy eyes all you want, ~name~. I'm not going to touch you until you pledge your servitude to me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="61">Hmph, I suppose your little performance wasn't &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; bad.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="60">I did get &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; meager enjoyment out of this. Which is more than what I expected from you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="63">Clean yourself up, you look embarrassing like that.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="65">And now, whenever I look at you, I will only see that pitiful face of yours that is consumed by pleasure. OHOHOHO!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="64">Hope you enjoyed your 15 minutes of fame, ~name~. Time for everyone's eyes to fall back on me!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="66">You didn't moan my name when you finished, ~name~. Unacceptable! Do it again and do it properly!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="206">I knew you didn't have it in you to be captivating, ~name~. Such amateurish movements! Ohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="238">You look &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; too happy about being humiliated, ~name~. How about you touch yourself down there again, and I will properly humiliate you this time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png">...I should be mad at all of you for cheating... But I have something much more important to do... me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png">Hmph... Just remember that you all don't deserve what I'm about to show your feeble brains!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-start_forfeit.png">Hmph, though I cannot stand the fact that I lost. At least I get to focus on myself now... and my body pillow with me on it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This is the only way I could ever get off! What else but an object with my &lt;i&gt;gorgeous&lt;/i&gt; body on it would suffice?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">This show I'm giving is worth &lt;i&gt;millions&lt;/i&gt; of clams! Something you plebians don't even deserve!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">If you &lt;i&gt;beg&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;grovel&lt;/i&gt;, and offer your body and soul to me! Maybe I'll allow one of you to come closer.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Nngh... I feel &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; good!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I could look at myself forever~</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">&lt;i&gt;Mmn...&lt;/i&gt; If only I could kiss myself on the lips.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Everyone wishes to marry me, but none other than myself is worthy of it!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="250">If only I had a mirror, that way I could enjoy myself even better! Such luscious moments need to be savored and relished!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="249">I was always so blind, looking for love... &lt;i&gt;Hnng&lt;/i&gt;, If only I had realised sooner that I am my own biggest lover.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; you all desire me. And I understand, I &lt;i&gt;crave&lt;/i&gt; myself too.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Do you have any idea how &lt;i&gt;hard&lt;/i&gt; it is being a princess? No, of course you don't. Just understand that I &lt;i&gt;deserve&lt;/i&gt; this!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">There is no shame in a princess loving herself so &lt;i&gt;intensely&lt;/i&gt;! </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">​What was I even thinking, as if a clone could &lt;i&gt;ever&lt;/i&gt; make me feel &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; good.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Losing myself to my own pleasure... I could just drown in it forever and ever...</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">No-one is more perfect than me! &lt;i&gt;No-one!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">​Those... dumb sea-witches... They understood &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; about me. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Having the perfect body makes all of this feel so much better.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="273">​Am I not a work of art, ~Player~? Don't answer that, I already know it's true~</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">It's a miracle that I could manage not to touch myself with how drop dead gorgeous I am.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There is no shame in worshipping someone who is better than you~</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Even the statues and paintings in my castle are &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; compared to my ever-lasting beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hng... not even that stupid &lt;i&gt;Perfectheart&lt;/i&gt; is as perfect as me!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Having this pillow made was easily my best idea ever~</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="277">It's unfair! Why do all of you get to look at someone as perfect as me, but all &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; get to look at is a bunch of peasants!?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">For once, I don't think I mind the fact that I lost... even if you all cheated. Ohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Even those paintings that I have... Even those don't properly portray how desirable I am!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Who needs a prince charming? When I myself am already princess charming~</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It just feels so much better when I can look at myself.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy.png">Perfect... ah... I'm... perfect.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy4.png">Everyone here... they could only wish they were me!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I'm... The best!... The hottest! The most immaculate princess of them all!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">None of those clones... None of them could even come close to how &lt;i&gt;perfect&lt;/i&gt; I am!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">...I... want more...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy.png">Hah... I want this pleasure to last forever...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy4.png">Thousands of fans... screaming my name... desiring &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy4.png">No-one... no-one at all compares... I am the most lovely princess of them all!...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">Aah... Aaah~ The perfect spot~</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Only &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; could make myself feel sooooo good~</state>
                <state img="#-heavy.png">Hnngh... I don't want this to ever end...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finish.png">AH! YES! YES!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">I LOVE YOU, SWEETHEART!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-after_finish.png">Aaah... Hah... I really am the best~</state>
                <state img="#-after_finish.png">That... Felt... &lt;i&gt;Perfect.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Ugh. I'm all sticky. I could really use a spa right now.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Those sprout moles better have cleaned all my statues as I ordered. They know what will happened if they don't do it.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">How long are you peasants going to make me wait? I have plenty more things to do after this game, like spoiling myself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I should make my own rules for strip poker... ones that make it so that royalty can't ever lose.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Why does &lt;i&gt;he&lt;/i&gt; come up in my mind right now?</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="126">My garden needs to be taken care of daily, but those stupid sprout moles always complain about not being tall enough to do the hedges. Well, that's not &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; problem now, is it?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="127">I wonder if castella is done throwing out that worthless statue of my ex.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">This might be the rarest sight of them all, every single one of you has to count yourself lucky to be able to see me bask in my afterglow. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">The real show is already over, all that remains are the leftovers.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Nothing else compares to the show I gave, so waiting till the others are done is quite uneventful.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It is because I am such a humble princess that I will wait until the &lt;i&gt;trash&lt;/i&gt; is done. </state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">With the main show already over, why don't you peasants wrap this up so I can go home?</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Of course, if any of you dare start spreading rumors that the great Sweetheart attended a strip poker match, there won't be anything left of you once I'm done with you.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Is there even a reason to keep going now that I'm done? Ohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmph, having to wait is frustrating. But at least I get to mock your inferior genes while doing so.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">​I wonder if my servants are done expanding my castle. I gave them eight hours for them, four more than I usually do, so it had better be done!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder what happened to the ever approaching dark clouds... At some point, they just vanished. Which is good because it was going to ruin my view.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="13" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="125">What a horrible establishment! They don't even offer you a towel once you're out of the game!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">There was never a doubt that I would win. Just another victory for the perfect princess!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-upset.png">I will have my revenge! A princess never loses!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
