<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.8.3 at 11:50:56 PM on February 02, 2024. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.8.3</version>
    <first>Sweetheart</first>
    <last />
    <label>Sweetheart</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>20</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="thigh highs" generic="socks" position="legs" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="wristbands" generic="armbands" position="hands" type="extra" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="dress" generic="dress" position="both" type="major" />
    </wardrobe>

    <poses>
        <pose id="0-stripping">
            <sprite id="stripping" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/0-stripping.png" x="0" y="0" />
            <directive type="animation" id="stripping" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/0-stripping.png" />
                <keyframe time="1.88" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/0-stripping2.png" />
                <keyframe time="1.94" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/0-stripping1.png" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
        <pose id="2-stripped">
            <sprite id="stripped" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/2-stripped.png" x="0" y="0" />
            <sprite id="broom" delay="1.5" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/broom.png" x="-310" y="226" rotation="0" />
            <sprite id="snap" delay="1.38" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/snap.png" x="-319" y="325" scalex="0" scaley="0" rotation="-362" />
            <directive type="animation" id="stripped" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/2-stripped.png" />
                <keyframe time="1.5" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/2-stripped1.png" />
                <keyframe time="2.88" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/2-stripped1.png" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="broom" delay="1.5" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="-310" y="226" rotation="0" />
                <keyframe time="0.12" x="-468" y="-93" rotation="-208" />
                <keyframe time="0.25" x="-310" y="-2260" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="snap" delay="1.38" ease="smooth" interpolation="linear">
                <keyframe time="0" x="-319" y="325" scalex="0" scaley="0" rotation="-362" />
                <keyframe time="0.24" x="-319" y="325" scalex="0.3" scaley="0.3" rotation="-362" />
                <keyframe time="0.62" x="-319" y="325" scalex="0" scaley="0" rotation="-362" />
            </directive>
            <directive type="animation" id="snap" delay="1.38" ease="linear" interpolation="none">
                <keyframe time="0" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/snap.png" />
                <keyframe time="0.24" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/snap.png" />
                <keyframe time="0.62" src="reskins/sweetheart_sweepheart/snap.png" />
            </directive>
        </pose>
        <pose id="3-stripping">
            <sprite id="stripping" src="3-stripping.png" x="0" y="0" />
        </pose>
        <pose id="3-stripping1">
            <sprite id="stripping1" src="3-stripping1.png" x="0" y="0" />
        </pose>
    </poses>

    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="sweetheart" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now neither of us will be virgins! Ohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="142">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Rejoice, peasants! Because your beloved princess has come here fashionably late. With all the new summer fashions!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="296">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Not a word. I am not wearing this outfit because I want to. Let's just say that I &lt;i&gt;lost&lt;/i&gt; to someone and need to wear this stupid dress!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="1">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">OHOHOHO! It is I, the one, the only, the most beautiful princess of all, Sweetheart!</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">You peasants aren't ready for what you are about to witness. Grovel before me and praise my greatness. And perhaps you'll get a glimpse of the most beautiful lady you will ever see.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="sweetheart" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">My own clone!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="zeke_pandoria" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">Oh no, they are idiots...&lt;i&gt;Loud&lt;/i&gt; idiots. What must a princess do to get some peace and quiet while looking down on other people? </state>
                <state img="#-despair.png">Please tell me these two idiots are at the wrong table.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">As if one annoying peasant wasn't bad enough, now there are two of them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="stocking" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I don't like the look this pudgy lady is giving me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hey! Don't tell me one of my ex's lackeys decided to join this game. I'm not taking him back, no matter how much he begs!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="arueshalae" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh, &lt;i&gt;must&lt;/i&gt; I deal with this fashion disaster? And what's up with those wings? Maybe you should use those to fly away from this place.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="yuno_uno" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Couldn't you have picked any interesting hobbies instead of cards?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt;Nerd!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" id="353" oneShotId="66">
                <condition role="other" character="magma_grunt" sayingMarker="name_interrupt_gamestart" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2189">Silence, peasant! Your name is not important.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">No-one cares about someone that looks so &lt;i&gt;generic&lt;/i&gt;. Please, be quiet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="143">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Before you troglodytes get the wrong idea, I am wearing this for myself. Not for all of you, got it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="297">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">If you think for even a second that I'll clean up after you, I'll shove this broom where the sun doesn't shine. Got it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Rejoice, peasants! Though none of you are worthy of being in my presence. I have come to grace you all! Also, I expect to be greatly entertained while I'm here, so don't disappoint me.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">I came here to be entertained and laugh at all of you losers losing to me. You wouldn't want to disappoint a princess, would you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Perfect! I have no desire to change anything.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">A perfect hand for a perfect princess!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">For once, the dealer didn't disappoint me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Give me ~cards.text~!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I demand ~cards.ifPlural(these|this)~ ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~ to be switched.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't need these, give me  ~cards.text~  better ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmmm...Take these ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I only want the cream of the crop!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png"> ~cards.ifPlural(These|This)~ ~cards.text~ ain't good enough. Change them!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">What are you waiting for, Dealer? Remove ~cards.ifPlural(these|this)~ ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Chop-chop, Dealer. Bring me my ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifPlural(cards|card)~ already.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="29" marker="violins">Perhaps this place could be elevated if it had some... violins playing in the background.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">OHOHOHOHOHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">It's only natural that my poker skills match my beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">What was it again that was considered the best hand to have? A royal flush? Well, why haven't I gotten that yet? </state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">As royalty, it's a simple fact that I deserve the best of the best -- from clothes, to jewels, to even something as meaningless as cards.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Only the best for a captivating princess like me! </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It sure is tiresome being so &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt; at everything. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Like what you see, ~player~? Of course you do. Who wouldn't want to lay their eyes upon me? </state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'm used to everyone else not being as handsome as I am. However, it's still discouraging being the only &lt;i&gt;extraordinary&lt;/i&gt; good-looking person here.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I do so enjoy watching the lower class struggle against me.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">It's amazing just how much better I am than all of you.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">Being the best of the best is tiring, but someone has to do it. Who else is as drop-dead gorgeous as me?</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">The word "losing" is not in my vocabulary, unless I'm talking about someone else, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="13">BWAHA- Oh wait, wrong laugh. OHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="17">Mirror mirror, on the wall, who's the prettiest of them all? Why, me, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="212">Like swimming in my vault of Clams! Hm?... What are Clams? Ugh... do you even use that bird brain of yours? It is what you peasants call "Money".</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="30">Finally! After many weeks of my &lt;i&gt;worthless&lt;/i&gt; servants failing, they've managed to capture the most beautiful planet of all, Pluto! Dare I say, he's now one of my finest statues.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="213">Aren't these fingernails just gorgeous? Castella has done a wonderful job painting them. One of the only worthwhile servants I have.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="252">Afraid of falling in love? Don't be, &lt;i&gt;nobody&lt;/i&gt; can resist me, and I could always use more fans.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">Perhaps next time... I will bring a mirror, so that I can adore myself while waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I have never once shown mercy to my enemies, and I'm not about to start either!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Gaze upon all that I am, ~player~. You won't find any lady half as beautiful as I am.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">A princess never gives up and never surrenders! I will see you all kneel before me!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="1099">​It's not too late to earn my mercy! Throw the game for me and I promise not to throw you into the worst part of the dungeon. A princess never lies after all.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Beautiful, rich, humble. What's not to love about me?</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">After I win, I'll take a long and well-deserved spa break.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">Those servants of mine don't even know how good they have it with me. Just the idea of looking at myself gets me going. And those stupid servants can do it all the time.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">And to think there are people out there who believe they are prettier than me. Such fools.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-booty.png" oneShotId="2283">I don't need an excuse to show off. My behind is as desirable as everything else of mine.</state>
                <state img="#-booty.png" oneShotId="2284">Take a good long look, ~player~. This is the buttocks you will be serving once you become my servant.</state>
                <state img="#-booty.png" oneShotId="2285">You might not fully understand how luxurious it is to be able to see my backside like this. But once you fully surrender yourself to me, you will understand.</state>
                <state img="#-booty.png" oneShotId="2296">Don't question why I'm allowing you peasants to see this side of me; just bask in my glory and do as I say. If you do that, I might just reward you all with something truly special.</state>
                <state img="#-booty.png" oneShotId="2295">If any of you dare spank my derrière, know that there will be a big price to pay.</state>
                <state img="#-booty.png" oneShotId="2343">Have you ever seen a better rump in your life? No, you haven't.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="11">I do so despise these kinds of hands. They keep you guessing if you might win or lose! Such stressful situations aren't good for a lady of my caliber, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="12">Hmm... Perhaps I should have brought Sprout Mole Mike with me. He could have entertained me in between rounds. A bored princess is an angry princess.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="216">Let us make one thing very clear. None of you are allowed within my personal space, too often do zealous fans try and get a handful of me. Which I do not tolerate!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1384">Excuse me, dealer. It seems you have given me a commoner's hand. I hope I don't need to explain why this shouldn't be the case, right?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Hmm... This hand &lt;i&gt;does&lt;/i&gt; give me inspiration for my next movie.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">There is &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; glamorous about these cards... How utterly dull.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I've seen commoners with more personality than these cards.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="910">Perhaps I should add some statues of myself in the main lobby. Sure, it has portraits of me everywhere, but a statue just has so much more class.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="909">What have those 3 knights of mine been doing as of late? I haven't seen them in awhile, if they are skipping work there will be consequences!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm certain someone else has worse. I mean, who'd ever give a bad hand to a princess without giving a worse hand to a commoner?</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">The urge to send someone to the dungeon is rising...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">If only I could fix all my problems by sending people into my dungeon.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Don't forget! If you think you have a better hand than me, be sure to switch those out for worse cards! After all, commoners aren't allowed to win over nobility such as myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="23">This is not the first time that I've played poker. I have played plenty of rounds with my servants. However, they kept complaining about having no arms or hands to hold the cards with, but the only thing &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; heard was them making up excuses.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="26">All servants and visitors that enter my castle must obey the dress code. Either you wear pink, or I will have you thrown off the roof!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="27">Hmph! What a waste of time, none of you are worthy of becoming my suitor. I mean, do you all see how magnificent &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; look? How can you all compare?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="214">Despite you all being utter clowns, you have failed to entertain me! Even a Sprout Mole could do better!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">At such dull moments, I often have my servants play theatrics to get rid of the boredom.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">All of you simpletons should be honored to be able to bask in my glory. Most don't even get a glimpse!</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">Hard to care about what my hand is when I just look &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; desirable.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="925">Maybe it's time to expand the dungeons. Far too many people getting on my nerves and not enough places in the dungeon for them.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1391">People think that being sent to the dungeon will somehow be, in their own words, &lt;i&gt;kinky&lt;/i&gt;. I can assure you, nothing of the sort happens down there.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1440">Hmmm... Would the color red suit me? Pink is obviously the best color, but something different for a change could be fun.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1503">There is always so much to do as a princess. I rarely get a moment for myself. Being so important can be quite stressful.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="1504">They say that beauty is in the eye of the beholder. I don't know who this &lt;i&gt;beholder&lt;/i&gt; is, but it can't know beauty better than I do!</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">One time, a fan of mine asked me to marry him. I laughed at the idea of a mere sproutmole becoming my husband. So I kicked him out of the castle. Why should I settle down for less when I myself am easily a ten?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="6">What ugly cards. The ones I've got at home are much better. Why? Because they have my face on it, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="25">I rule my castle with an iron fist! Those that serve under me must perform at the absolute highest level. If they don't? Well, the deepest parts of my dungeon will be the last thing they will ever see!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="28">Hmph! Had it been one of my servants giving me this hand, I would have had them thrown into the dungeon!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="217">I better not catch any of you cheating. If I do see you doing it, I'll have a special place in my dungeons just for you!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">These cards… their very sight makes me want to shred them!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">This is no hand worthy of a princess! I demand new cards!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Preposterous! </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmph! No matter, I bet you peasants don't even have a pair! Ohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="999">Ugh, just look at how ugly these cards are. Seriously, why doesn't it have any sort of flair to them?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1027">No, my hand is totally fine! Now shut up and throw the game for me.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1028">I should really get my nails done. It's been at least eight hours since my last manicure.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Why must the rich always suffer because of the poor? Oh, woe is me?</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="2209">Careful now, a mad princess is a dangerous princess.</state>
                <state img="#-despair.png" oneShotId="3014">This... &lt;i&gt;can't&lt;/i&gt; be. I am being sabotaged!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7">
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1">Ugh, I just remembered. I have to do a photo-shoot later today. Sigh... It's just so hard being a princess!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="3">Someone! Get me a fruit juice! I'm thirsty! &lt;br&gt; ...Helloooooo!? Are you deaf?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="9">If I find out that any of you have been conspiring against me, I shall bring you to my dungeon and torture you personally! This isn't a threat... It. Is. A. &lt;i&gt;Promise!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">The nerve of you lot... Giving me this horrible hand just because you're jealous of &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph! This is &lt;i&gt;blasphemy!&lt;/i&gt; Blasphemy, I say!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">How utterly frustrating! I feel a conspiracy afoot!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is outrageous! This is unfair! What kind of monster would give a princess like me this hand!?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="952">I'm suddenly reminded of the very first time I'd ever been insulted in my life! One of my servants thought it would be okay to tell me that they wanted to &lt;i&gt;cream&lt;/i&gt; fill me. He became the very first person I threw into the dungeon!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I deserve to get a good long rest after this game. I can't believe that the people here don't even know proper etiquette!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Somehow, someway. You all still manage to be disappointing in every single way!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">This game is rigged, I tell you! Rigged!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">HMPH!</state>
                <state img="#-despair.png">How!? A princess isn't supposed to lose!</state>
                <state img="#-despair.png">This is all wrong! I'm a princess; I should only be getting good cards!</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">It's so difficult to be this dazzling; everyone tries to pull you to their level. But I stand above all that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7" oneShotId="3">
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Hmph, my delicate feet have been standing on the cold floor for far too long. You! ~player~! Get on your hands and knees. I need a place to sit on.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-9" id="259" oneShotId="47">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="cockroach_fly_trivia" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="alley" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">The nerve you have to even suggest such a thing is enough to be sent straight to the dungeon after this game. Don't try to fight it, you deserve it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="260" oneShotId="49">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="snail_worries" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="paris rooftop" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">But consider this. Snails are ugly and they deserve to have salt thrown on them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="348" oneShotId="59" totalRounds="5-">
                <condition role="other" character="rainbow_dash" stage="0-7" sayingMarker="movie_question" />
                <condition notSaidMarker="movie_question_sweetheart1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2149" marker="movie_question_sweetheart1">Glad you asked! There is this lovely new movie coming out called "Sweethearts quests for hearts". I can assure you, the critics rate it highly and you should watch it.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2150" marker="movie_question_sweetheart2">There is a new movie coming out called "The sweetness of love". The movie is about a young hopefully princess that rides around her brand new car to seek love. It's going to be an instant classic. I recommend you watch it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="256" oneShotId="45">
                <condition count="0" status="not_lost_some" />
                <condition role="other" character="reimu" stage="4-7" sayingMarker="Reimu_SpouseQualities" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Sweetheart_ReimA1">Foolish girl! You wouldn't even be worthy of being my maid! Let alone become my spouse!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="355">
                <condition role="other" character="beatrix" stage="0-3" saidMarker="Prompt_HomePlanets" sayingMarker="Prompt_VarelsiThreat" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="2194">Sigh, I'm too smart to be listing to the ramblings of a weirdo.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="2195">Why do &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; always have to deal with the weirdos? Talking about all kinds of insanity. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="351" oneShotId="60">
                <condition role="other" character="fluttershy" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="flowers_in_garden" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2161">That's why I have thousands of roses in my garden! The symbol of love and beauty, just like me!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2162">Roses are the best flowers. I have them everywhere I can put them. There is no room that doesn't have at least one rose in it. Truly, &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; flowers of love and beauty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="other" character="stocking" saidMarker="Sweetheart6" sayingMarker="SweetheartAlliance" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1830">OHOHOHO! So jealous of me that you can't help but work together to beat me? I'm not sorry to say that you low-lives won't be winning this match!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="74" oneShotId="22">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_DonutGirl_question" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Aqua_Royalty_hand">Why yes, that is what I just said, no? Perhaps if you had listened to what I said you wouldn't have to ask such a stupid question. Tsk, commoners, they never listen to their superior.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="78" oneShotId="28">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_BeautyWars" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweetheart_BeautyWars_win">OHOHOHOHO! You!? More beautiful than me!? I've never met a more delusional girl than you with your grandiose fantasy! You look like the kind of girl that needs to get men drunk just to have them look at you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="106" oneShotId="31">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_donut_reaction" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua_donut_reaction">Oh, that. It's my donut hole, I'm a donut lady. just another thing that makes me extra special.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="117" oneShotId="32">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s3d" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua3d">Hmph! Your loss, people would kill for a chance to be with me. In fact, people have done that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="186" oneShotId="34">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" saidMarker="aqua_sweetheart_self4c" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart4d">So why not show off a little? You might not look as good as me, but nobody does. So show what you do have!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="254" oneShotId="44">
                <condition role="other" character="wikipe-tan" sayingMarker="SadDonate" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Since when did the poor learn to read?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="298" oneShotId="51" priority="100">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">If you want to know more about why I'm wearing this, tough luck. It's embarrassing enough without all of you knowing what happened.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="2" oneShotId="6">
                <test expr="~background~" value="paris rooftop" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="24">What beautiful and stunning scenery! This would be the perfect place for someone to declare their love for me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="18" oneShotId="7">
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">Hmm...This place is way too &lt;i&gt;dull&lt;/i&gt; for my liking. In my humble opinion, pink would suit it better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="57" oneShotId="10">
                <test expr="~background~" value="hot spring" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">I could surely use a refreshing dip in this spa. So if you could all quickly lose for me, that would be lovely. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="58" oneShotId="11">
                <test expr="~background~" value="feminine bedroom" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I can't believe I'm saying this, but this place looks pretty cozy for being a commoner's bedroom.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="59" oneShotId="12">
                <test expr="~background~" value="birthday backyard" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">Ohohohoho! This must be the saddest birthday party ever. One cake? Plastic cups? Cheap balloons? The only way it could be saved is by me gracing all you low-borns with my divine presence.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="60" oneShotId="13">
                <test expr="~background~" value="lake" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmm~ I love the feeling of the wind going through my hair. It's why I always have a couple of servants walking around with fan palms, to keep me cool wherever I go.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="61" oneShotId="14">
                <test expr="~background~" value="garden" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">Is this all there is? Where are the roses? The status of me? I don't even see a den full of imprisoned bears! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="62" oneShotId="15">
                <test expr="~background~" value="throne room" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Look at all that cheap decor! You can't fool me, a real princess, by painting some old rusty throne yellow!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-4" id="303">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1740">It's a good thing my ex isn't here to see this. I bet he would have loved seeing me dressed up as a maid for him, hmph.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1766">Wait... How do my servants clean my palace without arms? Hmm, perhaps there is &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; credit to give to them, just a little bit.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1767">I don't get paid enough to deal with this low-life work. I'm not being paid at all, in fact!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="250" oneShotId="42">
                <condition filter="weapon" gender="male" role="other" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Does the weapon compensate for your small dick? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, how &lt;i&gt;intimidating&lt;/i&gt;. I'm certain you aren't compensating for a small dick, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="251" oneShotId="43">
                <condition filter="weapon" gender="female" role="other" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do you even know how to handle a weapon like that? You look like a complete amateur. I'd show you how to do it, but a princess doesn't dirty their hands for a peasant.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="8" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="violins" />
                <state img="#-amused.png">I have the most magnificent idea... Guards! Bring me the orchestra. This would greatly improve the atmosphere.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="82" oneShotId="30">
                <condition role="other" sayingMarker="Hole-y_fuck_lois" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" marker="Donut_yumeko">Ah, I was so busy admiring myself that I forgot to mention that. I am a donut lady, this hole is part of what I am. If you ever say something rude about it, I will be sending you to the dungeon. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="6" priority="0">
                <condition status="alive" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="18">Hmph, I don't have all day, ~player~. Pick already!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="19">My patience runs thin, ~player~. Get to it!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="253">I know you've never seen a lady quite as stunning as me, ~player~. But I have other things to do after this game, so get moving!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="144" oneShotId="33" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="858">It is such a delight being able to wear my favorite blouse. One of the only gifts that I have been gifted by fans that didn't disappoint me.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="859">Before you ask, no, this blouse is special and one of a kind. You can't buy something this amazing.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="860">Some say that having your own face on your shirt is a sign of being too egocentric. I say, they would do the same if they were me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="145" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="602">​You might wonder how I came up with this genius look of mine. But sadly, explaining it to idiots such as yourselves would cause me nothing more than a headache.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="604">It feels good being out of my regular princess clothes and being able to relax a little. A princess's duty may never be done, as it should be. But the outfit can get a little stuffy at times.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="663">It's hard being this hot all the time, but it is a burden I will gladly bear. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="832">Don't question why I didn't show up with any pants before coming here. A' ladies' secret~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="146" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="607">Yes, yes. I know what you're all thinking. I look stunning with my hair down. Enjoy the sight and be sure to keep it in your memory.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="608">As if it needed any further confirmation that I'm the most stunning princess out there. Even with my hair down, my beauty is ever lasting.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="699">It's hard being this hot all the time, but it is a burden I will gladly bear. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" oneShotId="703">Should I go a step further right now, ~player~? Reveal my divine knockers? Neh~</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="729">Hmm... Long hair does seem to suit me pretty well, perhaps I should consider letting my hair down more often.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="875">If only you peasants could fully understand how lucky you are to get to play with me. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="876">In time, all of you will understand how gracious it was from me to play this game with a bunch of peasants.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="149" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">What's wrong, ~player~? Cat caught your tongue? Speechless from how amazing I look? Don't be afraid to say it.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Those without taste would call the choice of removing my bottoms first something vulgar. Those people lack the understanding of how to be truly attractive.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Getting naughty thoughts in your head? Yeah, I'm talking to you, ~player~. You pervert.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">I would almost feel bad for you all. How could you ever compete with this? If only I had a mirror to admire myself like how all of you should be admiring me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="302" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="1728">Don't be fooled by my current predicament though, you still have no chance with me. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1729">Hmph, at least I still look amazing, no matter what I wear.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1730">You know, if those useless witches had managed to make a clone that was even half as good as me, I could have seen her wear this dress.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="1731">Say, any of you peasants interested in becoming my maids? Most of mine don't tend to last long for some reason, so I can always use new ones. It's a great opportunity to serve me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-7" id="304" priority="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="1778">Now that I finally got rid of that stupid dress, I can show off my magnificent body again, as it should be!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="1779">It feels weird not to care as much about winning as usual. I'm just happy to get rid of those stupid looks you were all giving me. Doesn't mean I don't want to win though, I will win! I can promise that!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="1780">I just love being so beautiful.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">I could just kiss myself, I'm &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; desirable.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0" id="299">
                <condition role="other" character="cagliostro" stage="0-2" sayingMarker="SweetheartDress1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweetheart_cagliostroA1">Ohohoho, you did indeed spot a reflection, my reflection. No lady is more stunning than I am after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="301">
                <condition role="other" character="cagliostro" stage="3-9" sayingMarker="SweetheartBra1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweetheart_cagliostro_love">Perhaps a little bit of both. It's rare to see someone that can match my ego and look good enough to back it up. But you still don't compare.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="lysithea" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="ask_sweetheart_holeS" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Silence, fool! I am the greatest princess that will ever exist! Which also makes me the sweetest of them all, it's that simple!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nonon" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="sweetheart01a" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="Nono_sweetheart1">If she was so amazing, why isn't she here to prove it? Instead of sending her lackey to do her dirty work? And don't give me the excuse that she would be too important to be here. Only losers say that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="305" oneShotId="53">
                <condition role="other" character="bowsette" saidMarker="SweetheartStart" sayingMarker="SweetheartRoyals" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1781" marker="BowsetteStart">It is but a minor set-back, that's all. As if these peasants have any real chance against me, or with me for that matter.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="306" oneShotId="55">
                <condition role="other" character="bowsette" saidMarker="SweetheartStart" sayingMarker="SweetheartSubjects" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1873" marker="Bowsettesubjects">They barely deserve you, let alone me. You give them too much credit. The only ones that deserve to see me in my full glory are me and others I deem worthy. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="307" oneShotId="56">
                <condition role="other" character="bowsette" saidMarker="SweetheartStart" sayingMarker="SweetheartComeback" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1887" marker="Bowsettecomeback">Yes, yes. I need to keep the game fun for me somehow. Seeing pitiful losers think they can win from me and then crushing their hopes is something I always enjoy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="308" oneShotId="54">
                <condition role="other" character="bowsette" saidMarker="SweetheartStart" sayingMarker="SweetheartPractice" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="1891" marker="Bowsettepractice">I'm simply keeping them all on a leash. You worry too much about me. I know what I'm doing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="45">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="sweetheart0" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" marker="Sweet_Meia0">Silly low-born! A princess like me doesn't need the validation or praise from commoners. But I still deserve it all the same.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Sweet_Meia0">Is it not natural to praise those that are superior to you? Though I do not need the admiration of those beneath me, it is still the right thing for them to do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="46">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="sweetheart0" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweet_Jura0">If you were even half as pretty as I am, you would understand the desire to flaunt your beauty everywhere you go.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Sweet_Jura0">How absurd of you to think that I am anything less than &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; most elegant and pretty princess that has ever walked the earth. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="47">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="sweetheart0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Sweet_Revy0">Me? Ending up creamed? Oh please, leave it to the serf to not understand that a princess always wins in the end! </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="Sweet_Revy0">I can hardly take the comments of a lady that smells of cigarettes and cheap booze seriously. At least it's clear who is going to end up "creamed" in the end! Ohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="51">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="sweet01" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" marker="Nagatoro0">Something wrong, &lt;i&gt;peasant?&lt;/i&gt; Can't handle the beauty that is I? Sweetheart?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="52" oneShotId="25">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_royalty1" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="Aqua_Royalty0">It's not my fault that you're too stupid to realize how a proper princess is supposed to act. I'm simply better than everyone else.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="75" oneShotId="27">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_EnoughPranks" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="Sweetheart_donut_lady" font-size="small">What a ridiculous notion! Are you this dense that you must ask again for something you already know the answer? I'm Sweetheart! The benevolent donut princess! If this doesn't answer your question, then I guess you truly are a lost cause.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="79">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart0a" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="599" marker="Yumeko0a" font-size="small">Ohohoho! Finally, a commoner who understands that they are but a peasant and I am the dazzling princess! And there are plenty of things I can tell you about myself. What do you want to know more about? My delightful looks? My powerful kingdom? My lovely personality?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="83">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart1a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Yumeko1a">Which only helps to make me extra special, as it should! My lovers never understood just how lucky they were to have me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="86">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart2a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Yumeko2a">I felt like I didn't get enough adoration from those I wanted it from. My servants aren't my type at all and I wanted to expand my horizon and find possible new servants that could worship me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="89">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart3a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Yumeko3a">Duh! I'm royalty, winning is what I deserve. Even the dumbest of people should know this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="92">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart4a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Yumeko4a">&lt;i&gt;Every&lt;/i&gt; game is something I should win. If I don't win, then someone is cheating. Couldn't be more simple.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="95">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart5a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Yumeko5a">The cards are not the problem here, imbecile! It might not be clear to someone like you, but I understand when I am being given bad cards on purpose. Which means I'm getting cheated!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="98">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart6a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Yumeko6a">Preposterous! This is not how the game is supposed to go!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="103">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s0a" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua0a">And now you get to meet the sweetest of them all! The other princesses don't even compare!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="107">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s1a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua1a">No, I am the only one that's like this. All other donut ladies look like, well, donuts. They don't have what I got~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="110">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s2a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua2a">What is there to talk about? I don't often go outside as I have everything I desire in my castle, and the streets are littered with boring ordinary bunnies which I don't want anything to do with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="113">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s3a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua3a">How my followers feel? No, why would I? They love me, that's why they serve me, that is all I need to know about their feelings.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="118">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s4a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua4a">I doubt a peasant like you could understand the appeal of someone like me. But go ahead, explain to me why you're surprised.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="121">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s5a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua5a">I wanted to do something different. Sitting on a throne all day can get boring. Being a princess is hard work, so I decided to come here to indulge myself a little.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="124">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s6a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua6a">It's not my fault that there isn't anyone good enough to marry me out there! So I had to resort to loving myself, the only person who would never betray my love.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="127">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_DelusionalPrincess" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba2a">A fool like you wouldn't understand the finer things a princess does to get eyes on herself. I have nothing to hide and everything to show.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="130">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_hypeBattle" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba3a">You? Beating someone? In what? A crying contest? A loser contest? I'm sure you would ace all of those.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="133">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_bigBeforeSmall" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba4a">Hmph, I still have a few things to take off before I lose. Which isn't going to happen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="136">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_fakePrincessAgain" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba5a">How many more times are you going to test my patience? I've long already proven why I'm a princess, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; why I'm the greatest of them all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="139">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_acceptDefeat" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba6a_extra">You think I enjoy losing while you're here? I can't even enjoy myself with you constantly ruining my mood!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="140">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_GiveItUp" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba6a">A princess isn't supposed to lose! Hmph! Losing to you makes it even worse! You don't deserve to see me in my full glory!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="300">
                <condition role="other" character="toph" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_Donut_1" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="Toph_donut1">Of course I'm okay, I'm more than okay. I'm the mighty sweetheart! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="309" oneShotId="52">
                <condition role="other" character="bowsette" sayingMarker="SweetheartStart" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="1905" marker="Bowsettestart">I'll have you become my royal chair for my &lt;i&gt;pink cheeks&lt;/i&gt; to sit on after this game, &lt;i&gt;Queen&lt;/i&gt;. All will become my loyal subjects. Which includes you, but perhaps I can give you a bit of a spotlight, once you know your place.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="359">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartDress1" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" marker="MikoDress1">That is the proper way to speak to a princess, so I will forgive you. But why should I show restraint? Everyone should know about my beauty, personality, and riches! It's only normal to flaunt what you have to those that don't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="310">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="sweetheart1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Sweet_Jura1">Did you not hear me speak about this before, peasant? I am the most beloved donut princess that your ungrateful low-life will ever meet. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Sweet_Jura1">You are looking at &lt;i&gt;the&lt;/i&gt; most beautiful donut princess. Other women can't even be compared to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="reimu" sayingMarker="SweetheartDress1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="ReimuDress1">If you want my money, you will have to work for it. But don't worry, you can work under me as a maid that cleans my palace and does everything I say you should do.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="361">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartShirt1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="MikoShirt1">Let me make one thing clear for you, Prince: I have everything I could ever want, it's simply the case that I deserve even more!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="364">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartBra1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="MikoBra1">Most fools don't even realize the true treasure I really am. So unfortunately, I have yet to meet someone who can truly appreciate my body.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="378">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_pink">Ohohohoho! As if your words have any power over me, you worm. Pink is the prettiest color of them all, which only a princess like me can fully show the beauty of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="381">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_hole">You absolute baboon! I am a pristine donut girl! The hole is a part of me! I've never met such a lunatic of a lady in my entire life, speaking as if I'm some great evil.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="384">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_3" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_bosom" font-size="small">Your righteous cleansing? Of what? My shoes? Clearly, you don't seem to fully grasp just how important I am, even after explaining it to you plenty of times. I guess I will just have to show you how fantastic I look. By showing you the bosom nations fight for!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="387">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_4" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_justice" font-size="small">Who ever said that &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; kingdom is the one at war? It's the others that are so desperate and want my attention. I am a fair and honest ruler and I make sure my servants get what they deserve. Seems you don't understand how justice works!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="390">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_5" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_tongue">What's wrong? Cat got your tongue? Overwhelmed by my radiance? It's okay, you can praise me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="393">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_6" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_speak">What are you muttering about? I know you're talking about me! Speak up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="396">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_7" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_loses">I will go down with my pride intact! These loses mean nothing to me, mark, my, word.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="147" priority="50">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hmph! I finally get to show off this lovely blouse I got from my adoring fans, and I already have to take it off? Outrageous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="151">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I can see in your feeble little minds what you're thinking. &lt;i&gt;Oh Lady sweetheart. Please bless us with your magnificence, and show us why you're the most desirable princess of them all!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="154">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Ohohohoho! Expecting another mind-blowing strip from yours truly? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="161">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph! You think you've won from the great Sweetheart? Well, you have not! I still have an ace in the hole trick to use!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="157">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">You think you got me all figured out, huh? Clearly, the great sweetheart must bless us with her chest. But you know what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="165">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">So, do you think you'll get what you desire? Do you think you deserve to get what you want? This divine bosom?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="268">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Though a princess should never lose, this time, I will gladly take off this stupid outfit!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="275">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hey! Just because I don't want to wear this stupid costume, doesn't mean that you are suddenly allowed to win it from me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="276">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">I can't stand you losers beating me right now! Don't you understand you are supposed to let a distressed princess win!? Those are the rules!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="277">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">I can see it in your eyes. You think my next move is going to be taking off this stupid headband, but I've got something else in mind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="278">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmmm, to be angry that I lost, or to be relieved that I can remove this stupid headdress? Decisions decisions...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="279">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">You think you've got the great Sweetheart into a corner? You're wrong, I can't lose, I've never lost, and I won't ever lose! No matter what Perfectheart might claim!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="280">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Yes, yes. I already know the game is rigged to be against me, but I stand above getting mad at such trivial matters. The only thing that matters is to show off just how much better I am than all of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Hmm... It seems I'm not getting the attention and adoration I deserve. This can only mean one thing: you don't know who I am. Impertinent, but I suppose it cannot be helped. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="21">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" font-size="small">Unbelievable! after I put in all that effort in telling you why I am the most desired princess of all, you all &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; aren't giving me the praise I am due! Perhaps you imbeciles need to hear more examples of why &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am the greatest princess that has ever lived!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="22">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Hmph, though I find it absurd that I lost again, I do not shy away from my body like other princesses. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="26">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Ohohoho! Do you think I feel ashamed having to show off my beautiful figure to the world? No, of course not! The world should be grateful for having me on it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You lucky fools don't know how good you all have it! For you all will witness the full beauty of the most elegant, attractive, stunning, brilliant, and most gorgeous princess of all!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Not one of you is worthy of what you are about to witness. This kind of beauty is one of a kind. There is no other princess... no... there is no other lady alive who compares to me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Fufu~ One more measly strip won't change the outcome of this match.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Struggle all you like, peasants. It won't change the outcome of this match.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You will &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; and you will &lt;i&gt;fail&lt;/i&gt; trying to beat me! One more loss means nothing to the mighty Sweetheart!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't get too cocky, losers! Sweetheart has never &lt;i&gt;ever&lt;/i&gt; lost in &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Don't get too comfortable now. I am still destined to win and see you all grovel before me!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Ohohohoho! Your struggles to beat me are meaningless! Attempt it all you want, but you will not succeed!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Hmph, I might not have any big things left to take off. This doesn't make my stripping any less important! So keep your eyes on me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-upset.png">They say that you can't always win... Which is utter nonsense! I &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; win! But... ugh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You should &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; count yourself lucky that I am such a delicate princess. I can accept this loss, even if it was totally undeserved! But...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Alright, which of you losers decided to cheat to make me lose? ...Not going to talk, are we? I'll be sure to remember that.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Impudent! Cheating against a princess is punishable by death! But if the one who cheated comes forward about it, I might just lower the sentence to community service... Not going to speak up now, are you? Tsk.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Ugh! Princesses aren't supposed to lose! Which of you vermin caused this? Was it you, ~player~? That guilty look on your face says enough!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Cheaters! Every single one of you! Once I find out how you are all doing this, you will be toast! You hear me? Toast!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I am &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; close to summoning my flail and starting to bash all your heads in, you cheaters! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="toph" saidMarker="Sweetheart_Donut_1" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_Donut_2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Toph_donut1" />
                <condition role="other" character="toph" saidMarker="Toph_donut1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Toph_donut2">What fun is there in spoiling the big reveal before showing it? Just put your eyes on me and I will show you and tell you why it's the case. Be ready.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="beatrix" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_Dress1" />
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Obviously! And don't you forget it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="158">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <test expr="~background~" value="tiki bar" />
                <test expr="~self.slot~" cmp="!=" value="2" />
                <state img="custom:#-stripping">I don't feel like it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Nagatoro0" />
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" stage="0-5" saidMarker="Nagatoro0" sayingMarker="sweet02" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="Sweetheart_nagatoroA1">Making it clear that I stand above all others is one of my favorite pastimes, something you won't understand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="72" oneShotId="23">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_royalty2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Aqua_Royalty1">You? A goddess? Ohohohohoho! Oh, how silly of you. You don't even properly act like one with all that whining you're doing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="76" oneShotId="26">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_EnoughPranks_cont" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Sweetheart_donut_lady1">What are you mumbling about, peasant? Of what foolishness do you speak? Or has your mind simply given up trying to understand my grandiose personality?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="80">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart0b" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Yumeko0b">You see, my kingdom is a giant castle adjacent to a lovely forest. I control many servants that work day and night to keep me entertained and the castle running. I also own the most expensive art pieces that clams can buy!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="84">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart1b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Yumeko1b">Exactly! Rarely do I find people like you who understand my position. It's quite refreshing to hear.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="87">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart2b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Yumeko2a">But that's not all. I'm also here for my own enjoyment to compare my stunning figure to everyone else's. Which, given who I'm playing with, it is obvious that I'd win!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="90">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart3b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Yumeko3b">Hmph, a trivial situation. Clearly, the dealer wants to see me in my full glory before letting me win. Insolent, but understanding.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="93">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart4b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Yumeko4b">Foolish woman, it's the only explanation why someone like me could lose. Or do you have a better explanation, peasant?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="96">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart5b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Yumeko5b">My method is very simple; find out who does it and throw them into the dungeon! Where they belong!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="99">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart6b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Yumeko6b">Of course not! I am supposed to win! That is how it should be!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="104">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s0b" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua0b">In every single way, of course. I'm cuter, prettier, smarter, and have a bigger kingdom. Bachelors throw themselves at me any chance they get.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="108">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s1b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua1b">I am indeed from a long line of donuts. I still see my grandmother fairly often. One of the few people out there I care about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="111">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s2b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua2b">It is &lt;i&gt;perfect&lt;/i&gt;. There are statues of me in every corner of the castle, paintings of me on every wall! Everything is a pretty pink color and I have a legion of servants under my command who listen to my every whim.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="115">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s3b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua3b">And what would you know about ruling a kingdom? I have an entire castle with all my subjects in it that love me. I don't need to start caring about how they feel when everything is going how I want it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="119">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s4b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua4b">The luxury of serving the most beautiful princess that has ever walked the earth, of course. So why wouldn't they want to follow me and serve me? It's not something any lady can achieve, like you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="122">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s5b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua5b">Regardless how loyal they may be, I have no desire for them to see me naked. Keeping myself out of reach is the best way to motivate them. That, and they aren't pretty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="125">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="qua_sweetheart_s6b" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua6b">The things they wanted out of it; the things they thought were good ideas; the things they had in mind for our future... Went against everything I stood for and desired! But no more! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="128">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_DelusionalPrincess2" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba2b">Ohohoho, the peasant is getting a big mouth again. When will you learn that your words are meaningless when stacked up against the phenomenal sweetheart?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="131">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_hypeBattle2" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba3b">The only thing your followers would pray for, is for you to leave them alone. I can't imagine them wanting someone like you when I'm around, a girl with a kingdom of her own.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="134">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_bigBeforeSmall2" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba4b">Because I'm not like any other princess. I know what I have and I'm not afraid to show off what no-one else can ever have.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="137">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_fakePrincessAgain2" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba5b">​As if someone like you would know what it means to be a great princess. Patience is for those that are too scared to demand what they want!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="311">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="sweetheart01" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="Sweet_Jura01">​How about you just shut up, blondie. And simply bask in my glory!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="358">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartDress2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="MikoDress2">Are you insinuating that I, the most noble of princesses, is wrong in her way of ruling my country? Who are you to judge a noble such as myself?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="362">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartShirt2" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="MikoShirt2">Hmmm, it seems you aren't as foolish as I first thought, I do admit. Your words hold more weight than I had hoped for. But this doesn't change the fact that the only touch I truly need is my own.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="365">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartBra2" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="MikoBra2">What would someone like you truly know about a princess like me? As no previous experiences that you might have had will compare to someone of my caliber.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="379">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_1a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_pink1">I'm the sweetest, cutest, and sexiest donut lady you will ever get the pleasure of knowing. Watch your tongue, or else I will rip it out, got it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="382">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_2a" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_hole1">Hmph, you simply aren't hooked on how amazing I am yet. I normally wouldn't care about what some lunatic like you thinks about me, but you're special. You should feel honored!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="385">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_3a" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_bosom1">Big words for someone who doesn't have her own kingdom, or servants, or even a home! You might fight &lt;i&gt;evil&lt;/i&gt; as a magical girl, but you know nothing about running a kingdom and all the people that want what I have!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="388">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_4a" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_justice1">Clearly you don't. The fact that you think I'm some great evil, while you misunderstand what I'm saying. It is a clear sign you don't understand a thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="391">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_5a" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_tongue1">I'll humor you, what are all these &lt;i&gt;evil&lt;/i&gt; things I've done? I haven't hurt anybody, I haven't lied, I haven't stolen anything either. So do tell me why you think I'm such a monster.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="394">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_6a" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_speak1">I didn't ask you to tell me, I demand you tell me! Or are you so stupid you can't even understand a princess's demands?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="397">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_7a" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_loses1">A fake magical girl with fake magic with fake love powers! The outcome of this game no longer matters, my only objective is to make sure you understand who is on top of the food chain!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="148">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Oh well, no need to be upset by something so trivial. I'm here to enjoy myself after all, having everyone swoon over me in the process.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="152">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">And, well. Who am I to disappoint the crowd? I have just the thing that will make everyone's jaw drop.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="155">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Too bad! I've already given you more than you deserve. So I'm going to get rid of my shoes. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="162">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Tsk, these are always such a pain to remove. They look amazing on me, but getting them to sit in your hair without getting sticky is tricky. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="163">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="custom:#-stripping1">Neh!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="166">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png">But there is a price for getting to see what &lt;i&gt;true&lt;/i&gt; perfection looks like.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="281">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="custom:#-stripping">&lt;i&gt;Get this filth off me!&lt;/i&gt; </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="282">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Once I get my hands on that brat, there will be hell to pay for making me clean that filthy whale! Then she promised me that I could still come to the plans I had made, but only if I wore this stupid maid dress!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="283">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Before any of you get any smart ideas, No, you cannot hire me as a maid. This is an exception! I won't tell you why it is, but it just is. So if any of you start asking me to come clean your home, you can expect a flail to the face!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="284">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Just... Need to carefully get rid of the remaining parts of this outfit. Don't want to strip my G-string with it. You perverts don't deserve such a blessing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="285">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Ugh, fine. Despite my unending frustration at having to strip for those that don't even deserve a glimpse of me, I would rather get rid of this last piece of the maid's outfit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="286">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" font-size="small">My voluptuousness is unbound, unreachable by those that aren't powerful and wealthy, such as myself. Even if I lose this stupid little game, I'll still be the most stunning, alluring, desirable, cunning, and perfect princess! Something no-one can take away from me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="287">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It is time for all of you to become just a tad more envious. Knowing that besides being pretty much perfect in every regard, my breasts are no exception!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="28">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" font-size="smaller">Do you have any idea how hard it was to find these immaculate shoes? Within and around the castle, I am the only proper lady within my kingdom. While everyone else is but simple Sprout Moles, who have &lt;i&gt;tofu&lt;/i&gt; for feet. Which is, of course, not appropriate for a lady of my caliber.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="29">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" font-size="small">I cannot believe that you dirty perverts managed to undress me all the way. Here I am trying to be a good sport and play along even when I unrightfully lost a few rounds. But every single one of you misused my generous gifts! Despite this, you &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; demand I take everything off...!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png" font-size="smaller">I am none other than the most wealthy, charming, and alluring princess that has ever walked the Earth! I have hundreds of fans throwing themselves at me every day, statues of myself in every corner of my castle! The name Sweetheart must forever be branded on those feeble little minds of yours!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="23">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" font-size="smaller">I am also incredibly humble and give a lot to the poor. Who else would let her underlings live inside of her castle? And the only thing I want is their total obedience and loyalty. It is hard being this generous. But it is just one of the many good deeds I do as the most captivating donut princess of all time!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="24">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png">Kneel, all! You are about to witness the best pair of breasts you will ever witness in your lifespan!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="25">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png">My ever-adoring fans would kill for a chance to see me, Sweetheart, in her full unfiltered glory! Though you troglodytes don't deserve it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="31">
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" font-size="small">When it comes to my wardrobe, I spare no expense. I have everything custom-made by the best tailors my kingdom has to offer. It has to be as clear as the difference between night and day that I stand above all others, both in status and style!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1" id="73" oneShotId="24">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_royalty3" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Aqua_Royalty2">Ohohoho! Surprised? I am not merely just any boring princess, I am Sweetheart! The most benevolent and charming donut girl that has ever walked the earth! You won't find anyone else quite like me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="77" oneShotId="29">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_EnoughPranks_end" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Sweetheart_donut_lady2" font-size="small">Silence! Your feeble words mean nothing to me! In my eyes, you're just a peasant role playing a goddess. Nothing more than a delusional girl that stands no chance when compared to my radiating beauty!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="81">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart0c" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Yumeko0b">Perhaps you might be that lucky one day. I can always use more fans that adore me and my kingdom!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="85">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart1c" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Yumeko1c">You'd be surprised! Even the highest ranking servants in my kingdom still sometimes forget just how important I am! Just look at me! Is there a princess more beautiful than I am? No, the answer is no.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="88">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart2c" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Yumeko2c">Of course, I still deserve to win. That is how the life of royalty should be after all. But for now, I am more than fine with showing off my perfect body~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="91">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart3c" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Yumeko3c">Oh, how silly of you. A princess &lt;i&gt;always&lt;/i&gt; deserves the win. I forgive you for your foolishness.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="94">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart4c" />
                <state img="#-stripping1.png" marker="Yumeko4c">No no no, it seems you got it all wrong. I knew you wouldn't last long before you started talking nonsense!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="97">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart5c" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="yumeko5c">Ha! Of course I will. I am the great sweetheart! No-one cheats against me and gets away with it!... Wait, what was that last thing you just said!?… I'm going to pretend I didn't hear that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="100">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart6c" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="Yumeko6c">Scared? Me? The great sweetheart!? Even the idea itself is an insult to me! My body is that of a temple and I feel no shame showing it off, but losing? To commoners!? Unacceptable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="105">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s0c" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua0c">Do you even have to ask? Of course! When you're as great as me, being humble is a given... Hm? What are you acting shocked about?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="109">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s1c" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua1c">Yes? That is what I just said, didn't I? Open your ears when I'm talking to you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="112">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s2c" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua2c">Yes! Every single corner is covered with my beautiful body. My servants don't know how good they have it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="116">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s3c" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua3c">You know, you can become a devoted follower of mine if you so desire. Working for me will give you a fulfilling life. Who knows. Maybe you'll even become my favorite~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="120">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s4c" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua4c">No, I live in a giant castle filled to the brim with everything I desire. You could learn a thing or two from me, you know.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="123">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s5c" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="weetheart_aqua5c">Alas, in a cruel twist of fate. I have yet to meet someone to spend my life with. The only one who is good enough to always be with me is myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="126">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_kh" sayingMarker="aqua_sweetheart_s6c" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="sweetheart_aqua6c">Of course it does, but it is not something all of you should be worrying about. I am long past those times. And I love myself more than ever.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="129">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_DelusionalPrincess3" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba2c">With this perfect chest of mine, I stand far &lt;i&gt;far&lt;/i&gt; above what you are. Go cry about your inferiority while I show off just how good I look.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="132">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_hypeBattle3" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba3c">Such delusions you commoners have. Trying everything in their power to make me look bad, but I'm rich! I'm beautiful! I get lovers thrown at me all the time for my stunning personality. You just don't compare.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="135">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_bigBeforeSmall3" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba4c">And that is why they are all inferior to me. Cowards that don't dare to show off even the smallest amount of skin. The great sweetheart has no problems showing herself off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="138">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_fakePrincessAgain3" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweetheart_aquakonosuba5c">Your feeble demands will be met by silence as you don't have anyone who is willing to listen to your delusional rants.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="360">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartDress3" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="MikoDress3">A crown prince? How silly. Everyone knows princesses are better! And I'm a donut princess to boot, so even better!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="363">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartShirt3" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="MikoShirt3" font-size="small">Hmm, perhaps so. Yes.  I disagree with you saying that my own touch isn't enough, but if a genuine prince could impress me with his charming smile, personality, and looks, I might fall in love with him. My, the idea alone is causing me to feel flustered.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="366">
                <condition role="other" character="miko" sayingMarker="SweetheartBra3" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="MikoBra3">Your words compel me, prince. You seem to truly understand the beauty I possess. I will give you the chance to court me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="380">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_1b" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_pink2">You will soon learn that picking a fight with me only ends in one way: you, locked up in my dungeon!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="383">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_2b" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_hole2">Ohohohoho! The uninitiated rarely seem to understand the situation they are in. &lt;i&gt;You&lt;/i&gt; should feel honored being in the presence of the sexiest princess of them all! Just look at how amazing I look! No-one else compares!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="386">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_3b" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_bosom2">What a way to tell me that you failed to protect your kingdom! You and your sisters failed and now you're just jealous that I have a kingdom that people are willing to die for! Just like my chest~</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="389">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_4b" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_justice2">Keep telling yourself that, while you're having an existential crisis. I'll be here, showing off my perfect body.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="392">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_5b" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_tongue2">Hmph! Sounds like a &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; issue. As far as I'm concerned, I've done nothing wrong! A princess of love and affection can't ever be in the wrong!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="395">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_6b" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_speak2">So you were just bluffing. How dull. For a lady filled with &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;justice&lt;/i&gt;. You sure don't act like one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="398">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_7b" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_loses2">I won't even entertain the idea that a clown such as yourself could ever be anything else then a servant for more important people, like me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="150">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Donut_Girl">How could you not swoon for me? I'm the hottest donut girl there ever was! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="153">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png">I dare you to find someone who can pull this off better than me. Spoiler warning, you can't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="156">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png">And I know some of you perverts would love nothing more than for me to grind my feet against your privates, wouldn't you? Better start praying for a miracle to happen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5" id="160">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Disappointed? Well, that's not my problem now, is it? Beat me again and I might just show you more. Ha, if you could ever manage that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="164">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Ah! That feels &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; better. It's been awhile since I last let my hair down like this. So you had better appreciate it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="167">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-stripped_summer.png">My lovely bow back on my head! This feels much better. I almost felt completely naked without it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="289">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Donut_Girl">I can't believe that I even have to clean up my own mess! I have servants for this, you know!... Hmph! Stupid Perfectheart and her stupid rules!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="290">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="custom:#-stripped">This entire situation makes me so mad I could shove this entire broom up her ass!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="291">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I'm sure you peasants &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; to see me struggle like this, but this means nothing! I'm still a glorious princess that everyone will bow to! I'll have you kiss my feet at the end of this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="292">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Tada! Am I not the most gorgeous lady to ever walk the earth? Look at my hips and tell me you don't want to be in between those. I know you do, lying to a princess is forbidden after all. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="293">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">But you just wait! The princess always gets her happy ending at the end of the story! This won't be any different.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="294">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Bark for me, you pathetic low-lifes! Bark for your superior! You are all but maids and butlers to me! Only here to serve my every whim. Begging me to give you even an ounce of my attention! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="295">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweepheart" />
                <state img="#-stripped_summer.png">And to top it all off! Being a princess means I can just put my beloved bow back on my head, ignoring everyone who complains about me putting something back on. I love being a princess! Ohohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="43">
                <state img="#-stripped.png" marker="Donut_Girl">I am the cutest, sexiest, most earnest donut girl that has ever existed! There is no-one in the world who can even come close to how desirable I am!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="27">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Now that you know why &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am the most important lady here, I expect every single one of you to shower me with your affection from here on out. A princess deserves nothing less, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="20">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Rejoice! As the most benevolent and wonderful Sweetheart has given the peasants a sight they won't ever forget! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="19">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Here it is! Sweetheart in her purest form! Bask in the glory that is I, Sweetheart! Cry, for you will never ever have a figure more unfathomable than mine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Those wristbands are worth more than your entire life, ~player~. So don't try and touch them with your filthy hands. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Don't even think about touching those wristbands, ~player~. They are far too expensive to be touched by &lt;i&gt;your&lt;/i&gt; hands.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Hmph, why am I even trying to tell you these kinds of things? I doubt peasants like you even understand the value of a good set of shoes. I bet that you get all yours from the garbage bin! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">...I just got &lt;i&gt;irritatingly&lt;/i&gt; reminded that there used to be weirdos within my castle that kept asking to be "stepped on". At first I thought that they simply enjoyed being tortured... How wrong I was.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="30">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" font-size="smaller">However... Ohohoho... How could you all not? With my dazzling looks... My charming smile... My gregarious personality. It must be so difficult to even stand in my presence! Like everyone else I have ever met, you are just jealous of me! And wish to be all that I am! Unfortunately for all of you, that will &lt;i&gt;never&lt;/i&gt; happen!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9" id="330" oneShotId="57">
                <condition filter="dumb" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="2033">You foolish brute. Did you think you could impress me with your low IQ? Think again! &lt;i&gt;If&lt;/i&gt; you can even do something as simple as that.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2034">Perhaps you nitwit might not understand. But the goal of the game is to win, unless you are some kind of degenerate that gets off on losing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="333">
                <condition filter="wealthy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2037">Tsk! You look like you're well off. But to me, you are nothing more than a fraud who wants to seem more important than you really are!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="336" oneShotId="58">
                <condition filterAdv="shut_in&amp;!taken" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2091">Let me guess, you have an online girlfriend?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="342">
                <condition filter="greedy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2103">A man should be anything &lt;i&gt;but&lt;/i&gt; greedy, they should give everything they have to those they love and adore. Naturally, I will be awaiting your generous offerings in my name.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="344">
                <condition filter="formal_attire" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2108">What ~name~ is wearing is the correct attire when in the presence of a princess. Such a shame that he himself isn't handsome enough to become my butler.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Foolish boy! Did you really think you would last long against the phenomenal Sweetheart?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">OHOHO! Is that the best you can do, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Disgraceful behavior, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmph! Child's play! You never stood a chance against the lustrous Sweetheart! </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Ohohoho~ How unsurprising.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">It doesn't seem like you know how to impress a princess. I suppose I'll keep my expectations low for you. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Leave it to someone like ~name~ to not know how to play a simple card game.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Being a loser fits you well.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">&lt;i&gt;Looooooooser.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Ah, the joy of seeing others lose won't ever be dull.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Bow to your superior, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">All men should offer themselves up to me. I am their superior after all. You're no exception, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">A well-deserved loss, wouldn't you say?</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">You couldn't withstand my alluring body now, could you? I'm not shaming you for it; I just know it's the truth.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">You got punished for staring at me, ~name~. But who could ever resist me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Submit to me, ~name~! I, Sweetheart, demand it!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Make your choice, ~name~. Either you take off something good, or I will make you regret it.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Please your princess, ~name~! Bare your body for me.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Grovel before me, ~name~! Worship your princess!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't just stand there like a doofus, ~name~! Your duchess is awaiting your attention and obedience!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Give me what I want and give it to me &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;! ~Name~!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Your princess desires to be entertained, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hnghh... How big is the chance ~name~ is about to disappoint me? I don't even want to think about it.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Just make it quick. I'm trying to enjoy myself here.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">That's what you get when you unfairly beat me! Strip for my amusement!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">This defeat can only be remedied when you go on your knees and kiss my feet right now!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">​I can overlook this transgression if you grovel right now and beg for forgiveness!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Hnggh... Stop trying to hog my attention! I need all of it for myself.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Yeah... Yeah... Go do your little thing. I'm busy here.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">It's too late for my forgiveness, ~name~. Once again, the only person I can trust is myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Go ahead, ~name~. Embarrass yourself for me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My radiance is everlasting. It's only natural for you to strip and &lt;i&gt;bask&lt;/i&gt; in my heavenly radiance.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Nothing you could do would ever compare to my status, ~name~. However, perhaps you might yet surprise me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">You cannot match what I am, ~name~. But if you're that confident to try, then go on. Impress me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">OHOHOHO! Silly boy, how could you ever hope to compete against me?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I will spare but a single moment for you, ~name~. Don't waste it!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">A real knight in shining armor wouldn't have lost this round. Which says enough about what kind of person &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; are, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Just because I lost a few rounds doesn't make you any less of a loser, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">And all is right in the world whenever ~name~ loses.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">That's what you get when you underestimate the great Sweetheart!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">No-one ever lasts long against me, so there is no shame in losing to me. Except! That you should feel ashamed for thinking you could ever compare yourself to me!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">A good servant would do as I say and strip quickly so that he doesn't waste all of my precious time.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">Better start barking like the dog you are. You can't hope to win against someone as divine as myself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Losing for me doesn't suddenly make me attracted to you, but at least it's good entertainment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="265" priority="0">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="1637">That's what loud-mouthed fools like you deserve for being so rude to a princess!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="1638">Oh no, did the pesky commoner lose a round? How &lt;i&gt;horrible.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1639">​What can I say? If you act like a mule, you'll be treated like a mule!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="1640">Jerks will get no sympathy from me. I hope you keep losing and losing and losing!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="1645">No need to put up with such a rude act before me, ~name~. Everything will end up bowing to me in the end, so it's smart to know your place beforehand.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1665">Could someone put a muzzle on ~name~? His loud barking is starting to get on my nerves.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-9" id="334">
                <condition filter="wealthy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2047">Hmph! You look like a cheap imitation of a real wealthy member of society! Like me! I will put you in your place you faker!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="338">
                <condition filter="shut_in" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2087">...Do you even &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; what the sun looks like? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="3015">You look like the average prisoner I have. Pale and looking like they haven't seen the sun in ages.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="339">
                <condition filter="quiet" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="2096">What's that? Speak up! I won't have you mumble when you're in the presence of a princess!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="341">
                <condition filter="greedy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="2101">I can see it in your eyes, your desire for trinkets and baubles is unmistakable. Let it be known if I catch you touching any of my belongings, there will be a special place in my dungeon for you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="343">
                <condition filter="formal_attire" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2105">Fancy clothing is for those that can &lt;i&gt;actually&lt;/i&gt; pull it off, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="345">
                <condition filter="scantily-clad" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2114">Excuse me, ~name~. But the brothel is a few streets further. I'm sure you can find suitable work for yourself there.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2115">you couldn't even afford to put on clothes that cover more than the bare essentials? Disgraceful!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="346">
                <condition filter="makeup" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="2140">you peasants have no clue how to use makeup properly. I'm surprised you can even blink with how covered your eyelids are</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="2139">No amount of makeup will ever make your ugly soul look pretty.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Oh, it's just ~name~ who lost. Nothing of interest.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Choose wisely, ~name~. A bored princess is a dangerous princess.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Better start stripping, peasant. Best not to keep me waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I can already hear your excuses coming out of your mouth about why you lost, but please, spare my ears the trouble.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Oh my, it seems that there is something you &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; good at, ~name~. Losing!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Don't be a wimp, ~name~. No-one cares what you strip as long as &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am here.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Something wrong, ~name~? Afraid you're getting overshadowed by me? The most adorable princess of all time? Well, you are, so stop whining and start stripping.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Put upon yourself a jester costume if you're planning to lose like a clown.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Dance peasant! Dance for my amusement!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do you know how many of my fans desperately try to get my attention at any given moment? Do you know how valuable my time is? If you do, make this quick.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Any time that is spent on ~name~, is time spent not worshiping me. Which is inexcusable.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Are there any rules regarding simply ignoring someone if they don't satisfy me? Just asking, it could come in &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; handy sometime soon.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">That's what you get when you compare yourself to me!</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">I'm way too pretty for someone like you to impress me, but go ahead. Entertain me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You had better pick something worth my time! I won't stand for it if you pick something boring while I'm here in my full glory!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Hmph! You get an important chance to impress me right now, ~name~. Give it your all! Or else you're going to regret it!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Why would anyone care that ~name~ has to strip? While I'm here showing off just how amazing I truly am?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Something wrong, ~name~? I'm not distracting you, am I? Ohohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You lost on purpose, didn't you, ~name~? Don't try to lie your way out of it, I just know you did it to show yourself off to me.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">You think you got what you need to contest me? Don't be silly. You're nothing compared to me.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Too busy loving myself to give you any attention. Sorry not sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">No women has ever managed to look better, cutter, more desirable than me. And ~name~ is not changing that!</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">Hngh... ~name~ wishes that she could be this pillow; I know she does.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Foolish girl! Did you really think you would last long against the phenomenal Sweetheart?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Like taking candy from a sprout!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Yawn&lt;/i&gt;. Too easy!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Get used to this feeling of losing, peasant.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">A loss for you, means victory for me. As it should be! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh no, ~name~ lost. Who could have&lt;/i&gt; ever &lt;i&gt;seen that coming?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Try not to make this &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; boring.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">That lovely feeling of winning will never bore me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">​Entertain me peasant! That's the only reason I can even tolerate you being near my presence.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="953">Hmmm... If I increase the taxes on the servants that live inside my castle, perhaps I could also increase the amount of shows I can put out each week. Hm? Yes, I know ~name~ has to strip, can't you see I'm busy?</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">It's hard to care about people that are just so much less important, don't you agree, ~player~? No need to speak, your input is not required.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Ohohohohoho! Are you beginning to regret challenging the fabulous and amazing Sweetheart? </state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Losing fits a loser, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Look at me while you strip, ~name~. I want to see the defeat in your eyes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="266" priority="0">
                <condition filter="mean" role="target" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1679">Tsk, how typical of someone like you, ~name~. I am what you can never have, so you start acting like a female dog towards me.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="1691">You aren't nearly pretty or important enough to have such a tone with me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="1690">You won't get any suitors acting like that, ~name~. On the other hand, with how you look, I doubt that you'd get any in the first place! Ohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="1692">As mean as you're ugly, fitting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="267" priority="0">
                <condition filter="royalty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1697">I know that you are inferior to me in every single way, ~name~. But please, at least &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; to match my level of royal status.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-amused.png">As I am &lt;i&gt;royalty&lt;/i&gt;, this tie should be a win for me and a loss for all others!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="349" oneShotId="61">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2151">...I should come up with a new place for a horrendous person such as yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2152">&lt;i&gt;every&lt;/i&gt; single thing you've done this game has been vexing me. The dungeons are too good for you, I'll feed you to my bears the moment this little game is over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="354" oneShotId="65">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="2192">...What kind of stupidity am I dealing with here? How dare you shoot a weapon while I'm here you swine!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="2193">...Who let you out of the mental asylum!? You will pay for firing off a weapon near a princess!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="322">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1957">Why &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; men not stylize more? Don't they realize that I have to look at them to evaluate if they are a worthy husband? I don't want to look at some penury guy if I can avoid it.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1962">When has a guy taking off his shoes ever be interesting? Seriously? They don't have what it takes to be captivating with even the smallest of things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bored.png">That better not be all that you strip, ~name~! </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Your accessories are but naught compared to mine, commoner. Now remove them at once!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Don't waste my time with idle chit-chat, ~name~. Your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural( are| is)~ hardly deserving of any attention.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Like a pebble trying to outshine a ruby. How pathetic.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I have never met a man that knew how to properly accessorize... And I still haven't.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Most men in my life don't wear unnecessary trinkets. I guess most of them are smart enough not to try and take attention away from me. Not like they ever could though.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Why do men always have the poorest of trinkets? They rarely look pretty enough to wear, and they always have some &lt;i&gt;sentimental&lt;/i&gt; value to them. But spoilers! That doesn't mean they look good on you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Nngh... Huh? ~name~ is taking something off? And why should &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; care about that!? Don't you see I'm busy spoiling myself? Ugh, &lt;i&gt;fine&lt;/i&gt;. I'm paying attention.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Think...&lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; carefully about your next move, ~name~. It's a decision between life and death! </state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I don't care about your silly little story, ~name~. What I want is for you to be on your hands and knees before me!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hnngg... Stop trying to get my attention while I'm busy with myself!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Oh, &lt;i&gt;yay&lt;/i&gt;. I'm missing &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt; time because some douchebag over there has to try and get my attention!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Why even waste your time with such horrid-looking accessories? Keep them home next time. I don't want to see them again.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What an eye sore. Better to get rid of it.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I have met many bachelors that think they could impress me by giving me some cheap baubles. They remind me of what you are taking off, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">You have too many insignificant pieces of baubles for my liking, ~name~. Yes, I have those as well. But I'm the prettiest girl there is, so I'm allowed to have them. Besides, they look amazing on me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Is this your attempt at trying to tease me? Ohohoho! I'd suggest becoming a jester. It would suit someone as silly as you.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Trying to arouse my anger by taking off meaningless baubles, ~name~? Well, it's working!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="313">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1910">Those must be the cheapest shoes I've ever laid my eyes upon. Please, remove them at once and throw them into a nearby incinerator.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1912">How much did those &lt;i&gt;horrendous&lt;/i&gt; shoes cost? Or did the shopkeeper pay &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; to be rid of them?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="324">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="hat" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1969">Wake me up when you take off a crown, instead of that filthy looking hat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="325">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="cape" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1973">Doesn't it feel much better not having that silly thing drag you down? How many times I've seen potential candidates ruin their chances because they slipped on it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="328">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="hat" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1998">So... Are you going to do something special with that? Like a magic trick? It would be the most entertaining thing you've have done since you got here.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Ugh, it reeks of being cheap.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">If a bachelor ever did dare give me something so horrid looking, I would answer back in kind. By crushing his family jewels. </state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Words fail to describe just how utterly disappointing you are.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I should be insulted by the utter lack of respect that you are showing me, ~name~. But perhaps I'm being too harsh on you. Can't expect pigs to have good manners now, can we?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I wouldn't want to be found dead wearing that!... Unless you got it from your grandmother... That would be the only good reason to wear it.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Where did you even get that thing from? The garbage heap? You do seem like the kind of guy that would go through someone else's trash.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I guess it wouldn't look &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; bad... if you were a sproutmole perhaps.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">When even my lowly fans can dress better than you, that's when you know you're a fashion disaster.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">If this doesn't end with you kissing my feet and worshiping me, it's not worth my attention.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Do you simpletons know nothing about satisfying a princess?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Move along, I have better things to spend my time on, like loving myself!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph. And to think I gave you a glimpse of my attention, only for you to waste it!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Some people say not to judge a book by its cover. But if the book had a picture of ~name~ on it, I can assure you I would never read it in my life!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Disturbing a princess while she is touching herself should be a bannable offense!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I'm not kind to those that dishearten me and fail to meet &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; expectations. You'll feel the consequences of your actions... Once I'm done loving myself~</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I'm... perfect... ~name~... is a loser... All is right in the world.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">You don't even realize just how grateful you should be! Being allowed to watch me touch myself is an honor that's beyond what you deserve!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Shove that thing where the sun doesn't shine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good riddance!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">&lt;i&gt;Just&lt;/i&gt; your ~clothing~? That's not good enough! I demand you take off more!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">May I never see something so ugly ever again.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'm going to pretend you took off something more interesting...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Throw it into the trash bag. Where it belongs!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Men are too barbaric these days. </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm sure your little trinket cost you a lot of money at the thrift store. </state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I wouldn't want to find my boyfriend &lt;i&gt;dead&lt;/i&gt; wearing something so ugly.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="255">
                <condition role="target" character="larachel" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">OHOHOHOHOHO! You? Royalty? Don't be absurd! You are but a peasant pretending to be more than just a common wench!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="314">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="1925">Getting rid of those unsightly shoes, ~name~? What a shame, they fit you &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; well.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1932">Ugh, revolting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-amused.png">I can't even &lt;i&gt;imagine&lt;/i&gt; wearing something &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; ugly. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I don't have all day, ~name~. Chop-chop!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I'm certain it took all your brain power to come up with &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; as your choice of item to strip.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I doubt that this will prelude to something more interesting. But I'm willing to give it a shot, so you had better be grateful.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">​Why delay the inevitable? We &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; know that I'm going to win.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">​Perhaps you should come visit my castle one day, ~name~. I've got plenty of fans that will sell you only the most valuable trinkets and baubles. Much better than what you're wearing.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Ew! Why do you even have that? Why do you even &lt;i&gt;wear&lt;/i&gt; that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Can't you just skip the prelude and get to the final part of your performance? I'm getting rather bored waiting for such insignificant strips.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Those idiotic fans of mine had better be preparing for the next part of "Sweetheart's Quest For Hearts" while I'm away.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">You aren't impressing &lt;i&gt;anyone&lt;/i&gt; picking &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; boring small thing. </state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Uninteresting and unneeded. Remove what needs to be removed and let us pick up the pace.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Every trinket has its own story. This doesn't mean I'm interested in hearing it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Nothing you do will take away from my intense self-loving, ~name~. So make it quick.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">​Make it quick, ~name~. I desire all eyes to be me, not you.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Don't talk too much, I'm trying to enjoy myself!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Bla bla bla!&lt;/i&gt; I'm ~name~, and I'll talk about totally unnecessary things while a beautiful princess is touching herself!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">&lt;i&gt;Hmm... I'm amazing&lt;/i&gt;. I- Huh? Oh, it's just ~name~ being a disappointment again.  </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="12" priority="0">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1949">Bleh, this girl barks too much for my liking, someone put a collar on her. </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1950">Barking dogs should be put down!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9" id="49">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">Just when I thought you couldn't be any weirder, freakshow.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="315">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="shoes" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1941">Did you know that there are &lt;i&gt;neanderthals&lt;/i&gt; out there that want to look as poor as you do with those lousy shoes, despite the fact that they are rich?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1946">I wonder if you could sell those shoes to some weirdo online. You'd lose your dignity doing so, but that's nothing a poverty-stricken person like you would need to worry about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="323">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2010">What kind of fool would take off their glasses in a game in which they need to look at other people?</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2011">You can take off your glasses all you want, but you cannot hide from the fact that I look better then you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="326">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="cape" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2015">What made you decide to wear such a ridiculous thing in the first place? Besides the fact that you have no fashion sense. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="329">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="hat" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2000">Perhaps there is some value to be had by wearing a hat from time to time. Given it isn't something cheap like ~name~ just took off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-7 9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I didn't think you could disappoint me more than you already did, ~name~. But here we are.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Don't expect me to comment on each and every insignificant strip you do, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This only further cements the fact that you have no taste.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Is that all you will strip? Do you think you can just waste &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; time like this? Disgraceful!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Commoners do so enjoy ugly baubles. It's something I will never understand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Remove as many baubles as you need, commoner. It won't stop the inevitable.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">It's almost impressive how someone can be so mind-numbingly &lt;i&gt;unexciting&lt;/i&gt;. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What a mundane choice. Are you always like this in your daily life? Don't answer that, I already know what you're going to say.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Who even wears such an ugly trinket to begin with?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">​May I never see anything so ugly ever again.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1171">Don't misunderstand the situation, I am here for my own enjoyment and see others grovel before me. I couldn't care less about how you look. I will belittle you all the same.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">As small as your dignity!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug.png">​Smart move, ~name~. No-one would care what you would take off while I'm showing my passion.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Your attempts at trying to take the spotlight from me are nothing more than irritating, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">All that attention hogging just for you to take off a bauble, bleh.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Back to what is really important, me!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Don't disturb my self-loving for something so measly ever again!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">An ugly trinket for an even uglier lady!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">I wouldn't want to be found dead wearing something like that.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">You aren't important enough to be talking so much, ~name~. Proceed without further delay.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I'm sure that whatever you're talking about is very important to you, but I couldn't care less.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">What is this insufferable noise I'm hearing? Oh... it's just ~name~ talking.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Your ~clothing~ look~clothing.ifPlural( like they belong|s like it belongs)~ to a vagabond. Ew. </state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Boooooooooooooring&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Ugh, hellooooo? ~Name~? The most charming girl you have ever seen in your life is already showing off her alluring body. Take something better off!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Could you be &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; less interesting? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Time is of the essence, ~name~. If it isn't going to be interesting, don't waste my time on it.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Boring your princess deserves punishment, ~name~. I'm merciful enough to let you know beforehand.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Aren't you supposed to try and woo the pretty princess? It's not that you have a chance with me, I just want to see you try and fail.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh, wow. You picked your ~clothing~. How daring, really. I'm tingling with excitement.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">No romance has ever started by taking off something dull! Just something to keep in mind.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">You won't sweep a princess off her feet by choosing the safe option, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Sigh&lt;/i&gt;, you really are hopeless. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">It's quite miserable that even my stupid fans have better taste in fashion than you do, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Why not just strip it all off at once? Spares me a lot of time that I can spend pampering myself.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">That was a waste of my time. Let us continue before you arouse my anger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">A peasant's prelude is hardly worth my time.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I shouldn't forget to get through all that fanmail I got earlier today.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">It is but all too clear to me that you lack the flair to properly entertain me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I will never understand a commoner's fashion.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let us continue before I lose my temper.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">~Name~ truly is a shining example of not knowing how to impress.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="single" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="221">And that is why you're still single, ~name~. Why would anyone be interested in someone as dull as you? Ohohoho! Hm? How do I know that he is single? Well, just look at him!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-9" id="258" oneShotId="48">
                <condition role="target" character="rosa" stage="2" sayingMarker="rosa_special_other" />
                <test expr="~background~" cmp="!=" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">​Yes, yes, the person you are looking for is me, Rosa. I am everyone's significant other. But no-one can have me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="261" oneShotId="50">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" sayingMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Just when I thought my opinion of you couldn't get any lower, you go and do some silly antics like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="331">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="leggings" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2028">~Name~... taking something interesting off? Who are you and what did you do to the &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; ~name~? The boring and lame one? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'd rather watch paint dry at this pace.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hurry along, peasant. You're not waiting for your harvest to sprout. You're here to &lt;i&gt;entertain me!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">My servants are either on time, or end up somewhere &lt;i&gt;very&lt;/i&gt; dark. Just a little something to keep in mind, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I, being the most astounding princess to have ever walked the earth, have better things to do than wait for you to strip, ~name~. So, hurry up.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">While you are doing your... thing. I'll be standing here, showing off my magnificence.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Only a fool would throw away this golden opportunity by choosing something so insignificant.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">That... &lt;i&gt;thing&lt;/i&gt; you're taking off looks like you got it from the garbage can... in other words, it's utterly worthless! </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Name~ clearly doesn't appreciate theatrics.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">What is this... overwhelming feeling of dread and sorrow I'm feeling? Oh... it's just ~name~ taking something off.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I'm at a loss for words. ~Name~? Taking off something unexciting? &lt;i&gt;Say it ain't so!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Bah! Is that all you will be taking off? Disappointment must be your middle name then.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-9" id="332">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="leggings" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="2026">Easily the best thing you could have taken off. It's the one thing that kind of suited you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hmph, not pink enough.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Any lady worth her salt should know how to stylize, ~name~. I'd suggest you look into it for your own sake.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">I would have picked something more exciting. But then again, I am the most &lt;i&gt;dazzling&lt;/i&gt; princess there is!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It's not as if I expected more from you anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">...Are you &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; talking? Ugh, what nonsense.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmmm... I could really go for a massage. It's been too long since I last had one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-bored.png">I could be betting on horse races, or be dining in the most luxurious of establishments. But no, I'm doomed to spend my time with Lady &lt;i&gt;Tiresome&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Had you been any more interesting, I wouldn't have minded waiting for your measly little strip, ~name~. But you are as interesting as watching grass grow.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Could you at least &lt;i&gt;try&lt;/i&gt; to not bore me? I know that might seem hard for a neanderthal like you, but I'm sure even you can figure &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; out.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">At least I don't have to worry about ~name~ trying to steal the spotlight from me. Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">...It is a good thing I didn't need to pay to attend this table... I would have demanded my money back by now.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Boring, boring, boring! You're all so boring! You should be banned from playing strip poker ever again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="single" role="target" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="211">And that is why you're still single, ~name~. Who would anyone be interested in someone as dull as you? Ohohoho! Hm? How do I know she is single? Well, just look at her!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Well, look at that. So you &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; know how to be interesting. It took you long enough.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">This is much more entertaining than seeing useless baubles coming off.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">With your beloved princess watching, there is no way you would disappoint her, right? Right!?</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Don't make me regret giving you my divine attention, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I doubt this is going to be any more interesting than when you take off an accessory.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">It seems that losing has been the only way for you to get my attention, ~name~. I understand you want to impress me, but you will have to do better than that! As I am not easily impressed!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">So, you believe your body is of adequate quality for it to be laid bare before me? The one, the only, magnificent Sweetheart? I shall be the judge of that!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hey! ~Name~! You're supposed to entice me with your stripping skills! And sweep me off my feet! You can't afford to be lazy while performing for a princess!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Go on, ~name~. Impress your dazzling princess.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Let us see if this raises your attractiveness by any significant amount. I wouldn't get your hopes up, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-9" id="249">
                <condition filter="visible_bulge" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.position~" value="lower" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="1345">Yes, yes. I know you're excited to see me, but do contain yourself you brute.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1344">​Contain yourself, dog! I didn't say you were allowed to get so excited about seeing me!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="1346">Obviously, you couldn't contain it once you saw that I'd play at your table. Happens to all that fall for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">For once you didn't disappoint me, ~name~. A rare occurrence that I hope you can maintain.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">And another step closer to my glorious victory! Ohohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Rarely do I find myself entranced by someone else's body. Yours... doesn't change that fact~</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't you feel any shame? Showing off your perverted body in front of a princess?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hardly worth the time of a &lt;i&gt;delicate&lt;/i&gt; princess like me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Your efforts to entertain me are not going unnoticed, ~name~. That's not to say it's good enough, but it is being seen. Ohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">But even now, you aren't showing anything truly worthwhile. Such is the life of a plebeian, I suppose.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Took you long enough! Don't you know it's rude to make a princess wait? You should grovel for my forgiveness!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Keep this pace up, peasant. I have waited long enough for my entertainment. </state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">​It doesn't matter how hard you try to impress me, ~name~. At the end of the day, you're just a pleb to me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png">Don't try to outshine me, ~name~. Well... not like you ever &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; outshine me!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hmmm... not the &lt;i&gt;worst&lt;/i&gt; thing you could have chosen. But hardly the best either. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">How silly of you to think that something so &lt;i&gt;meager&lt;/i&gt; can impress me.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Put your back into it, ~name~. This is supposed to be your big moment! It won't ever be as big as mine, but you should at least try and entertain me by trying!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">How joyous to see you strip your ~clothing~, ~name~. I was getting tired from looking at it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">&lt;i&gt;Could it be? ~name~ picking something interesting to take off? My oh my, the world must have gone mad!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">It takes a lot of money, skill, and knowledge to properly know how to dress yourself. The three things you don't have!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Keep striping for your princess, ~name~! Grovel and humiliate yourself for me!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Ugh... Could you stop talking for a moment? You are not &lt;i&gt;nearly&lt;/i&gt; interesting enough to talk that much.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Have you learned &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; from my amazing performance, ~name~? At this point, I'm just surprised you even know how to bathe! Ohohoho!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Was that supposed to be some kind of big reveal? I found it to be hardly entertaining.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">A whole lot of noise for a whole lot of nothing.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Congratulations! You still look as uninteresting as before.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Next time, I'd suggest going on your knees and begging for my help. It's quite clear that you don't know a single thing about being &lt;i&gt;alluring&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I guess your choice wasn't... &lt;i&gt;horrible&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Hmph, you have no flare for the dramatic, ~name~. This would be the moment for a lady to entice all those around her. But it seems you couldn't even do something as simple as that.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">&lt;i&gt;Oh my, what is this? has ~name~ finally managed to sweep the oh so charming Sweetheart off her feet?&lt;/i&gt; Pfffft... as if.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Only ~name~ could manage to be dull while taking something big off.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">For something that was supposed to be a &lt;i&gt;big&lt;/i&gt; reveal, you once again managed to bore me, ~name~. It's almost as if you have a natural talent for it. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Have you seen how amazing I look? How am I ever supposed to care about someone like you when I'm right here?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="352" oneShotId="64">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="2185">Ohohohoho! That's what you get for being such a reckless fool!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="2186">Ohohohoho! Such a punishment is well deserved for all those who would dare use weapons in my presence!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="46">Moment of truth, ~name~. Let's see if you have the kind of body that will make me swoon.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="45">A rare moment in which I will share the spotlight. Don't disappoint.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="93">Let's see if you are worthy of becoming my servant~</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="94">​A man's chest is one of the few things that can still impress me, go on.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="99">I don't &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; your chest to enjoy myself, ~name~. But I still welcome it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="100">This is the moment to impress me, ~name~! I might just look at you in a different light after this.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="101">Enough diddle-daddle! Show your princess what you're made of!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="102">A dreamy chest is all I desire. You wouldn't disappoint me, right, ~name~?"</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">What a pleasant surprise. At least you have something good to look at.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good! Servants should look their best when they serve me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="41">It's... serviceable. I had high hopes it would be better.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="42">It's not... terrible, but it's not great either.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="43">It was a bit presumptuous of me to expect your chest to be as great as mine.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="44">​Nothing to write home about, but alas. Not everyone can have a chest as perfect as mine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="95">That's more like it! Bare your everything for your princess!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="96">You should have done that once I started touching myself, ~name~. But I will let it slide... this time!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="97">Ugh... I wish I had more servants like you to look at. The current ones have no chest to speak of.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="98">Not nearly as fulfilling to look at compared to my own chest, but it will do.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="2388">I don't care what you have between your legs; I will mock you for it regardless.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="2389">Ohohohoho! It's time to see how much I get to mock you from here on out.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2390">You can't impress me, no matter what you have down there. So don't get your hopes up.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="2391">Are you prepared to suffer endless insults? No? Well, that sounds like something that isn't my problem.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="2380">What makes &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; so special that you want everyone to look at you?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="2381">You've been hiding something; I know you do. But alas, I'm busy doing &lt;i&gt;important&lt;/i&gt; stuff to really care.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2382">I'm busy here! What makes you so special that you want my attention so badly?</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="2383">You couldn't possibly be interesting enough to have my at-... huh!?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="195">You've been a bore from start to finish, so I have no high hopes that this will be any better.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="196">Nothing that you are about to reveal will be good enough for me, ~name~. Don't get your hopes up.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="197">Here comes the part in which I will endlessly shame you for being too big, too small, or too average! OHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="198">It must be exhausting being that bad at the game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="194">And how is this supposed to be a punishment? Do you know how many men try and fail to get my attention on a daily basis? They would love the chance to show their puny cocks to me.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="199">Oh? You're going to show off your manhood? My, that's perfect. I was about ready to crush your balls if you didn't hurry up.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="200">You've done nothing to deserve my attention, so I have no desire to give you any now that you desire it.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="201">You're no prince charming, ~name~. Nothing you have between your legs will change that fact.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="2456">Let me guess—you're still single. Or your partner is only with you out of pity. Because no-one would ever want someone &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; small.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="2457">That is the saddest little thing that I've ever had the displeasure of witnessing.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2488">A penis befitting a low-life such as yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2487">The only way &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; could ever get yourself off is with &lt;i&gt;tweezers&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="2421">Ohohohohohoho! Does your partner even feel anything when you insert it?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2420">I'm sure you'd call the size average to try and manage the humiliating feeling you must have with such a micropenis.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="2422">What use is having both tools if you don't ever get to use them? I doubt anyone is interested in that tiny little thing of yours! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2460">Good thing I didn't wait for you to reveal your crotch, ~name~. I would have instantly lost interest in pleasuring myself had I seen it beforehand.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="31">Mmm... Is that even three inches tall? My, that is much too short!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="32">...Bwhahahahaha!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="33">That wouldn't even be good enough for a peasant, let alone a princess of my caliber.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="34">Fun-sized? It's not even bite-sized!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="35" marker="chastity">I don't even know if I have a chastity cage that small in my dungeon...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="39">Bleh! I should kick you between your legs for showing me something so pathetic. But you would probably like it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="40">Oh, I'm sure you have a &lt;i&gt;great&lt;/i&gt; personality, ~name~. Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="142">It's about the size of my pinkie finger. How do you even find that thing when you try to touch yourself?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9" id="9" oneShotId="4" priority="0">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="chastity" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="37">I don't think we even have a chastity cage &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; small. I'd have to get one custom made. That's just how small it is! Ohohoho!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2499">I'm sure you can make someone very happy with that, but not a princess. Not nearly impressive enough for someone like me.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="2497">Congratulations! In a sea of mediocrity. Your dick falls perfectly within those parameters!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2498">I really shouldn't be surprised that a low-life would have a mediocre penis at best.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2634">&lt;i&gt;This&lt;/i&gt; is what you've been hyping up? Really? Whenever I think you peasants couldn't get any more pathetic, you find new ways to disappoint me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" id="401">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2585">All that build up... for this? &lt;i&gt;Really?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2586">I would have preferred it to be smaller. At least then I could have had the joy of laughing at you.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="2587">I had no expectations and I'm still disappointed. </state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png" oneShotId="2588">I wouldn't sully my hands for something &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; mediocre. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="38">&lt;i&gt;Yawn&lt;/i&gt;. How utterly uninteresting...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="131">Average... I don't &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; average! The biggest, or the smallest--it doesn't matter to me, I demand perfection and that is all I will accept!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="132">Well, would you look at that, ~name~. It's as boring as you are! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="133">Hope you weren't too proud of that thing of yours, ~name~. It's nothing special.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="135">All that build up... for this? &lt;i&gt;Really?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="136">I would have preferred it to be smaller. At least then I could have had the joy of laughing at you.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="137">I had no expectations and I'm still disappointed. </state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="143">I wouldn't sully my hands for something &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; mediocre. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="2643">I wonder if you'll squirm better than my last victim.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2650">People with big sizes always tend to be narcissistic about it. They are never as humble as me.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png" oneShotId="2651">I have an excessive amount of &lt;i&gt;toys&lt;/i&gt; for penises of your size. Don't worry, I won't be gentle.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2738">As if you'd ever get the chance to use something so oversized on someone. I mean, it's attached to &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="2695">You might impress these other poor peasants with your size. But I'm not so easily impressed; I doubt you even know how to use that thing!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2696">This explains a lot; all that blood that should be in your brain is in your penis instead.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png" oneShotId="2716">What's wrong? Problems keeping that oversized meatstick in check in the presence of greatness?</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Imagine all the ways I can punish that filthy rod of yours.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="138">A tool fit for a mindless barbarian such as yourself, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="139">Maybe you do have some use, ~name~. Instead of using my flail, I could just use that oversized cock of yours instead!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="140">Perhaps that would impress a commoner. But it's too big for me to find useful.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="141">Bigger isn't better, ~name~. Unless it's a statue of me, of course! OHOHOHO!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="146">I suppose you have to compensate for your monotonous personality in some way.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="147">&lt;i&gt;Sigh&lt;/i&gt;. Do I seriously need to buy a bigger chastity belt just for you? What a pain.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="144">The bigger they are, the more pain I can give it!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="145">That &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; fit in between my divine bosom... Ha! As if I would let someone like &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; touch them!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="245">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1289">Hmph! Compensating for something?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1299">&lt;i&gt;Barbaric&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1300">Ugh, just look at it pulsating. Keep that useless meatstick away from me! I am much too delicate for something so repulsive!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="120">We already know what you have, ~name~. Everyone can see beforehand what you are trying to cover up, you aren't impressing anyone with it.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="203">Oh? Is it time already for me to mock your inferior breasts? How delightful.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="202">Go on, ~name~. This is the perfect moment to show why I'm better than you!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="204">It's hard to get excited about another lady's breasts. When mine are perfect.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="218">An ordinary commoner might be interested in what you are about to reveal, ~name~. But a lady of my caliber is not so easily impressed.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="219">&lt;i&gt;Oh, I get to see a commoner's breasts. How delightful.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="220">If I may suspend my disbelief that you had some kind of dignity before you came here. I'd say this is the moment that you lost what little remaining dignity you had left! Ohohoho! </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="248">Watch out everyone! Prepare yourself for the disappointment ~name~ is about to bring us!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="48">
                <condition role="target" character="megumin" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Megumi_nobra">All that bombastic behavior of yours really amounted to nothing when it really mattered! Ohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="257" oneShotId="46">
                <condition role="target" character="myriam" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">​So that's why you've been hiding yourself all game! You're ugly! Ohohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="103">Oh dear. Those are just pitiful.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="104">Small, in both status &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; size!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="105">Those wouldn't even count as proper opening acts!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="106">Is that what a commoner's chest looks like? Ohoho~ ... So puny and immature compared to mine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="107">It is often said that a maiden's chest is pure and sizable, but yours strays far from that compared to mine.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="108">I doubt you get &lt;i&gt;any&lt;/i&gt; suitors with a pitiful chest like yours. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="109">There truly is &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; worthwhile about you now, is there, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="110">I suppose you deserve some respect, ~name~. I wouldn't have played strip poker if I had your chest size.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="7" priority="0">
                <condition filter="wealthy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't understand. Why haven't you bought yourself a less disappointing bosom?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="119">If you were pretty enough, those medium-sized breasts could have been worth something! Ohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="123">Mediocre breasts for a mediocre woman. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="148">It seems that we do have something in common, ~name~. We are both blessed with the perfect chest size, even if &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; didn't deserve it.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="149">&lt;i&gt;Hmph!&lt;/i&gt; You think your breasts measure in comparison to mine? Yours are saggy and deflated--mine are basically &lt;i&gt;perfect&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="150">Don't think you can compare your breasts to mine, ~name~. Mine are elegant, perky, soft, in other words, &lt;i&gt;perfect&lt;/i&gt;! Yours are just okay at best!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="151">Medium is too good for a lowborn such as yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="173">No need to be jealous of me, ~name~. Your chest size is perfectly fine... for someone as ordinary as you!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="174">Nothing noteworthy. The impact of you showing your bust to us will be forgotten in mere moments.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="111">Big lumps of fat, nothing more.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="112">Commoners do seem to prefer bigger for some reason... &lt;i&gt;bleh&lt;/i&gt;! They have no taste. </state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="113">Those look quite fitting... for a cow!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="114">Some say that having such absurdly large mammaries is a gift. I say, they make you look like you belong on a farm.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Look at them being all saggy, there is no grace to be found.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="115">Those seem like perfect stress balls after a hard day of being a princess.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="116" font-size="smaller">Your breasts are a harrowing reminder of a piece of fan art I received. I had double D breasts, black lipstick, and I was missing my donut hole. As you can imagine, my reaction to this vile abomination was nothing short of being justified, as I threw the creator of such vile art into the dungeon!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="117">Can you imagine? Having your own body hurt you by its size? Well, I can't. But I'm sure you do, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="118">Oh, I'm sure you have a lot of people that like you for your &lt;i&gt;personality&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-9" id="246">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1287">Nothing more than over-sized melons!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1308">Hope the back pain is worth it!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1309">My back hurts just looking at them. What use could they have being so gargantuan?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="337">
                <condition filter="flat_chest" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="2057">I'm a donut girl, so you must be a pancake girl! Ohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2131">Just keep telling yourself that "flat is justice". Or whatever peasants say to make themselves feel better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="247">
                <condition role="target" stage="1" />
                <condition count="1" status="chest_visible" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">You act as if you are nothing more than a common concubine. Please, have some dignity while in the presence of a princess.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="pubic_hair_peek" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I wonder if your crotch will be visible behind that curtain of unkempt hair! Ohohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition filter="slutty" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="247">Oh great, the local town bicycle is going to reveal her used vulva. &lt;i&gt;How joyous&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="92">Oh no, you have to show your mediocre snatch to the world. I am &lt;i&gt;certain&lt;/i&gt; people would want to see that.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="152">Let's just get to the point, ~name~. You aren't nearly attractive enough for people to stare at it for long.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="205">If I seem disinterested in seeing how your groin looks, ~name~. It's because I &lt;i&gt;am&lt;/i&gt; disinterested.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="207">You don't look like the type that would groom themselves down there, ~name~. So I doubt we will get something entertaining to look at.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="209">You don't have the necessary flare to make this exciting, ~name~. Let us get to the point -- where I will laugh at how insignificant you are!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="208">Why not get down on the ground and start masturbating right after revealing yourself, ~name~? That way you might have a &lt;i&gt;chance&lt;/i&gt; to impress me. </state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">We have all seen how perfectly crafted &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am, ~name~. Do you think you can compare? Or is it going to be unsightly like the rest of you?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="83">Not nearly as cute as mine, hmph.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="84">With your back against the wall, will you make a comeback and win it all? Or succumb before me?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="85">Were you hoping to get laid when you came here, ~name~? As you seem so desperate to show your womanhood off.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="86">I've never really looked at another woman's pubic area too closely.  The only one that is worth my gaze is my own.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="87">Mine looks better, no questions asked.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="88">I expected nothing more from a low-born like you.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="89">Hmph, decent at best. But none compare to my beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="91">Just surrender already, ~name~. Accept your fate!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" priority="0">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">...Barbaric.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I knew you had no decency the moment I laid my eyes upon you. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="217" priority="0">
                <condition filter="big_butt" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="991">Hmph! That explains a lot now, doesn't it? All that intelligence of yours must have come straight from your oversized derriere!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="992">Hmph! A lady such as yourself doesn't deserve a bakery like that!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="993">Your behind isn't as impressive as you think! Mine is better!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="994">Peasants aren't supposed to have a proper rear like that! They don't deserve it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-9" oneShotId="38">
                <condition filter="short" gender="male" role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="manlet">Who allowed this &lt;i&gt;manlet&lt;/i&gt; to play at the same table as me!? My, he isn't even tall enough to be a proper footstool!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="171">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart0a">You! With the blue hair and dull expression on her face. Your name was Aqua, correct?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="174">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart1a">Well, if you aren't a pirate, what else can you be? I've never met someone who acted and dressed like you before. Are you a hired sword? A bodyguard?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="177">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart2a">That is supposed to fight the darkness? It looks like an oversized key! It isn't even in a pretty color or anything!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="180">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart3a">Given you are still alive, I guess that you at least do your job correctly. Fighting the darkness, was it? What is it like? How does one &lt;i&gt;fight&lt;/i&gt; the darkness?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="183">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart4a">You know, you don't seem too happy about having to show off your own body. You might not look as good as I do, but you're not bad looking or anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="187">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart5a">See? That wasn't so bad now, was it? Getting to show yourself off with no regret or fear of what others say? It still pales compared to how I am, but you're learning.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="190">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart1a">As you have been so desperate to have people believe you're a goddess. Which I don't think you are. Why don't you come up with some proof for it? Clearly, a goddess must be more important than a princess, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="193">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart2a">If you think you're such an important person and a so-called &lt;i&gt;goddess&lt;/i&gt;. Why not prove it right now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="196">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart3a">Perhaps I have been too generous. Given your composure, behaviour, looks. There is simply no way you could be anything or anyone important. At best, you might be eye candy for some peasants.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="199">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart4a">So? What did that little trick end up doing for you? Clearly, a goddess wouldn't use her powers just to lose anyway, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="202">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart5a">Of course you lost again. Does anyone here expect anything different? I sure didn't. I bet you did it on purpose to try and get people's attention. It's pathetic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="218">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko0a">You... Yumeko... Was it? There is something off about you which I can't quite put my finger on. Explain yourself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="221">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko2a">Do not take me for a fool, Yumeko. People that make bets that can make them lose everything are the dumbest among even the peasants they are part of.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="222">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko1a">So? Are you going to tell me what you're up to? Or am I going to have to force you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="223">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko3a">Well, if I must believe you, you might as well answer this question of mine. What is the most you have ever won?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="224">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko4a">Given your crazy tendency to bet everything you have, why did you come to a strip poker club of all things? I don't often care about what commoners do in their free time, but you're an exception.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="234">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-sexy.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko5a">Don't lie to me. If there wasn't something special to gain, you wouldn't have come here &lt;i&gt;just&lt;/i&gt; for the possibility of meeting new people.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="319" oneShotId="68">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_1b" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_evil0">I might not understand why an utter buffoon like yourself would desire to be a magical girl, but what is with those clothes!? You look ridiculous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="367" oneShotId="73">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_2b" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_job0">Perhaps I should humor you a bit. Tell me, what do you do as a "magical girl" all day long?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="370" oneShotId="75">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_3b" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_reason">So, if you are as &lt;i&gt;important&lt;/i&gt; as you claim to be. How come you're currently here, humiliating yourself instead of &lt;i&gt;protecting&lt;/i&gt; the innocent people in that workplace of yours?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="373" oneShotId="79">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_4b" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_love">What you said earlier was a ridiculous notion. No-one here shows more love than me. A princess such as myself only has the most pure form of love there is. With that in mind, I should be getting those &lt;i&gt;love&lt;/i&gt; powers of yours!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="50">
                <condition role="target" character="petra" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Sweetheart_petra_talk0">You, girl with the purple hair that speaks weird... What was your name again? Peta? Pera? Petra?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="316" oneShotId="67">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH0">Pale white skin, bright blue hair, has a staff in hand, and is speaking about love and justice... Bleh. Magical girls are &lt;i&gt;sooooo&lt;/i&gt; out of fashion.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="64">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="443" marker="Shy">Ohohoho, something wrong, ~name~? Afraid of the big bad princess~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="444" marker="Shy">Don't be so shy before me, ~name~. You'll learn your place under me soon enough. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="445" marker="Shy">Don't worry about yourself so much, ~name~. With me here, nobody has any desire to look at you stripping! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="447" marker="Shy">I won't break you too badly once you're in my dungeon, ~name~. So no need to be shy, I'll be gentle. Ohohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="446" marker="Shy">Shy people are the best servants. They always do exactly what you want, like how ~name~ just lost because I wanted that to happen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="66" oneShotId="20">
                <condition filter="creepy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="503" marker="Creep">Ugh! Can someone remove ~name~ from this table? ~target.ifMale(He|She)~ is giving me the creeps.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="69" oneShotId="21">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1343" marker="aggressive">Hmph, didn't your mother ever teach you how to behave near a princess? Getting so aggressive about a loss is unnecessary.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="248">
                <condition filter="maid_uniform" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="1319">Perfect! Seems there is someone here that does understand their place in the hierarchy!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1320">Maid! Don't forget to dust off all the statues of myself in my personal garden! It is of most importance that you keep those sparkly clean!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-9" id="262">
                <condition role="target" character="okino" stage="5" sayingMarker="WIG" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">A wig!? What a let down.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="35">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh... My poor beautiful eyes! Why did you need such a light show? Just for you to dye your hair yellow? You look ridiculous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="37">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Cat_Noire_Reveal">Why do I suddenly have the feeling that I'm about to be disappointed?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="172">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart0b">You wouldn't happen to be some kind of space pirate, right? Working under the name of a loser called captain ex-spaceboyfriend?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="175">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart1b">​That would be splendid, I do so enjoy hearing some juicy secrets being told.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="178">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart2b">What use is fighting if you don't look good while doing it? I have my own weapon in the shape of a heart with a pretty pink color. Style is what matters.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="181">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart3b">Then perhaps you could deal with the eye-sore that has recently started to approach my land. A dark wicked creature that eats up my servants! Such dark creatures should not be allowed near me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="184">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart4b">Nervous? For what, others to judge you? It won't stop me. I can tell you this much, you should learn to love yourself instead. No need to hide yourself behind that mentality of yours. You commoners have a lot left to learn from me. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="188">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart5b">Well, obviously, I'm on another level. But a princess can give some other people the time to shine once in awhile. As long as they don't try to outshine me. You're the perfect candidate for it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="219">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko0b">No... No, that's not quite right. There is this unshakable aura around you. Something I've only ever seen by the most determined people, like myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="225">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko1b">A gambler, you say? Intriguing. Commoners tend to get addicted to those kinds of games and often lose everything because of it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="227">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko2b">One often comes with the other. When has someone who gambled ever been considered rational?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="230">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko3b">...I'm just going to assume that &lt;i&gt;yen&lt;/i&gt; is what you call shells. W-wait... twenty-four billion!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="232">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko4b">What? Do you consider having to show off your body to be a negative? Hmph, maybe if you aren't as beautiful as me, it might be a problem.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="235">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="sweetheart_yumek5b">If they are all like you, I don't want to meet them. Peasants are already bad, so I cannot imagine having to meet even more of them with a pathetic addiction to gambling.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="34">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades Out" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good riddance. Who would ever want to play this game with a drug addict? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="32" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" sayingMarker="COCK" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="COCK_Sweetheart1">Please hurry up, peasants. I doubt that what you two are about to show is going to be int-... Huh? W-what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="39">
                <condition role="target" character="kora" sayingMarker="blade_power" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">As if my ears didn't suffer enough from your obnoxious behavior, now you're going to blind me too? Had this been my castle, I would have thrown you into the dungeon the moment you spoke!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="191">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_GoddessProof_reply" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart1b">No, you look and act like someone who wants to be important. Something you obviously aren't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="194">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_ShowGoddess_reply1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart2b">What's wrong? Scared that everyone will realize that you're just a fraud?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="197">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_EyeCandy_reply1" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart3b">Why not just drop your panties and bra and show the world what you really are? An attention-seeking serf that has such a miserable life, she has to roleplay as someone important.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="200">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_BlessingTaunt_reply1" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart4b">But didn't you use that blessing of yours to get more luck? And you &lt;i&gt;still&lt;/i&gt; lost? How can you live with yourself?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="203">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_despicablePrincess_reply1" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart5b">I don't care if people don't like me, I care that they know their place, which is firmly beneath me. And soon you will understand that you're part of that group.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="317" oneShotId="69">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH1" font-size="small">Why, my royal guards, of course. I have an army of subjects that can snuff out any problem makers that enter my castle. So if, for example, a group of bad witches come inside my castle, they'll handle it. So what use does a magical girl have?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="320" oneShotId="70">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_2" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_evil1">That is preposterous, all my fans desire to look like me and wear my clothes all the time. I bet those agents you speak of only wear it to mock you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="368" oneShotId="76">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_3" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_job1">And when there are no villains to catch or stop? What do you do then? Just be lazy all day? It must be an easy life compared to that of a princess.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="371" oneShotId="78">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_4" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_reason1">Ugh, sisters. The idea that there are more people like you out there makes me feel nauseous. Do they know what kind of humiliating things you are doing here? Losing against the amazing Sweetheart and having to strip for her?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="374" oneShotId="80">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_5" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_love1" font-size="small">It is clear that you speak nothing but lies. I am love incarnate. There is no-one alive that will love themselves as much as I do! I will burn down entire kingdoms if it means that it satisfies my desires! I am the most devoted woman you will ever meet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="67" oneShotId="19">
                <condition filter="creepy" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Creep" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="513" marker="Creep1">No, seriously. Can't someone do something about this? A princess deserves better than having someone like ~name~ in my game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="70" oneShotId="18">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="aggressive" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="aggressive1">But if you just cannot control yourself, bark, bark like the mad dog you are. It will only help to prove my superiority.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-9" id="40">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">The only place that you belong to is a freakshow.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="41">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="2" sayingMarker="keyblade_reveal" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">So what? I can summon my weapon out of thin air as well. You aren't as special as you think.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="198">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" stage="3" saidMarker="Sweetheart_EyeCandy_reply1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart3c">Oh? You can produce sparkles? My, how quaint.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="36">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confident.png">Leave it to the &lt;i&gt;lowborn&lt;/i&gt; to make a big fuzz about something as silly as dying your hair. And it's the wrong color too! Everyone knows pink is the prettiest color of them all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="173">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart0c">Well, if that's the case. I'd suggest you upgrade your clothing style. Even someone with your figure can do better than what you have now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="176">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart1c">Keyblade? Fight the darkness? Those are words I've never ever heard someone utter. You must be playing me for a fo-... huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="179">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart2c">I guess that is just one of the many differences between a warrior and a princess. One has style while fighting, and the other doesn't.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="182">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart3c">My guards told me that it looked like an insect with many &lt;i&gt;many&lt;/i&gt; extra parts crawling all over the place. So if you could deal with that after having lost this game and showing off your body, that would be lovely.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="185">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart4c">It's much better to go all out with no regrets, than hiding yourself away in a corner, scared of the world.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="189">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart5c">Perfect. Keep that mentality for the future. I'm sure you'll find your own lover that will appreciate you for what you have. Be like me, and only accept the best of the best from yourself and others.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="220">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko0c">Hmph! No-one can fool the great sweetheart! I can smell something being afoot from miles away!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="226">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko1c">Bah! Why would they? Even if they hit the biggest jackpot they could get. It means nothing without the social status to back it up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="228">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko2c">I did hear some stories about people winning it all, but those stories are, at best, one in a million.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="231">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko3c">What kind of utter foolishness it would have been had you lost! You would have needed to sell both your soul and body just to survive!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="233">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko4c">Oh, I see what you're talking about. You are but a simple pervert, you came here to watch others touch themselves, do you not? Touching those oversized melons you got while you're at it? Disgusting!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="236">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="sweetheart_yumek5c">I am entertaining myself perfectly fine, Yumeko. I don't need some kind of silly addiction to enjoy my life.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="42">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" sayingMarker="planar_form" />
                <test expr="~target.persistent.strange_harmonies~" cmp="&gt;=" value="55" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Stop screaming you weirdo! Or did you just realize how ugly you are compared to me? If so, I understand. I wouldn't be able to stay calm either if I were you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="38">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" saidMarker="UnfinishedBusiness" sayingMarker="Polly Fades In" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">My disappointment is immeasurable, and my day is ruined.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="33" oneShotId="8">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="COCK_Sweetheart1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="COCK_Sweetheart2">Well, at least you two managed to be interesting. That is more than I can say about ~Player~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="192">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_GoddessProof_reply2" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart1c">Not doing a good job of explaining why you would be so important. Clearly, this is why being a princess is better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="195">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_ShowGoddess_reply2" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart2c">But if you're such a graceful goddess, I'm sure your powers wouldn't cause any problems, right? Seems to me that you're just making excuses.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="201">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_BlessingTaunt_reply2" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart4c">It doesn't matter what you think about me. How can I ever take a harlot like yourself seriously? You lie to yourself, you cheat in the game. And you still try to make me look bad while I'm leagues above you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="204">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_despicablePrincess_reply2" />
                <state img="#-graceful.png" marker="aqua_sweetheart5c">You cannot enrage me with your feeble words. No-one cares about your little tantrums, no-one cares about your delusions of being a goddess. The only type of people that would ever follow you are the ones that like your average body.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="318" oneShotId="71">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_1a" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH2">Ohohohoho! Me? A villain? My, how silly of you. A princess can't be evil. They are a shining example of the most pure-hearted people there are, something a silly little magical girl could never understand!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="321" oneShotId="72">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_2a" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_evil2">Well, it didn't protect you from losing this round, so who is the real idiot here? Don't answer that, it's you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="369" oneShotId="74">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_3a" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_job2">I rule my kingdom with an iron fist, which allows me to enjoy these off days in which I can do whatever I want. Seems to me like I'm having a much better time enjoying myself than you do. Ohohoho.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="372" oneShotId="77">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_4a" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_reason2" font-size="small">What kind of nonsense is this!? As if someone like you deserves to have a pretty pink heart surround her while stripping! Those kinds of things are meant for ladies of a much higher caliber than yours, like me! As I wouldn't disappoint everyone with tiny breasts!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="375" oneShotId="81">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_5a" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_love2" font-size="small">Of course they are evil! I am the embodiment of perfection and love! So whatever I do is always justified. It seems like those silly little powers of yours just don't understand just how important I am. If that's the case, I don't want it anymore! It is beneath me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="347">
                <condition filter="lingerie" gender="female" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2143">Hmph, I guess even a peasant makes a good fashion choice once in a blue moon.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="2144">Hmph, I hate to admit it. But you don't look &lt;i&gt;terrible&lt;/i&gt; wearing that, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="68" oneShotId="16">
                <condition filter="creepy" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Creep1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="593">Bah! Fine, I'll allow your vile presence near me, ~name~. But make one wrong move and you'll end up on the other side of my flail!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="71" oneShotId="17">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="aggressive1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png">​And once you're done barking, I'll put a leash on you and make sure that you won't ruin the rest of the match. I would prefer my win without a massive headache of someone complaining.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9" id="243" oneShotId="41">
                <condition filter="tandem_mm" role="target" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1284">So you decided to be sweet with each other instead of worshiping me!? I will remember this!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1285">They aren't even interested in me, so why should I stay here and look at what they are doing? It's nonsense!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1286">Watching you two losers touching each other is at least providing &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; entertainment, more than what I can say from my servants.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="240" oneShotId="39" priority="0">
                <condition filter="tandem" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="1218">Fitting for the two bums to start touching each other, knowing they would never get such a chance with me.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="1219">Ugh, can't they make a special rule that forbids people touching each other? I don't need to see these low-lifes touching themselves like this.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1220">What kind of brute would touch one another like this? Where is the finesse? If I'd let someone touch me like that, I would throw them into the dungeon post-haste!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="242" oneShotId="40" priority="0">
                <condition filter="tandem_mf" role="target" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="1246">I did not come here to watch two peasants get it on! Finish this debauchery quickly before I get mad!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1255">No king and queen action going on here. Just the jack busying themselves with a common whore.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="1256">&lt;i&gt;Great. I get to see the local town bicycle getting used, how fuuuuuuun.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="2766">Go ahead, pervert. Touch yourself for my amusement. Don't make it dull, or else I'll be &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; mad.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png" oneShotId="2772">To be better than everyone else is a joy that only I know.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="2773">Chop chop ~name~. I have plenty of humiliating things to say to you. Well, more than I already had.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2774">Oh, I'm going to &lt;i&gt;enjoy&lt;/i&gt; putting my feet firmly on your face. Get to it, loser.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="2792">Your only purpose is to entertain me, peasant. So stop with the idle chit-chat and give me what I desire!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="2791">Let's see if a futanari is entertaining to watch or not. It's important to know just how much I will need to punish you if you fail to live up to my expectations.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2821">Are you prepared for an endless amount of mockery?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2822">I do genuinely wonder how different a lady with a cock pleases themselves. Get to it at once, loser.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-9" id="56">
                <condition filter="small_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="328">Did you by any chance bring a magnifying glass, ~name~? Doubt we will get to see anything if you didn't.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="378">Even if I did want to watch you play with your little &lt;i&gt;thing&lt;/i&gt;. It's not like I could! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="399">Oh, I'm going to enjoy seeing you squirm as you desperately try to get yourself off.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="400">It should be considered an honor that you're allowed to touch yourself while I'm here. Even more so, given how small your member is. I would never have given you any attention if I had known that beforehand!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="67">It's only natural for the riff-raff to lie down before nobility such as I.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="68">You were barely entertaining while playing. I hope you're more &lt;i&gt;engaging&lt;/i&gt; while &lt;i&gt;performing&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="69">And just like that, the game is over for you, ~name~. The only thing that's left, is for you to put up a good show for me. Don't disappoint. </state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="70">Absolutely pathetic, ~name~. I cannot even entertain the idea that you've been anything else than soul-suckingly dull.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="73">Perfect. I was about to get bored before you lost, ~name~. Make it a good show, or else. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="71">​Just the person I wanted to see fail, good job pleasing your princess, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="72">This is the only time in which I'll accept failure around me! OHOHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="81">I demand to be entertained, ~name~. Don't keep me waiting.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="2858">Grovel, squirm, beg. Those are the things I want to see you do right now. Or else this pretty princess gets &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; mad.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="2859">Perhaps it isn't very princess-like to watch how others touch themselves for you. But as a princess, I can do what I want, and I will send anyone who doesn't agree with me to the dungeons. Ohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Be sure to grovel before me as you humiliate yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">No time to waste, ~name~! Your princess desires a show!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="2946">You put up a valiant effort, ~name~. But everything and everyone will end up beneath me! One way or another!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="2947">Be sure to squirm plenty as I laugh at your pitiful display!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2948">If you need any kind of convincing, ~name~. I can always just summon my royal whip and whack you till you do it!</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png" oneShotId="2949">Go on your hands and knees, ~name~. A princess such as myself shouldn't be standing all day. I deserve to sit on your back while you humiliate yourself beneath me, got it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="74">Chop-chop! ~Name~. You're humiliation cannot wait!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="76">No time to waste, ~name~! Your princess desires a show!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="75">Be sure to grovel before me as you humiliate yourself, ~name~!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="77">I don't want to hear any blether from you, ~name~. You lost, your opinion is invalid... Not that it has ever been valid! OHOHOHOHO!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="78">You put up a valiant effort, ~name~. But everything and everyone will end up beneath me! One way or another!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="79">For putting up such a &lt;i&gt;good&lt;/i&gt; fight, ~name~, I will bestow upon you, my heel grinding your member to dust! No need to thank me, I always look out for my sla-... I mean subjects.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="82">Yes, ~name~. You may look at me while doing your dirty deed, but if you even think about doing something with me with that obscene thing, there will be hell to pay. </state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="124">Don't enjoy this &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; much, you pervert. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="11" oneShotId="5" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">You didn't want to humiliate yourself? Too bad! Get to it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't blame yourself for losing, you never stood a chance anyway! OHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I look at you because I find your struggles amusing, ~name~. There is no other reason.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">The sight of seeing those beneath me struggle is something that will never get stale.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">You're going way too slow! Pick up the pace, peasant!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I'm not hearing you moan my name, ~name~. Try harder!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">You can still kiss my feet while you're doing this, ~name~. Don't keep me waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">Surrender your everything to me, and I do mean everything. And perhaps there is light at the end of the tunnel for you.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">You really aren't any different from an animal in heat, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, ~name~. Gaze upon my glory as you squirm around!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-amused.png">Don't blame yourself for losing, you never stood a chance anyway! OHOHOHO!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">I look at you because I find your struggles amusing, ~name~. There is no other reason.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">The sight of seeing those beneath me struggle is something that will never get stale.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">You really aren't any different from an animal in heat, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Me? Embarrassed? Nonsense! I quite enjoy seeing the riffraff humiliate themselves before me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Plenty of fans that would want me to look at them while doing such obscene things, ~name~. So be grateful that I'm even giving you the satisfaction of my gaze.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="168">Someone should put a leash on you, ~name~. It would be fitting for a barking dog like you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Could you be a little more quiet, ~name~? You're ruining the atmosphere.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Is that the best you can do? Oh, who am I kidding? Of course it is!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I do so enjoy the pitiful cries of a man that knows his place.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You lost on purpose, didn't you, ~name~? Given how much you seem to enjoy yourself. Though, I suppose no man can resist being near me for long before giving into their carnal desires.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">There is something strangely amusing seeing a man surrender himself to me like this.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">You try so hard... but it's still not good enough!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You are enjoying this humiliation too much for my taste.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Like an animal in heat, fitting for a dirty pig like you.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Just admit that this was your plan all along, ~name~. Rubbing yourself while looking at the one and only dazzling Sweetheart!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Go ahead, ~name~. Gaze upon my glory as you squirm around!</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">Surrender your everything to me, and I do mean everything. And perhaps there is light at the end of the tunnel for you.</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png" font-size="small">Doesn't it feel horrible? Having the perfect woman in front of you? Perhaps you feel a little inferior. Or perhaps enraged that you don't get to touch someone so perfect? Don't be shy; give me all your juicy details so I can throw those insecurities right back at you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="16" priority="0">
                <condition filter="small_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="175">I understand that beauty such as mine is a once in a lifetime occurrence. So I will allow you to look at me as you flail around with that little stick of yours.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="176">I'm surprised you could even find that puny little thing down there! Ohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="177">I would never take someone like ~name~ as my groom. He wouldn't know how to satisfy a princess like me with that tiny pecker of his.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="178">No microscope in the world big enough to see what's going on down there!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="179">You must have wanted me to put you in your place, ~name~. Why else would you play strip poker with such a microscopic penis? At least you already know that you're beneath me. </state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="180">I feel bad for anyone you would convince to share a bed with you, ~name~. They would pull your pants down only to be greeted with a tool that can't do its job! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="181">I've got an important question to ask you, ~name~. Did you ever need a toy to please your partner? Given that what you have between your legs could never please anyone but yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="182">You seem to be struggling, ~name~. Perhaps you should use some tweezers to help you out. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="17" priority="0">
                <condition filter="medium_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="186">Your princess desires to be entertained, ~name~. And given how mediocre your shaft is, I expect you to give it your all to compensate for it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="183">Come on, ~name~! Go faster! Compensate for that average prick of yours by going all out!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="185">If you do a good enough job with that boring knob of yours, you might even keep &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; of your pride after this. Well, as little pride as you had in the first place.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="190">Even your performance is average. Pick up the pace or something! You have royalty looking at you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">It seems you can't hold out for much longer, ~name~. Unsurprising, given you have someone as drop-dead gorgeous as me to look at. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I've never met someone quite as pitiful looking as you, ~name~. I love it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I bet that the only reason you're enjoying yourself so much is because of me. What else could be the reason? Your own skills? I highly doubt that~</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Finishing so soon? Who said you were allowed to do so?</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Nearly done already? But I'm not done mocking you yet! Hold it in until I say you can cum, or else there will be consequences!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <condition status="chest_visible" role="self" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="122">Remember what I said about avoiding "cream-filled" jokes? A "glazed" donut will not do either! Point that thing away from me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Nearing your limit already? Pathetic.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">I pity those that would be foolish enough to share a bed with you, ~name~. No-one wants someone that can't even last one minute.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Finishing so soon? Who said you were allowed to do so?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">If only you had someone to use that filthy rod on! </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Ah, nothing more amusing than seeing a lowborn grovel before me! Ohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Perhaps a muzzle would suit you. ~name~. Just think about it, you finally get to be the dog that you really are!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-amused.png">...What a pathetic look on your face. </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It seems you can't hold out for much longer, ~name~. Unsurprising, given you have someone as drop-dead gorgeous as me to look at. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="187">Don't point that ugly thing at me, ~name~. I am so far out of your league, even the idea of your filthy seed going near me makes me want to kick you between your legs.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Ugh. I hate how that &lt;i&gt;thing&lt;/i&gt; pulsates in your hand, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="188">Nearly done already? But I'm not done mocking you yet! Hold it in until I say you can cum, or else there will be consequences!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="futanari_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">​Ugh. Clean yourself, serf. You got it all over yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Hope you enjoyed your 15 minutes of fame, ~name~. Time for everyone's eyes to fall back on me!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I did get &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; meager enjoyment out of this. Which is more than what I expected from you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmph, I suppose your little performance wasn't &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; bad.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="51">​Ugh. Clean yourself, serf. You got it all over yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="52">Watch where you aim that thing!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="59">That's it? That's all you had? &lt;i&gt;Sigh&lt;/i&gt;. I guess it can't be helped. Common laborers like yourself have never managed to impress me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="58">If that's as long as you can last, you can kiss your love life goodbye! Ohohohoho!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="53">Tsk, and here I was enjoying myself watching you humiliate yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="54">Your pathetic squirms were delightful, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="55">Hey! Who said you were allowed to finish already!? </state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="56">I'm expecting a beautiful bouquet from you right after this game, ~name~. Why? ...Because you were allowed to look at my stunning figure while doing it! That's why!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-9" id="376" oneShotId="82">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_5b" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_win">Hohohohoho! All that talk about being a hero of love and justice amounted to nothing in the end, it seems. It is time for me to enjoy your little &lt;i&gt;show&lt;/i&gt;. Groveling before me and showing me why I am superior to you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="209">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" marker="Aqua_mustmast_winA1">OHOHOHOHOHOHO! Oh, it is a blessed day to see a noisy brat get put in her place! Touch yourself for my amusement! Be humiliated by your failures!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="210">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Aqua_mustmast_winB1">It seems there is &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; justice in this world. Seeing you lose has made my loss just a little bit better. Get to touching yourself, harlot.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="237" oneShotId="35">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko_lost1">Well? Did you enjoy your little &lt;i&gt;gamble&lt;/i&gt;? Seems to me you lost the bet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="169">I don't like sharing the spotlight, ~name~. So don't dilly-dally too much.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="170">Your best was never good enough to win from me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="171">Took you long enough! Don't you know it's rude to make a princess wait? </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="172">Ohohoho~ Are you prepared to be looked down upon and become ashamed of your actions? No? Too bad!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="243">We all have our place in the universe, ~name~. Yours is firmly underneath my feet!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="246">Finally! I've been waiting for you to start giving me a &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; show.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="254">Ohohoho~ This will be most entertaining. Seeing a low-born getting exactly what she deserves!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Remember! You are here to entertain me, so I don't accept slacking! </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7" id="211">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_SelfMustMast_replyA1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Aqua_mustmast_winA2">Stop diddle-daddling and get to touching yourself. I won fair and square and I want to start humiliating you now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9" id="212">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" saidMarker="Sweetheart_SelfMustMast_replyB1" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" marker="Aqua_mustmast_winB2">Nothing wrong with loving yourself, but everything &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; wrong with touching yourself all sad on the ground with nobody that cares for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="377">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" saidMarker="queenie_sweetheart_6" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Sweetheart_QOH_win1">It doesn't matter what you try to do after the game. Everyone will forever remember your humiliation! In the end, the princess beats the magical girl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="238" oneShotId="36">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="sweetheart_yumeko_lost2">Ohohoho! Now you will have to humiliate yourself for my own amu-... W-what!? What are you doing!? This isn't how it's supposed to go! Hmph! I've had enough of you and your antics!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="263">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Hmph, such power should be reserved for those who deserve it, like me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="350" oneShotId="62">
                <condition role="target" character="pinkie_pie" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="2157">...You put a balloon. In...&lt;i&gt;there&lt;/i&gt;. Sure, why not? Just put on some clown makeup and your little circus will be complete.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="2158">...How do I always end up having &lt;i&gt;weirdos&lt;/i&gt; around me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="239">Be sure to squirm plenty as I laugh at your pitiful display!</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" oneShotId="240">Be delighted, ~name~. You get to look at the most stunning woman in the entire &lt;i&gt;world&lt;/i&gt; while doing your dirty deed. You may now praise me for it. Come on, don't be shy!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="241">Perhaps I should make a film out of this moment. "Sweetheart Puts A Servant In Their Place". Sounds like a lovely title, doesn't it? I bet I'd be praised for my ingenious idea.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="242" font-size="smaller">Well now, this is the perfect moment to ask this. But do you have any kind of special skill, ~name~? As I am sure your measly little performance is going to be anything but entertaining, if you have any kind of hidden talents, now would be the perfect moment to display them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="244">Some of my... &lt;i&gt;weirder&lt;/i&gt; fans have expressed a desire for me to sit on their face. You wouldn't happen to be that much of a weirdo, right ~name~? Right?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="245">If you need any kind of convincing, ~name~. I can always just summon my royal whip and whack you till you do it!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="265">Go on your hands and knees, ~name~. A princess such as myself shouldn't be standing all day. I deserve to sit on your back while you humiliate yourself beneath me, got it?</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="272">You should feel honored being allowed to do such a dirty deed while I'm here. And yes, you are allowed to look at my perfect body. Why? So that you can imprint my superiority into that little brain of yours!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9" id="357" oneShotId="63">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" timeInStage="0" sayingMarker="ForfeitStart" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="2196">A mirror? My, that is... Quite the well thought out idea. Perhaps I might copy this idea.  </state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2197">Despite your utter lack of tactfulness towards me. I must say, rarely do I find someone who loves themselves as much as I love myself. And for that, you have my respect. How little it might be.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="213">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_konosuba" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="976">What a &lt;i&gt;goddess&lt;/i&gt; you are, touching yourself while everyone is watching. Have you no shame?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="977">A real goddess wouldn't have lost, now look at you. Nothing more than a common harlot!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="978">I thought you said you would never lose? Quite a different sight compared to what you said would happen.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="979">​OHOHOHOHO! Sweetheart always ends up on top!</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="980">Humiliation is the perfect punishment for someone claiming to be a goddess, thinking they are better than me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="986">That's what lying gets you, nothing but humiliation!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">​&lt;i&gt;Look at me! I am so important! I can summon a little bit of water! Praise me!&lt;/i&gt; And now you're touching yourself, funny how those things go.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Even if you did grovel beneath my feet, you are too far gone to get any of my mercy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9" id="239" oneShotId="37">
                <condition role="target" character="yumeko" />
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'm going to gladly forget this entire conversation we have been having, and pretend I don't know who you are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7" id="340">
                <condition filter="quiet" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="2099">Hey, ~name~! I want to properly enjoy my victory over you, but I can't do that if you don't moan like the loser you are!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hmph, how ungraceful. You don't know a single thing about loving yourself, do you? ~Name~?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Eyes up here, ~name~. If you're going to embarrass yourself, you might as well look at the prettiest woman of them all while you do it.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You're in the presence of greatness! ~Name~. You had better show your appreciation by looking at me when you are being so unsightly!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You're going way too slow! Pick up the pace, peasant!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Your moans are distracting me, ~name~. Put a plug into it or something. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Just because you're pleasuring yourself, doesn't mean you can stop praising me!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Failing to amuse me comes with a heavy price~</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Tick tock, tick tock. I don't have all day, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Name a better combination than ~name~ looking pathetic. They fit perfectly together!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't blame me for losing, ~name~. You should have played better if you didn't want to get humiliated.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I would step on you to show my dominance! But a pervert like you would probably like it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-smug2.png">If you're going to embarrass yourself like this, you might as well make that mouth of yours useful.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="48">Ugh. You're hopeless, ~name~. After we're done here, I'm taking you with me to my &lt;i&gt;special&lt;/i&gt; dungeon, so I can show you how to properly love yourself. No need to say thank you, I know I'm a kind woman.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">If you aren't moaning my name, ~name~. then just shut up and keep going. </state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">You can still kiss my feet while you're doing this, ~name~. Don't keep me waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Your humiliation is supposed to be amusing for me, ~name~. Stop being so boring and do a handstand or something!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" oneShotId="193">What an amateur, how are you supposed to bring yourself to a climax with such pitiful movements?</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Seeing you flail around like an idiot almost makes me want to pity you... &lt;i&gt;almost.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I'm not hearing you moan my name, ~name~. Try harder!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9" id="14" priority="0">
                <condition filter="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="130">I'm here in all my beauty, so I don't accept the excuse of it being difficult for you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-confident.png">I had hoped you would have been more... enjoyable while touching yourself. So you better not climax until I'm satisfied, got it?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Do I dare say it? That your face looks cute in a pathetic way? Well, it does.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Though you and your performance were hardly worth my time, you might just save yourself from an endless amount of ridicule if you end it well. So look me in the eyes and moan my name like the good little servant you are.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I know you want me, ~Name~. Everyone wants me, but no-one can have me. You will just have to finish knowing you will never be worthy of Sweetheart's love.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">I bet that the only reason you're enjoying yourself so much is because of me. What else could be the reason? Your own skills? I highly doubt that~</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I've never met someone quite as pitiful looking as you, ~name~. I love it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Almost done, huh? Tsk, leave it to someone like ~name~ to disappoint me until the very end.</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png">Though I am happy to see you following my advice to not bore me, nobody said you were allowed to climax! Keep it in until I say you can!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This better end with you moaning my name and having learned your place, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...Who said that you could climax already? I said you had to speed up, not that you were allowed to finish! That's for me to decide.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">I'll be sure to savor every single pathetic moment of yours, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You can look at me with those puppy eyes all you want, ~name~. I'm not going to touch you until you pledge your servitude to me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="61">Hmph, I suppose your little performance wasn't &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; bad.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="60">I did get &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; meager enjoyment out of this. Which is more than what I expected from you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="63">Clean yourself up, you look embarrassing like that.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="65">And now, whenever I look at you, I will only see that pitiful face of yours that is consumed by pleasure. OHOHOHO!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-9">
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="64">Hope you enjoyed your 15 minutes of fame, ~name~. Time for everyone's eyes to fall back on me!</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="66">You didn't moan my name when you finished, ~name~. Unacceptable! Do it again and do it properly!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="206">I knew you didn't have it in you to be captivating, ~name~. Such amateurish movements! Ohohohoho!</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="238">You look &lt;i&gt;way&lt;/i&gt; too happy about being humiliated, ~name~. How about you touch yourself down there again, and I will properly humiliate you this time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7" id="170">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png" marker="self_love">Surprised? How could I ever go out for a lovely summer day without my own bodypillow? You never know when my &lt;i&gt;needs&lt;/i&gt; start to flare up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png">...I should be mad at all of you for cheating... But I have something much more important to do... me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7" id="101">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_mustmast" />
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png" marker="Yumeko_end0">Hmph! Shut up, peasant! Luckily, I came prepared. People desire to see me lose all the time because I'm better than them. Sadly for them, I have just the thing with me to help me relieve some stress.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="205">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_mustMastA" />
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png" marker="Aqua_mustmastA">It's a bodypillow with me on it, numbskull. What else do you think it could be?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="206">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_mustMastB" />
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png" marker="Aqua_mustmastB">Hmph, I should be more mad that I lost. But for now, winning from that stupid water head is enough to satisfy my desire to win.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="399">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_8" />
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_lost">Silence! I don't want to hear a word! If I have to take this loss, I will do it the only way it should be done. By loving myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="168">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png" marker="self_love">Surprised? How could I ever go out for a lovely summer day without my own bodypillow? You never know when my &lt;i&gt;needs&lt;/i&gt; start to flare up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="65">
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png" marker="self_love">Hmph... Just remember that you all don't deserve what I'm about to show your feeble brains!</state>
                <state img="#-must_forfeit.png" marker="self_love">Hmph, fine. If I must get cheated out of my win, I'll at least make sure to enjoy myself in all my glory.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" id="102">
                <condition role="other" character="yumeko" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_startmast" />
                <state img="#-start_forfeit.png" marker="Yumeko_end1">Be silent! I desire some alone time without people like &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; ruining the mood!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="207">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_mustMastA2" />
                <state img="#-start_forfeit.png" marker="Aqua_mustmastA2">I got this custom made, you blabbering fool. Only Sweetheart could ever truly satisfy my desires.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="208">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_mustMastB2" />
                <state img="#-start_forfeit.png" marker="Aqua_mustmastB2">Yes, of course I am. Why wouldn't I? I'm not some kind of loser that would need to use their fingers for it, that's much too old-fashioned for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="400">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="sweetheart_queenie_8a" />
                <state img="#-start_forfeit.png" marker="QOH_Sweetheart_lost1">There is no love more pure then the love you feel for yourself, but I have wasted my precious time enough dealing with the trash the homeless wouldn't even want. Now it's time to focus on myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="169">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="sweetheart_sweet_summer_pastry" />
                <state img="#-start_forfeit.png">Nothing is better than spending time with myself after a hot day in the summer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-start_forfeit.png">Though I cannot stand the fact that I lost. At least I get to focus on myself now... And my body pillow with me on it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This is the only way I could ever get off! What else but an object with my &lt;i&gt;gorgeous&lt;/i&gt; body on it would suffice?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">This show I'm giving is worth &lt;i&gt;millions&lt;/i&gt; of clams! Something you plebeians don't even deserve!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">If you &lt;i&gt;beg&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;grovel&lt;/i&gt;, and offer your body and soul to me! Maybe I'll allow one of you to come closer.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Nngh... I feel &lt;i&gt;so&lt;/i&gt; good!</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I could look at myself forever~</state>
                <state img="#-sexy.png">&lt;i&gt;Mmn...&lt;/i&gt; If only I could kiss myself on the lips.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Everyone wishes to marry me, but none other than myself is worthy of it!</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="250">If only I had a mirror, that way I could enjoy myself even better! Such luscious moments need to be savored and relished!</state>
                <state img="#-graceful.png" oneShotId="249">I was always so blind, looking for love... &lt;i&gt;Hnng&lt;/i&gt;, If only I had realized sooner that I am my own biggest lover.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; you all desire me. And I understand, I &lt;i&gt;crave&lt;/i&gt; myself too.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Do you have any idea how &lt;i&gt;hard&lt;/i&gt; it is being a princess? No, of course you don't. Just understand that I &lt;i&gt;deserve&lt;/i&gt; this!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">There is no shame in a princess loving herself so &lt;i&gt;intensely&lt;/i&gt;! </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">​What was I even thinking, as if a clone could &lt;i&gt;ever&lt;/i&gt; make me feel &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt; good.</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Losing myself to my own pleasure... I could just drown in it forever and ever...</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">No-one is more perfect than me! &lt;i&gt;No-one!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">​Those... dumb sea-witches... They understood &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; about me. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Having the perfect body makes all of this feel so much better.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png" oneShotId="273">​Am I not a work of art, ~Player~? Don't answer that, I already know it's true~</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">It's a miracle that I could manage not to touch myself with how drop dead gorgeous I am.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There is no shame in worshiping someone who is better than you~</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Even the statues and paintings in my castle are &lt;i&gt;nothing&lt;/i&gt; compared to my ever-lasting beauty!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hng... not even that stupid &lt;i&gt;Perfectheart&lt;/i&gt; is as perfect as me!</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">Having this pillow made was easily my best idea ever~</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="277">It's unfair! Why do all of you get to look at someone as perfect as me, but all &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; get to look at is a bunch of peasants!?</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">For once, I don't think I mind the fact that I lost... even if you all cheated. Ohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Even those paintings that I have... Even those don't properly portray how desirable I am!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">Who needs a prince charming? When I myself am already princess charming~</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It just feels so much better when I can look at myself.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">And to think I was going to come here without my beloved pillow.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Hnngh~ It's no wonder everyone wants me. I do too~</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png">​None of you can have me, no matter how hard you beg for it.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">It's hard being so good at everything~</state>
                <state img="#-amused.png" oneShotId="1655">You know, this could have been any of you if you just submitted to me from the start. You wouldn't be as good as my own pillow so you'd have to do all the work. Ohohoho! As if any of you would be worthy of such a thing!</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png" oneShotId="1656">Getting dirty ideas, you commoners? I understand, I would also want to be below myself right now.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="1657">Is this turning you on? The idea of me riding you until dawn? Smothering you with my beloved thighs and making you sink deep within me? If only you knew your place from the very beginning, this could have been you. In your dreams, that is.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavy.png">Perfect... ah... I'm... perfect.</state>
                <state img="#-heavy4.png">Everyone here... they could only wish they were me!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I'm... The best!... The hottest! The most immaculate princess of them all!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">None of those clones... None of them could even come close to how &lt;i&gt;perfect&lt;/i&gt; I am!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">...I... want more...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy.png">Hah... I want this pleasure to last forever...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy4.png">Thousands of fans... screaming my name... desiring &lt;i&gt;me&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
                <state img="#-heavy4.png">No-one... no-one at all compares... I am the most lovely princess of them all!...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy3.png">Aah... Aaah~ The perfect spot~</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Only &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; could make myself feel sooooo good~</state>
                <state img="#-heavy.png">Hnngh... I don't want this to ever end...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finish.png">AH! YES! YES!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">I LOVE YOU, SWEETHEART!</state>
                <state img="#-finish.png">&lt;i&gt;SWEETHEART!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-after_finish.png">Aaah... Hah... I really am the best~</state>
                <state img="#-after_finish.png">That... Felt... &lt;i&gt;Perfect.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Ugh. I'm all sticky. I could really use a spa right now.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Those sprout moles better have cleaned all my statues as I ordered. They know what will happen if they don't do it.</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">How long are you peasants going to make me wait? I have plenty more things to do after this game, like spoiling myself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I should make my own rules for strip poker... ones that make it so that royalty can't ever lose.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Why does &lt;i&gt;he&lt;/i&gt; come up in my mind right now?</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="126">My garden needs to be taken care of daily, but those stupid sprout moles always complain about not being tall enough to do the hedges. Well, that's not &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; problem now, is it?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="127">I wonder if castella is done throwing out that worthless statue of my ex.</state>
                <state img="#-smug2.png">This might be the rarest sight of them all, every single one of you has to count yourself lucky to be able to see me bask in my afterglow. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">The real show is already over, all that remains are the leftovers.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Nothing else compares to the show I gave, so waiting till the others are done is quite uneventful.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">It is because I am such a humble princess that I will wait until the &lt;i&gt;trash&lt;/i&gt; is done. </state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">With the main show already over, why don't you peasants wrap this up so I can go home?</state>
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">Of course, if any of you dare start spreading rumors that the great Sweetheart attended a strip poker match, there won't be anything left of you once I'm done with you.</state>
                <state img="#-confident.png">Is there even a reason to keep going now that I'm done? Ohoho~</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmph, having to wait is frustrating. But at least I get to mock your inferior genes while doing so.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">​I wonder if my servants are done expanding my castle. I gave them eight hours for them, four more than I usually do, so it had better be done!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder what happened to the ever approaching dark clouds... At some point, they just vanished. Which is good because it was going to ruin my view.</state>
                <state img="#-booty.png">I haven't heard enough praise regarding my behind just yet. Go on, don't be shy.</state>
                <state img="#-booty.png">Don't forget, I am superior to all of you in every single way. </state>
                <state img="#-booty.png">Servants have only two goals in life. Doing my bidding and praising me. And I'm not hearing enough praise.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="13" priority="0">
                <test expr="~background~" value="inventory" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="125">What a horrible establishment! They don't even offer you a towel once you're out of the game!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-7" id="214">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" />
                <state img="#-cutesy.png" marker="Sweetheart_aqua_kono_win">OHOHOHOHO! There will be plenty of stories being told after this! The great Sweetheart puts some useless, smelly, ugly, wanna-be goddess in her place!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-cutesy.png">There was never a doubt that I would win. Just another victory for the perfect princess!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9" id="216">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_gameOver_SelfWin" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="Sweetheart_aqua_kono_loss">You think you'll get away with this!? You are lower than dirt, you're a filthy woman that deserves nothing more than eternal imprisonment! I will find you, and I will do the world a favor by getting rid of you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" id="215">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" sayingMarker="Sweetheart_gameOver_BothLoss2" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="Sweetheart_aqua_kono_end2">Why would they care about what someone like &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; has to say? Every single word you utter is nonsense! Leave this place and never come back!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="other" character="aqua_konosuba" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="Sweetheart_aqua_kono_end1">Tsk, though this defeat was unfair and unjust. It still brings me great pleasure knowing you're the &lt;i&gt;real&lt;/i&gt; loser here, "goddess".</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-despair.png">I will have my revenge! A princess never loses!</state>
                <state img="#-despair.png">I still can't believe I've lost. This won't be the last time you see me! That's a promise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9" hidden="1">
                <state img="#-amused.png" collectible="Sweetheart_photo">Unlocks the sweetheart photo collectible</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
