<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.9.2 at 4:41:38 p. m. on febrero 10, 2023. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.9.2</version>
    <first>Solar</first>
    <last>Flare</last>
    <label>Solar Flare</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>15</timer>
    <intelligence>good</intelligence>

    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="cheryl">Cherryl</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="bra" generic="underwear" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shorts" generic="shorts" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="socks" generic="socks" position="lower" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="lower" type="extra" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0" id="9">
                <condition filter="human_male" status="crotch_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">~Player~! I can see your... phallus! Isn't that very taboo in human culture? Isn't that why this game was fun to begin with?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">I think I'm a bit confused, ~player~... I thought this game was fun because you slowly removed clothes and defied established taboos. If you aren't wearing anything down there, what's the point?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="11">
                <condition filter="human_female" status="crotch_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">So that's your human "flower", ~player~... It's kinda neat! I was hoping to see it later on the game, but at least now I know what to expect!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Hey, I can see your human vagina, ~player~! It looks just like mine, but at the same time, it's totally different! That's neat!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="8">
                <condition gender="female" status="chest_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">Woah, ~player~! I can see all of your naked torso! I thought that was taboo, but here you are, defying expectations!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">You're not afraid of showing yourself a bit, ~player~? Good strategy! Leave them wanting to make you lose as fast as possible, challenge them to make you masturbate!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="10">
                <condition gender="male" status="chest_visible" role="other" character="human" />
                <state img="#-grin.png">So, ~player~, you're telling me men can walk around shirtless without any social repercussions? That's hot! Plants walk around naked anyway, perhaps I should follow your example.</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">Stop me if I'm mistaken, ~player~, but I thought the whole point of this game was to defy social norms by slowly taking off our clothing. If you're not wearing a shirt, doesn't that kinda defeat the purpose?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="day" />
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="outdoors" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png" marker="Best" set-intelligence="best">The sun's up, I'm getting all warmed up and filled with nutrients. Are you sure you can handle me at my best?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="Best" set-intelligence="best">If you were hoping on winning, you might wanna come back at night. The sun's up, and I'm about to go all out on you.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png" marker="Best" set-intelligence="best">They say only mad dogs and Englishmen go out in the midday sun. If it's because of my poker skills, it's true! I'm crazy good under this weather!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="night" />
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="outdoors" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Don't think that just because I'm a plant I can't fight at night. A superhero like me can protect you from zombies at any hour!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Your one-sunflower lawn defense is here, ready to defend you at day and night!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Did somebody call for a card game enthusiast, superpowered sunflower-turned-human to defend you from the zombie hordes? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="day" />
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" marker="Average" set-intelligence="average">We are literally where the sun doesn't shine... No natural oxygen, no direct sunlight, I might not be at the top of my game... but I'm definitely gonna try!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" marker="Average" set-intelligence="average">It's a beautiful day outside. Birds are singing, flowers are blooming... Wouldn't you rather play outside, ~player~? Where I can get some direct sunlight?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Average" set-intelligence="average">My powers work a lot better when I'm under the direct sunlight... I hope that won't affect my card skills...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="night" />
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" marker="Bad" dialogue-layer="over" set-intelligence="bad">Hey, ~player~, can't we play outside? I'm not really a "night" plant, or an "indoors" plant. I mean, if we can't, I'll still play! I'd just... prefer us to play somewhere else.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" marker="Bad" set-intelligence="bad">Okay... this isn't the first time I have to fight indoors and with no direct sunlight. I'm sure it can't be that bad, right? I'll just think of it as the dark ages...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Bad" set-intelligence="bad">I'm... really not in my element here. It's too dark outside, I can't get any fresh air, are you sure we can't at least play outside...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Solar Flare" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Solarflare" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Solar" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Destello" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Destellosolar" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~player~" value="Destello Solar" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-scared.png">... Wait a minute, your name is ~player~? That's my name! You can't steal it! Name yourself something else, you cheater!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A chance to check other human bodies and compare them to my own! I'm going where no plant has ever gone before!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Good ~background.time~, ~player~. Are you sure you wanna go against the one and only tomboy sunflower? You're in for a real match.</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Well, I'm pretty good at arcade poker and other card games, so I'll probably do well here! Solar Flare is reporting for duty!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Hey there, ~player~. Are you having a zombie problem you need me to take care of? Don't worry, let your big sis Solar Flare take care of it for you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <state img="#-grin.png">I'm a sucker for that long, green hair! And her pink girlfriend is pretty cute, too!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Doesn't having two people sharing the same hands break a rule or something...? Well, if everyone's alright with it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="4">
                <condition filter="undead" role="target" />
                <condition count="0" filter="zombieland_saga" role="target" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Is that an undead opponent I see? Well, ge ready. It’s gonna be bloom vs. doom like you’ve never seen it before.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="5">
                <condition filter="zombieland_saga" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worry.png" marker="ZLS_1">Why, hello you... regular human girl with a very specific faint aura of death?</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="ZLS_2">Ahh! A zom... wait, is that a regular human girl? Why does she feel like...? I... I must be imagining things...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuno_uno" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Finally... a worthy opponent.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="trixie" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">There's an Imp at the table! Let me kill it for you!&lt;br&gt;... What? I-It's not an imp? It's a... "goblin"?</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I see an Imp has made its way to the table. Don't worry, I'll burn it right away!&lt;br&gt;... What? What in the juglone is a "goblin"?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="3">
                <condition count="1-" filter="gamer" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">Those keen eyes... That eye-hand coordination... I sense that a gamer has entered the table. As a fellow enjoyer of the electronic arts, I'll make sure this game is worth ~target.ifMale(his|her)~ time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="pirate" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="classic_pirate" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Is that a... pirate!? Prepare for boarding! All hands on deck! Get me some kernel-pults! </state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Oh, drat... Pirates? Again? I'm gonna need some tacos, berry blasts and a good hero power to survive this...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Drat... I wasn't expecting pirate opponent. If only I had some spring beans, spikeweeds or coconut cannons to deal with them...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-grin.png">We could always use another player! Come on ~target~, join us!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm far more used to 1v1 games... But I'm always up for a new challenge!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">A new challenger approaches! Bring it on, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Join in! The more the berrier!&lt;br&gt;... No? Too &lt;i&gt;corn&lt;/i&gt;y? Well, thanks for the feedback anyway!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Come play with us, ~target~! We won't leaf you alone!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Another one joins the table! We don't need a controller for this game, all you need is some clothing and some human genitals!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">And ~target~ joins the table! Are you ready for an epic match of strip poker night at the ~background~? I know I am!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" filter="undead" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'm in danger!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Why do I get the feeling I got assigned to the wrong table...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">It's already weird for a plant to wear clothes, so I have no experience at all stripping out of them. But I'll do my best!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I'm pretty used to card games. Don't be too mad if you lose, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm not used to stripping clothes in front of other people. Plants are usually naked most of the time, but... I can give it a try.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Were you having a zombie problem? Don't worry, it's fine now! Why?&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Because I am here!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I know your type! Tall, dark, and looking for a real challenge! Look no further, I'm already here!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="2" totalRounds="0-1">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Ready? Set! GO!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Round 1. Fight!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Nobody blink, it's showtime!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Fighters ready... Engage!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Getting to mulligan my entire hand every turn  is so chaotic! I love it!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Are you sure I can't at least keep ~cards~ from my previous hand? No? Fine, then I'll take ~cards~ for this hand instead...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I've got a good feeling about this. ~Cards~ should be enough.</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Hey, I've won games with way worse starting hands! Just give me ~cards~ and I'll be golden!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Mmh... Yup! Just ~cards~ will do!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Now that's what I'm talking about! I'll take ~cards~!</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Is poker really that different from zombie-fighting...? I guess I'll take ~cards~ then...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="53">Ugh, I'm sick of seeing this card all the time. Begone...&lt;br&gt;... &lt;i&gt;ia!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Okay, so this is just like sun economy. I can do sun economy!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Just think of it like sun economy. You're good at sun economy. We can make it work...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I come from a place that's all about randomness and adapting to it, do you really think I'd need more than ~cards~?</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Give me those 4 cards already!&lt;br&gt;... I mean, 5 cards. I'll take my 5 cards. Sorry, force of habit.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I know I have to take 5 cards, but I'm feeling confident today. I could do with just 4, like I usually do.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I'm still not used to drawing 5 cards rather than 4, but that's what makes this interesting!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">I've got a good feeling about this! The same exact feeling I get when I have to choose my seeds!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-6" id="1" totalRounds="0-5">
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="pirate" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="classic_pirate" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="168">This hand should be enough. I'll survive any swashbuckler, monkey smuggler or barrel roller coming my way.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png" oneShotId="169">With cards like these, I could beat any quickdraw con men, pirate captain, seagull or parrot these pirates throw at me!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png" oneShotId="170">Who's got a green thumb, fire powers and a plan to survive pirate aggression? This plant right here.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="281">I'm gonna have to bring the heavy firepower to deal with this aggro onslaught...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="league_of_legends" role="other" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="353">Wait until my seeds take root!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="354">Just a harmless flower...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png" oneShotId="355">Wait until my seeds take root.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I wonder if I could get gems for winning this match...</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">No trick is gonna save you from this hand!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I shouldn't get cocky and overextend... If I play all my best cards at once I might end up losing a lot of tempo later...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">In the jungle, all plants have to compete for sunlight. And &lt;i&gt;nobody&lt;/i&gt; is gonna keep this sunflower in the dark.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Don't you know plants are huge into STEM? Prepare for some big brain plays incoming!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">This card game isn't even that hard! I'd say it's easy-&lt;i&gt;peas&lt;/i&gt;y!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png" oneShotId="50">Alright, that's what I'm talking about! Let's fry 'em up!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Say aloe to my little friend!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Bring your aggro strategies if you want, I'll heal through them! Better yet, I'll out-aggro them!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Oh yeah, I'm at the top of the world! Like a Cabbage-Pult on heights!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Call me gympie-gympie 'cause this is gonna sting!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png" oneShotId="154" weight="0.05">Get ready, you're gonna go out faster than Plants vs Zombies Adventures.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="217" dialogue-layer="over">While plants can have both male and female organs, I ended up as a biological woman when I came here. But I've always wondered what having a dick would feel like.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Where I come from, it's all about expecting, managing and adapting to randomness. Are you sure you can beat me?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">If I can survive egyptian pirate zombies from the far future in the dark ages, I can win this game with no problem at all!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Time to put the poker strategies a sentient time machine taught me to use! </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">One step closer to winning this and setting off to the sunset.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Hope you brought some sunscreen, because I'm about to drop a sunblast on you!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You might wanna put on some sunscreen, this play is gonna be burning hot!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Just imagine I have a Soul Patch on my Force Field and Dragonfruits on other lanes as well. That's how good this hand is.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="2-6">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="day" />
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="3">This is... okay. Though I assume I would've made better plays if I had access to direct sunlight...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="10">Okay, it's not as good as I expected, but for a game where I'm not getting direct sunlight, it's not that bad either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">I might just have enough tempo to make it to the next turn! I just gotta believe!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Talk about Shroom for Two! If only I had a Pineclone now...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I'll admit this isn't my hottest play... But it's warm enough to give me a fighting chance.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Hey, I've survived worse with less! Don't count me out yet!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Well... I can make this work. You just gotta adapt to it, like spider plants do...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I'm as resilient as a dandelion! Even if you beat me, I'll keep coming back!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png" oneShotId="24">The world might chew you up and poop you out, but you gotta keep true to yourself, be strong and resilient! Like a piece of corn!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Got a good feeling about this one! Not a great feeling, but still good enough!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I'm not used to gambling... &lt;i&gt;Buuuuut...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="114" font-size="smaller">I suppose zombies have a better chance at this game when starting out... Just like how new players can easily make cheap aggro zombie decks and plant players have to wait until they get all the good cards...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I could use some plant food to really turn this had from good into great, but... plant food is not as tasty when you're not a plant.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Just like how a Nepenthes ampullaria originally ate only bugs but then adapted to eat leaves as well, I'll adapt to this hand and survive.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'll just have to make do with this hand. Being a good card player is all about knowing how to adapt to RNG and predict your opponent's moves, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Not great, but... good enough. Kinda like a regular peashooter.&lt;br&gt;Don't tell Green Shadow I said that...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" oneShotId="159">I get asked this all the time, so let me be forward about it...&lt;br&gt;Yes, grass can talk, but they're not really up for conversation.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I've had Penny explain the rules of poker to me, but honestly, I just came here to look at attractive humans...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'll make this hand work. And if it doesn't, I'll make the next one work. The important thing is to keep going forward, no matter what!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Alright, this could go either way. Like a Seedling. Now I just gotta keep it alive...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="391">I enjoy my job, but fighting zombies... It changes you, bud. My friend Heartichoke was a real sweetheart, but fighting zombies... made her hard.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="2-6">
                <test expr="~background.location~" value="indoors" />
                <test expr="~background.time~" value="day" />
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" oneShotId="4">I miiiight have lost a bit of my power because we're playing indoors and I'm getting no sunlight at all...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="5">I hope next time we get to play somewhere with more direct exposure to the sun...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="6">Drat! I need to get some sunlight soon, this lack of light is making me do bad plays!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" id="2" totalRounds="0-5">
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="pirate" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition filter="classic_pirate" role="opp" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Drat. I was hoping for a better hand, but... this is gonna be rough...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Drat! I needed tempo, removal, heals, &lt;i&gt;something&lt;/i&gt; to survive a pirate attack! But this hand is just... unbeleafable!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grin.png">Not the greatest hand, but... The next one will be better. I'm a sunflower, I'm always headed towards a brighter tomorrow!</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" oneShotId="17">I wish I could use Flourish to get better cards, but... Green Shadow hasn't taught me that trick yet. </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="15">I could really use a Petal-Morphosis right now... But I never run it in any deck, so I wouldn't count on it anyway...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">B-but...! Drat, I almost had a good hand there! I want my card back!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Drat! Crashed and burned!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">... All I need is for someone else to have a worse hand than mine, right? Then I still have a chance.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="16">&lt;i&gt;(Psst, hey, cards. You're made out of vegetable fibers, I'm made out of vegetable fibers... Give a sister a hand, pretty please?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">... I guess I wasn't supposed to swap that card. &lt;i&gt;Oopsie daisy!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="109" font-size="small">So this is what it feels like to be new at a game and have no idea of where to start and what to do... Maybe I've been a bit too hard on the newbies...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Can't I use sparks to craft me some better cards...? No...?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I guess I can't conjure my way outta this one...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-6">
                <state img="#-angry.png">Drat!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Drat.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'm a better player than this! Come on SF, put the petal to the metal!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This hand... I'm not a one trick peony! I need to step it up!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Drat... Help me, Starch Lord!</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Drat... If life's a party, then to~background.time~ I'm the piñata...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">I'm used to being way better with RNG than this... I could easily predict my block meters just yesterday...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">There's gotta be more strategy than this to this game! It can't just be "swap cards and hope for the best!"</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I feel so useless right now... Like a Cabbage-Pult once we discovered time travel...&lt;br&gt;Don't tell them I said that, though.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Drat... This is exactly like those daily challenges that give you a gimmick bad deck against a consistent enemy deck!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I'm still not done! Even with this shitty hand, I can prevail! Against all odds, through the fire and the flames, I'll carry on!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Is it too late for a comeback?</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="379">I've got a really bad feeling about this... Like when your opponent sets up a Medulla Nebula, fills his side with little zombies and starts playing Brain Vendors...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-6" id="3">
                <condition role="other" character="9s" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png" oneShotId="25" marker="9SZombieRobotDisguise">These zombie robots sure are getting more convincing, but none of them are getting past me! </state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="26" marker="9SPod153">Be careful of that Pod-153 or whatever its name is, ~player~. It looks oddly similar to the drones of zombot drone engineers...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png" oneShotId="27" marker="9SAggro">The best way to deal with these zombie robots is to not give them any time to buffer their combat data! Go full aggro from turn 1!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="21">
                <condition role="opp" character="cheryl" />
                <state img="#-worry.png" marker="CherylCherry">I heard that a "Cherry" girl who also fought zombies would be present today... She doesn't look like a cherry to me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" totalRounds="20-">
                <condition count="1-" status="not_crotch_visible" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="87">I'm on a roll today! If I were using Mega-Grow strategies, this would be like playing all my Clique Peas on curve!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png" oneShotId="460">Do I have a Soul Patch on a Force Field or what? I'm unstoppable this game!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png" oneShotId="500">Looks like I'm pretty good at this card game as well! Look at me, I haven't even taken off my shirt yet!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="32">&lt;i&gt;And you'll be left in the dust, unless I stuck by ya...&lt;/i&gt; ♪</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="66">&lt;i&gt;Invite us for some gingivitis...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Halitosis that is your prognosis...&lt;/i&gt; ♪</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="67">&lt;i&gt;Come on down to Neighborville, come on down to Neighborville&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Love it here and we know you will&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;Come down to Neighborville!&lt;/i&gt; ♪</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="68">&lt;i&gt;Today is your birthday, today is your birthday!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;It is the day when you were...Booooorn!&lt;/i&gt; ♪</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="69">&lt;i&gt;Bashing through the snow, in a Snow Pea-powered sleigh...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;O´er the lawn we go, tossing snowballs all the way...&lt;/i&gt; ♪</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="306">&lt;i&gt;I wanna take you for a ride&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;I wanna take you for a ride...&lt;/i&gt; ♪</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="12">
                <state img="#-competitive.png">You can call me Solar Flare, SF, Solar, Sunny, Sol, Sully, Destello, or any way you want.&lt;br&gt;But I'm a hero, so whatever you call me, if you call me, I'll be there to save ya.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Call me anything you want: Solar Flare, SF, Solar, Sunny, Sol, Sully, Destello...&lt;br&gt;But I'm a hero through and through, so if you call me, I'll come to save you!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="5-" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">You know what? I don't give a ffffff-... fig. I'm all out of figs. Does it look like figs grow on trees? Because they don't. I'm all out of them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="4-" />
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">You're all pretty good at this game, huh? Perhaps you'd consider stop playing so much and go touch grass... Literally.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-worry.png">Huh, twice in a row? That's... That's some bad RNG right there.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Again? But I just lost! Drat, I really need to rethink my strategies!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Aaand... it's me again. I guess I'm not as good as I thought...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Okay, this stopped being funny. I need to focus, &lt;i&gt;now.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Now I'm just mad. Burning hot and mad.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="7" totalRounds="5-">
                <state img="#-worry.png">Drat, there goes my winning streak...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-wink.png">Well, if you can’t beet ‘em... join ‘em!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">My turn! Let me show you what I can bring to the table!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Try not to catch on fire, okay? I know I can make things get real hot sometimes.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">You've got spunk, I'll give you that. But it's time for me to show you how it's done.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Alright. Let the sunflower brighten up your day, won't ya?</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">You've got some tricks, sure, but I've got a whole lot of surprises myself! Don't count me out just yet!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Okay, sure, that wasn't a good pick. But I still have more clothes than you! I'm at the top of my game!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Seems like I got the short end of the stick... But I'm still the flower of the flock! So nothing to worry about!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Just a bit of bad luck, I can come back from this!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Oh, drat. Well... I guess I'll be the one to go.</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Couldn't block that one, but hey, I'm still not done! I can still take another hit!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Drat.&lt;br&gt;Oh well... At least I'm doing better than someone else at the table...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I thought I calculated that one better... I'm not mad at you, I'm mad at myself.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Drat. Well, it was bound to happen, you know? Why would I come to a strip poker game if I wasn't prepared to strip?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I was hoping to be able to conjure a solution to get me out of that hand, but nope.</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">This play blew up in my face like an exploding fruitcake... And I {b}hate{!reset} exploding fruitcakes.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-angry.png">RNG is straight up messing with me to~background.time~...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Double drat!</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Aw. I was hoping someone else would have an even worse hand...</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">What kind of tricks are you using? Oh this is just bull...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Come on! I was pretty close! Give me another chance!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">Are you really so desperate to see me naked? What a tryhard...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Are all of you vegan or something? Because you're eating me alive here!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png" oneShotId="332">I shouldn't have changed that card... I feel as dumb as when I bought the Mayflower pack thinking it was a good deal...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Alright, just... let me take a moment to... ah, prick me. I'll just leave the shoelaces tied.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">Just give me a moment to untie these... I'll just... On second thought, I'll just take them off like this.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">No problemo! I'll just take these off with... Maybe I can... Nope, we're taking them off with the shoelaces tied.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">I never got why humans wore soft clothes under their hard clothes... until I got into this body. Humans sweat a lot!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I don't really mind taking off these. After getting this body, I finally got why humans liked walking on grass barefoot. It's a real funny feeling!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It was a shocker to learn that humans got turned into zombies when they got bitten! No wonder why they wear so many clothes, it protects them from bites!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">While nothing beats the nudity of being a plant, these shorts are pretty close! They're comfy and easy to wear!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">Okay, just... give me a second... fiddling with buttons is one of the worst part of having fingers...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I'm still not used to having to use these... fingers to unbutton stuff. When you're a plant you don't have to deal with these kinds of problems!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">If only I could just get a vine to unbutton these... No? Maybe I can burn them off...? No, Dave would get mad at me again...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You've been waiting for this, didn't you? For some reason, a lot of people wanna see what's under my shirt. Even when I was in my plant body.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">I don't get why people are so desperate for me to take off my shirt... Even when I had the other body, people always kept asking about it...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Seeing something you like, ~player~? Zombie fighting makes for a great workout routine, especially on your abs.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">... Why are you looking at me like that, ~player~? Yeah, I got abs. You've got them too, you know?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well, I could take off the bra, but... nah. I'm a proud member of the League of Extraordinary Action Foliage. If I can wear its symbol for a bit longer, I'll do it.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">I'm not taking off the bra yet. I'm a proud member of the League of Extraordinary Action Foliage! I'll keep it for as long as I can.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" dialogue-layer="over">You weren't hoping to see my human mammary sacks or whatever you wanna call them, were you? Because I'm keeping the bra for a bit longer. I'm quite fond of the L.E.A.F. symbol.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well, you got an agent of L.E.A.F. to take off her bra, hope you're proud of yourself...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">Fine... I'll take the bra off, I hope you're happy...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">It's not like you're gonna see anything mindblowing, you know... It's just human udders, you've all seen one at least once in your life...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm not used to tying and untying stuff, all this "clothing" stuff is pretty much new to me...&lt;br&gt;... Besides my t-shirt, of course...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I never had to wear shoes before, so I'm still new to all this. If we wanted to tie something up, we'd probably just use our vines to hold it tightly...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I'm not good with all the knots you gotta make with these human shoes... I tried some slip-on shoes before, but they kept slipping up, so...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-grin.png">How are my roots.. I mean, feet, ~player~? Not bad, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">While walking barefoot on grass is a pleasant feeling, I can get why humans don't do it that much. You get your feet all dirty and smelly, and cleaning them is such a drag...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I tried avoiding shoes for the most part when I got this body, but... stepping on little rocks, bones and thorns makes you realize how fragile humans really are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripped.png">I usually skip leg day. When you're a plant, you don't really need to exercise your legs.</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">I don't need to exercise my legs! I'm sure that when I come back to Zomburbia, I'll be a plant again!</state>
                <state img="#-stripped.png">Having legs instead of roots or walking leaves feels a bit weird, but I'm getting used to them. I just hope my training routine doesn't include a leg day now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I liked the color scheme I was going for with the shirt and the shorts, so... why not keep it the same for the underwear?</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Want a body like mine? Drink a lot of water and do some exercise under the sun, like fighting zombies to defend your loved ones!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">What's wrong, ~player~? Surprised by my bra and panties matching with my shirt and shorts? It's almost like I didn't strip anything at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Some people have said I'm supposed to have hair down there... I don't really know myself, but it hasn't grown so far. Plant-to-human anatomy is kinda weird.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">You might have taken that off of me, but you're not taking the bra. I'm an agent through and through, and I'll wear the symbol to the end.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">What's with that face, ~player~? Were you expecting a plant to have a bit more of a bush?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-grin.png">Alright, so that's it! No more block metrers, no more lawnmowers, one more hit and I'm out!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">The goggles stay on, so this is it. No more lawnmowers, no more block meters, another direct hit and I'm out. Bring it.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Hellboy">I can't really take off these leaves... and I like my goggles. They remind me of my favorite comic book hero, Hellboy. So I'm not taking those out either...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I kind of... need my goggles if I need to use my powers, so those are staying on. And I really don't know how to take off these leaves on my wrists, so... I'm all out?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="leon" />
                <state img="#-wink.png" oneShotId="529" marker="LeonPun">Can survive in any environment, really good at killing zombies, consumes a lot of other weeds... If you were plant, you'd be a great dandeLeon!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="528" marker="LeonZombies">Word around is that you're pretty good at killing zombies, Leon... We could use your skills at Suburbia...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This is gonna be so hot!  </state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">I'm not sure I get the point of wearing clothes to strip them anyway, but I'm willing to get it eventually!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're up, ~target~! It's your thyme to shine on the sunlight!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I haven't seen many human males other than Dave and Nate, so this'll be a nice change of pace...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I'm sure you're very sexy by human standards, ~target~... I'll do my best to cheer you on!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This is actually pretty exciting! Who knew the best part of wearing clothes was taking them off for other people?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I don't quite get the appeal of humanoids yet, but that's what I'm here for! Show me what you've got!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I'm used to beating Dave and Nate all the time at card games. This was only natural.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">You're dealing with L.E.A.F.'s finest over here. You need to step up your game.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Humans are fascinating! I can't wait to see </state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'm not sure what to expect, but that's what makes it interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Don't go disappearing on us, okay? I know a certain... fun guy who'd usually do that when he's embarrassed.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Let me give you some advice, have you tried winning? Perhaps that'd work for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Make it a good one for your gal Solar Flare, please?</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">You know, I think I'm getting the whole appeal of the human male figure. Show me more!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I'm not saying I'm into humans now... But I'm not &lt;i&gt;opposed&lt;/i&gt; to seeing more of you...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Hey, I'm already touching myself, sooo... could you hurry it up?</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Oh, here comes the really raunchy part!&lt;br&gt;... At least I hope so!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I'm learning so much about human sexuality and my own sexuality to~background.time~! Keep it up, ~target~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="wikipe-tan" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="463" marker="WikipetanQuestion">Can I really ask you any question I want? Any question? And you'd have the answer? Is that true?</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png" oneShotId="462" marker="WikipetanTOW" dialogue-layer="over">We have a Tree that knows a lot of stuff back where I come from! Perhaps you and him could have a long chat about... stuff nerds like you talk about!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="cheryl" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png" oneShotId="476" marker="CherrylZombies">I heard you were pretty good at smacking zombies. Is that true, Cherryl? Because I'm pretty good myself, and I'm looking for a match.</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="477" marker="CherrylHorrors">... Something in your eyes tell me you've fought way worse things than just zombies, Cherryl...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="aaravi" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="556" marker="AaraviMonsterHunter">I just realized... We're playing with an actual monster hunter! Someone who takes the fight to the monsters themselves! I need to pay attention to this woman!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png" oneShotId="557" marker="AaraviMonsters">I have to deal with the occasional monster every now and then, mostly zombies. So having the chance to play with a fellow monster fighter is pretty fire!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="zoe" />
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="564" marker="ZoeAlienOoze">... This girl's entire face reminds me of that annoying alien ooze that always gets me when I'm on heights...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="565" marker="ZoeBody">I've never faced this kind of monster before... It's like she had an octopus for a face, and had... a lot more things on the rest of her body...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="polly" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png" oneShotId="568" marker="PollyCategories">A partying ghost? Pfft, these zombie categories are getting ridiculous. I'll just burn her anyway like I'd do with any other zombie.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="569" marker="PollyFun">She's a lot more lively than most other zombie-adjacent monsters I've fought... Perhaps going against her willl be fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="panty" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <condition role="opp" character="stocking" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="574" marker="AngelZombie">Hey! Aren't you one of those overseas angels that defeated a whole lot of zombies, got turned into zombies but managed to heal it off?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Bloom and doom!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">So it's ~name~, huh... That's pretty neat...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Is ~name~ supposed to be attractive? I don't really know, but I do like that she has the guts to come here...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Composted!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">You gotta strip now, that's how the game goes! If you don't like it, you can always make your own game, like the guys from Eclise did!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Well... You kinda knew what you were signing up for...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Sorry, ~target~. I've got years of experience with card games, this is a walk through a rose garden for me.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I hope there's no hard feelings, ~target~. I'm just that good, and this round you were... not.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">That's how it goes with RNG, ~target~. Sometimes you get exactly what you need, and sometimes... you don't!</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="174">Don't get too mad at me, ~target~... That's just how the game is supposed to be played, you know.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Surely you wanted to strip for us, ~target~? What other reason would you have to come to a strip poker game?</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Your block meter just wasn't working in your favor to~background.time~, ~target~. Don't worry, it happens to all of us!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Don't let this loss get to you, ~target~! Time to turn on a new leaf, and what better way to start it than showing yourself off in a strip poker game!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You weren't hoping to beat the cream of the crop, were you?</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Your garden still has some lawnmowers left, ~target~!&lt;br&gt;... Which is a fancy way to say "you're still not defeated yet, keep going" where I come from.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I can get through your plays like a laser bean. You had no chance this round.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I'm a sunflower superhero that can burst into flames and command vast plant armies to repel zombie hordes, you'll have to do better than that!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Did someone play Brainana against you and made you lose your brain? That was a terrible play!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">This lawn is mine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-wink.png">You gotta give me something to look at, don't you? Make it something good!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">You put up a pretty good game, ~target~, but if even I can lose this game, then anyone can!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I hope I'm not too distracting, ~target~. I'd hate to be the reason you lost...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You didn't lose on purpose to join me, ~target~? I wouldn't blame you, this is pretty fun.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Soon you'll be here with me, ~target~! I'm rooting for ya!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Are you sure you're not missing the forest for the trees, ~target~? It's not about getting the best hand, it's about not getting the worst one...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-worry.png">How do ties exactly work here? Where I come from, a tie just means the zombies have the advantage...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Not a tie! There's no "tie" against the zombies, you either win or you lose!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">So... What happens here? Does no one strip now? Do we all strip, or...?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grin.png">That's one less piece of clothing for you! It might not look like much, but it's one step closer to your defeat!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Back where I come from, there's at least three chances for you to block the hits coming your way... So I'm grateful for every little victory I can get.</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I'm glad there's no super-block meter in this game...</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Take as much thyme as you need, ~name~. Everyone should learn to take it easy, to stop and smell the roses.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Accessorize all you want, ~target~! Everyone should wear whatever they want if it makes them feel good about themselves!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Not too much to go off for me, but you go...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">That's not really a sexy thing to take off... Or is it? I'm not really used to what humanoids find attractive...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Just like my goggles, you could've kept that on, don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Well, a loss is a loss, and that gets me off!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I'll just think of literally anything else in the meantime...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grin.png">You're doing good lad! Keep it up!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">And the game continues! Another round!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I was kind of expecting something bigger, but I guess I'll have to wait a bit more...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Now that that's outta the way, let's keep it going! I wanna see the end of this.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">You don't look half-bad without your ~clothing~, ~target~. I guess this wasn't a big loss for you.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Don't worry, ~target~. No one will steal your things while you're here. I'll make sure of it.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Your accessories are safe from zombies, ~target~. That's what I'm here for.</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Take your time! I'm used to having to wait in the middle of my games... Mostly because of intrusive ads...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I'll keep trying my best to masturbate, but you'll have to do better than that, alright?</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I've got my steamy fantasies to keep me going, so you can be as boring as you want!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Keep making those boring strips all you want. I'm a plant, I know one thing or two about being self-sufficient.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Don't feel pressured to strip more than what you want to, alright? I want you to feel safe and valid here, and if boring stripping is what it takes for it, so be it!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">A hero doesn't push others to do things they're not comfortable with like stripping in front of strangers, so I'm okay with you stalling like a coward!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="aaravi" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" marker="AaraviStrip1">Us plants can't really wear cloaks... I mean, I suppose we could, but we'd be losing out on some precious sunlight...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="AaraviStrip2">For a half-monster, she doesn't really look like a threat to humankind... She actually seems kinda nice, like an Atomic Bombegranate...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="6">
                <condition role="target" character="akko" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="AkkoStrip1">Holy copyright infringement!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png" marker="AkkoStrip2">Wait, can she do that? Is that allowed? Is that legally allowed?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="20">
                <condition role="target" character="queenie" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smile.png" marker="QueenieStaffStrip1">I know a certain Rose with a magical stick like that one. I'm pretty fond of her...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="QueenieStaffStrip2">A magical staff? One of my fellow agents uses a magical wand to turn zombies into goats. And even still I'm better than her.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="QueenieStaffStrip3">One of my friends uses a magical wand, but other than that, I've only seen magical staves used by wizard zombies...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-whistling.png">And here I thought classifying different types of asteraceae was boring...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="2" dialogue-layer="over">I hope your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(aren't|isn't)~ necessary for your survival, ~target~... Some people think a flower's petals are like clothes, and rip them out to see us "naked." </state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">You go on ahead, I'll just... keep humming to the beat.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'll just patiently wait until you finish taking off your ~clothing~. No need to hurry. It's not like we're under attack of zombies or anything.</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I get it! Sometimes you really have to take your time. Plant your sunflowers one at a time, maybe stall with a potato mine or two.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I wonder how our Zen Garden is doing...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">You don't really need your ~clothing~ for protection, right? Where I come from, just a bucket or a pot on your head can protect you from harm...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I really dig your ~clothing~! I'd wear ~clothing.ifPlural(some|one)~ myself if I knew how to get more clothes than these...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">All humans should accessorize! You never know when you might get bitten by a zombie and will have to wear those clothes for the rest of your afterlife...</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I get why humans wear so much clothing all the time. You only get one brain, you gotta put as many clothes between you and the zombies to protect it.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png" dialogue-layer="over">Other plants used to make fun of me for wearing this shirt. Now I see you wearing your ~clothing~ so freely, it reminds me that you should wear whatever makes you happy!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Take all the time that you need. I'm used to waiting in the middle of my games... mostly because of ads...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">You're a natural at this game, ~target~! But don't get too comfortable!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're a really good player, ~target~! I've already lost but you're still kicking like a pro!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Next time, I'll be the one stalling with trinkets like your ~clothing~ while you'll be the one touching herself!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">One step closer to falling to my level, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">We can wait for you, ~target~. You'll either join the losers' side or go home to relief yourself in private, anyway.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">So... do we keep the game going now?</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Wearing a lot of useless trinkets is what fashion is all about, right? I like it! Like a cuscuta, it's growing on me!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">You grow, girl! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Come join us, ~target~! I swear, this is a lot of fun!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">This isn't so bad, ~target~. Don't be too much of a tryhard, will ya?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Don't tell me you're afraid of joining me, ~target~. Trust me, it feels a lot better than it looks.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You gotta let loose, ~target~! This feels amazing, you really gotta try it out!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Come on, ~target~! Lose some more clothes! What's the point of a strip poker game if you don't stirp after losing at poker? This makes the whole game fun!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Does your ~clothing~ add some kind of stats that benefit you?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's a shame this isn't like a videogame... Like you could pick up clothes from boxes on the street like picking up food to restore your HP.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">We got a breaking weather report! An intense heat is coming to the ~background~ after ~target~ took off his ~clothing~!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">~Target~'s so hot, that if I brought him to the Frostbite Caves and kept him close, I wouldn't get frozen!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Remove your layers like an onion, and we'll get to the spicy center.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-worry.png">You don't happen to carry some sunscreen, do you? The sun can be pretty bad for your skin if you aren't careful about it...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I won't let anyone steal your clothes or take advantage of your nudity, ~target~. So you can keep playing without fear!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Tree of Wisdom gave me a tip that I should share with you: If you want to be good at this game, you have to get good at this game.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Have you considered trying not to lose instead of trying to win? Try it, it's gonna change your life!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I know RNG is kind of a bummer,</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">Are you looking at ~target~, ~player~? You find her attractive, don't you? Isn't that why you invited her to play?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Seems like it's time to turnip the heat, because ~target~ is setting the whole ~background~ on fire!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Oh, so you use your ~clothing~ for... clothing purposes. Right. So it's like that, huh? I totally get it. I understand everything now.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I wonder how I'd look in your ~clothing~! I wanna try putting on ~clothing.ifPlural(some|one)~ like ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ myself someday!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Don't be afraid of the cold, ~target~. I'll warm you up if it gets too chilly.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">I've beaten zombies wearing ~clothing~ like yours! But you're rocking that style way better than them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You were all dressed up like a Christmas tree, ~target~. But what we really wanna see is the magic under all those trinkets.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I'm sure I wouldn't take that long to take off my ~clothing~...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Next time, remind me to wear ~clothing.ifPlural(some|a)~ ~clothing~ like yours. Perhaps that way I'll last longer in the game!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You were looking pretty good with your ~clothing~ on, ~target~. But I'm more interested in seeing you out of ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ now...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I feel like I'm at a runway! So many styles, colors and ways to express yourself through your clothes!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Don't tell me you're afraid of being a little exposed, hm? Plants are naked all the time.</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Don't be afraid of being exposed, I'm here to protect you! I won't let any zombie get to your brain!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Just like those who call me Destello would say, you're &lt;i&gt;muy caliente!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I'm truly grateful to be able to play this game with you, ~target~. Not many people would trust a stranger to see them naked.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">You got this, ~target~! You're not out of the game yet!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">You don't mind getting a tan, do you? The sun can get pretty hot when I'm around...</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">I've got a tip straight from the Tree of Wisdom! Next time, try not to lose.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">We'll be seeing parts of ~target~ that no one has seen before! I'm all heated up for it!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">So you're really gonna show us a place where the sun doesn't shine, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Humanoid anatomy is so fascinating...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">The game is getting intense! Let's keep it going!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Things are heating up, and I wanna see where this takes us!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Make the most out of your time in the sun, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I've been waiting all game to see you like this, ~target~. I'll make sure to take some notes~</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">This is very educational! As a plant, I never had to deal with social taboos about clothing, so this is gonna be great for me to understand humans better!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Do... all humanoid women wear things like these? I wonder if Penny would like to wear something like this if she was human...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">... Patrice never told me about this part... I'll just pretend that I know what's it all about and move along...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Oh my gourd... You look radishing... I-I mean, ravishing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-grin.png">Heheh... I can see all of ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">~Target~ is actually kinda entertaining to watch... In a good way!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Maybe the human form is not so bad after all...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Plants don't really have "chests", we just have stems, so... I kinda wanna see what all the fuss is about.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">You lost fair and square, ~target~. Now you gotta show us the goods.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">My heart </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Show me all you've got, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I... I have to admit I'm pretty interested in seeing... you know, whatever you have up there...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I've heard guys' chests aren't as taboo as women's... But they're still pretty nice to look at, don't you think?</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">You don't mind me looking at you while you show off? Even if I drool a little?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grin.png">Not so different from zombies', but way more lively!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Not bad, ~target~. Do you wanna go to the gym later? I can show you how the agents of L.E.A.F. prepare for battle.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Mmh. Yeah, I can see how humans go crazy for these... Especially with sweat or raindrops falling on them...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh my gourd... My heart skipped a beet for a moment! I think I'm getting the hang of this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Not bad at all...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I wouldn't mind laying on top of that...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Hehe... That's actually pretty hot...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I wanna see more than just that...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-whistling.png">So... we're gonna see ~target~'s vine?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I gotta admit, I'm a bit... interested in seeing ~target~'s mushroom...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I haven't seen that many human dicks, so this is at least gonna be educational...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I wouldn't be totally opposed to seeing ~target~'s cock...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">So we're gonna see ~target~'s penis... That's the word, right? "Penis"? They sometimes use it in human porn but they also use "cock" and "dick" as well...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Please... I wanna see it...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I want to see your mushroom... Show it to me...</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">I'd like to do so many things to you... If you show me your cock, I don't know if I'll be able to hold myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-happy.png">We've been waiting all game to see little ~target~, so show it to us!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Hey, if it's a good one, I might get turned on again. Make it a good strip, 'kay?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I have fantasized about dicks before... You even saw me touching myself, so I don't really know what kind of reaction you're waiting for...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-wink.png">Your little shrub is pretty cute! I'm sure that if you take good care of it and nurture it properly, it'll turn into a big wood someday! </state>
                <state img="#-grin.png" font-size="small">Don't feel too bad about your tiny mushroom, ~target~! You can defend a whole garden from an army of zombies with nothing bu tiny mushrooms! Tiny sizes are valid!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" dialogue-layer="over">Aww, your little thing is adorable! One of my favorite zombie-stopping strategies is all about using tiny mushrooms like yours! I wish I had one attached to me at all times too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Hehe... It looks like a cute little Seedling... Who knows what it can do for you if you give it a chance...</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">It's so cute... Like a little Puff-shroom...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Don't worry about your size, ~target~! It's pretty big by plant standards!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Hey there, little fella. Need some watering to reach your full potential?</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Just what we wanted to see!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It reminds me of a Puff-shroom... T-that's nothing to be ashamed off. Puff-shrooms are total troopers...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">It looks... cute? I think? I'm not sure what I'm supposed to say, sorry...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">It's kinda cute... It reminds me of a mushroom— I-In a good way!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">So they look like that... Completely different than plants', I suppose.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">It has a stem, its filled with white goo, it has a big head at the end of it... if it had petals it might as well be a flower...</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">That's quite the wood you've got there! I'm impressed!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I knew it! They do look like Carnivorous Pitcher Plants! The Tree of Wisdom was right again!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I can see why people would call it a log... It's hard as one, too...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">It's so... hard... I want to know how it'd feel...</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">If my humanoid fingers feel so good, I wonder how your pickle would feel...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I could've used seeing that a bit earlier, but I'm still glad you're gonna enjoy yourself soon too!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Why do humans call it a log? It's barely a mushroom! I can definitely take it. Heck, bring me more of those, I'll take on them all.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You're very hard right now, ~target~. I didn't think tomboy sunflowers were your type~</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">If human girls can take on that... I guess I could too? I-I mean, I am willing to try...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">H-hey... If you're looking for a sun producer, I don't usually do it anymore, but... if it's for you...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Look at the size of that &lt;i&gt;Doom Shoom&lt;/i&gt;! You could whack zombies with it!</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="29">Are all humans like that? Is... Is Dave like that too?</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Now that's an impressive log, ~target~. Mighty and impressive like an unanswered &lt;i&gt;Poison Oak&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-scared.png">That's not a mushroom, that's a Doom-shroom!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">... I-it's not that big, not at all. I could definitely take on it, no problem.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;H-huh? Do you want to try? Right now? I'm... busy, perhaps later...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">... Well, drat. Hey, handsome, wanna come with me after the game? I need to experiment with this body, and you definitely seem to be packing an experiment log!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is a big deal for humans, right? Showing their chest to others? Alright, I'm here for it! Let's see it!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">So... all that's left now is for us to judge ~target~'s breasts, right? I'm no expert on the matter, but I am willing to give them a look...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Show us the goods, ~target~. And don't worry, you're safe with us. I'll make sure of it.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Don't feel embarrassed now, ~target~. I'm a plant, I haven't seen many human chests. So whatever you've got up there, it's all new and exciting to me!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Hey, you have boobs, I have boobs now... We've got nothing to be ashamed of! It's all natural, is it not?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I need to see you, ~target~... Show me what you've got...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I'm having a great time, ~target~! If seeing your chest makes me feel better, then I wanna see it!</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">Even though I've got these... breasts of my own, I'd like to see some more... I can understand why humans are so eager now...</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">Now that I see so many beautiful women... I can see why humans draw us plants with big chests... I wanna see yours, too...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-whistling.png">You can't really make a bigger mess than I did with just showing your boobs, so...</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">There's nothing to worry about, ~target~! Look at me, I'm doing just fine and I've shown all of me too!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Even if the game is over for me, I gotta admit I'd still want to see how you look with your chest exposed...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-grin.png">Not bad, ~target~! A slim, slender figure with small, almost imperceptible bumps. Like a plant's stem!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">You've got a cute body, ~target~! With no unnecessary fat on your trunk, your posture is perfect for standing uprights getting sunlight for hours!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I've been informed that "flat" is "justice", and as a righteous superhero, I approve of your body!</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="397">... I think the Tree of Wisdom got it all wrong. These don't look like Fukurokuryuzinboku at all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Don't feel bad about the size of your chestnuts! You're still legit, and if I had a penis I'd definitely &lt;i&gt;nut&lt;/i&gt; in your &lt;i&gt;chest&lt;/i&gt;!&lt;br&gt;... That came out really forced, I'm sorry.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">My nipples are so sensitive now... Well, I actually have nipples now, I didn't have them when I was a plant. I wonder if having less fat on my chest would change the sensitivity...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You're elegant and distinguished, ~target~. Slim and slender like a Scaredy-shroom, but with a lot of fight in your heart!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I guess they are pretty good looking... Us plants don't have anything like that, so it took me a while to really get it...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">We generally use nectar to entice pollinators, but it's nice to see humans have their own ways of enticing other humans into doing their bidding!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">Human breasts, huh. Not so different from the ones I have right now, but totally different to what plants usually have. Fascinating.</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">
                    <text>I'm still a bit confused about the role these... "boobs" of yours take in human reproduction. But I'll get it eventually! You don't have to slow down for me!</text>
                    <operations>
                        <forfeit attr="heavy" value="reset" />
                    </operations>
                </state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh, so that's why they call them nipplefruits!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">It took me a while, but I can really see the beauty of women now. There's a lot of reasons, and I'm seeing two of them right now.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">You're... sexy, ~target~. I think that's the word? Sexually attractive? You are... uhm, appealing to look at.</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">You shine like the daylight, ~target~. Your beauty sparkles like the light of sunrise, a light that everyone from plants to humans want to bask and revel in. You... are smokin' hot, bud! And your boobs are fire!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-scared.png">Look at the size of those human breasts! How can you walk upright? If we had those, the sheer weight would pull us down to the ground!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I suppose I could've chosen a chest as big as that for my humanoid form... Oh, nuts. I hope my size is still attractive for your standards...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="small">Okay, so, what kind of plant-based names do people use for those... Pumpkins? Apples? Cantaloupes? Watermelons? Melons?&lt;br&gt;Your... uhm... melons look pretty alright!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">The Tree of Wisdom was right, they &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; quite big! Now I just gotta find a Cattail or a Cactus to find out if they pop!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I've gotta admit, if having bigger breasts is gonna make others want to please me more, I kinda see the appeal now...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I used to think carrying those big sacks of yellow fat all day was a waste of energy, but... if it means that a lot of people would like me more and &lt;i&gt;want&lt;/i&gt; to sexually please me... I... kinda would want to try?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">The pleasure in this body feels amazing! Way better than a plant! If having a bigger chest would make others want to give me more pleasure, then drat, I wish I could change my body to have a bigger chest!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="undead" role="target" />
                <state img="#-whistling.png">... Not bad for a zombie, I suppose..</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">This doesn't look anything like the zombie hordes I'm used to dealing with...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">This better not awake anything in me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">So I'm gonna see ~target~'s vagina now... I got one too, but I can't really take a good look at it. And as a plant, I don't really have </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">We're gonna see ~target~'s... pussy now, right? I haven't seen that many in real life and I just got this new body, so... This is gotta be interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">C'mon, ~target~. You've got a vagina, I've got a vagina, we've got a lot in common. Enough for you to show me yours without making a fuss about it, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7-8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Don't be embarrassed, ~target~! You've seen a lot of me to~background.time~, far more than just my flower!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Can't wait to see ~target~ now! I think I know what she's gonna show us!~</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're on your last life now, ~target~! Make the most out of it and enjoy yourself! Set yourself free, show yourself to the world!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-worry.png">... I don't see the visual resemblance. How come people call that a "flower"?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I don't really mind people calling their genitals "flowers", considering that they're basically our genitals as well...</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Nothing to be ashamed of, ~target~! Your... pussy is a sight for sore eyes!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">The Tree of Wisdom was right! They &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; look like  Poppy Plants!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-grin.png">Your time's almost up, ~target~! Make the most out of this game or face the Continue screen!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">This is nothing for you, ~target~! I'm sure you can do a lot more lewder things than showing your flower to some strangers! Just look at what I just did!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">You're doing great, ~target~! Even when losing, you're still getting everyone's attention!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're really close to the best part, ~target~! I'm telling you, this was great! You should try it too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">Not so different from mine... And yet, I can get lost on watching the subtle differences...</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I can see why humans like seeing these now... It's definitely a sight that could cure sore eyes...</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">That's gotta be the cutest Poppy Plant I've ever seen...</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">... I wonder if you'd pleasure it the same way I am... I... kinda wanna see that now...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="goth" role="target" />
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="39">I wonder if ~target~'s ever heard of silk floss trees. They have beautiful flowers and are filled to the brim with spikes. Those might go well with ~target.ifMale(his|her)~ whole aesthetic...</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="41" dialogue-layer="over">Such dark, gloomy style... There are so many flowers that'd go well with your aesthetic. Dahlia flowers, Baccara roses, Penny blacks, Black magics, Black ray petunias...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" oneShotId="40">Someone here might have liked the Dark Ages a bit too much!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="42">So this is the human equivalent of shadow plants...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="8">
                <condition filter="undead" role="target" />
                <state img="#-angry.png">Zombies... Why don't you make like a begonia and &lt;i&gt;be gone, ya?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="13">
                <condition filter="catfolk" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="Catfolk">~target.ifMale(He|She)~ looks like a humanized Cattail... Does ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ go "Woof" when ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ sees something ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ likes too?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="witch" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smile.png">As long as ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ doesn't turn anyone ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ doesn't like into goats, ~target.ifMale(he's|she's)~ fine by me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="14">
                <condition filter="tomboy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-grin.png">I've been told that I'm a "tomboy" myself. And so are you, apparently!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="league_of_legends" role="target" />
                <state img="#-grin.png" oneShotId="359">Our seasons are reversed. My spring, your fall!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png" oneShotId="360">Watch your step, this is {b}MY{!reset} garden.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="16">
                <condition filter="gun" role="target" />
                <state img="#-bashful.png" marker="Gun1" font-size="small">So... ~target.ifMale(he|she)~'s carrying a gun, huh... I guess that's cool. Guns are great to deal with zombies, but they're so noisy they tend to attract even more...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="Gun2" dialogue-layer="over">I remember the first time I played the Last Stand on an arcade machine. It was so fun to shoot at zombies! Now I get why humans love their guns so much! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="monster" role="target" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Yetis, Frankentuars, Cursed Gargolith, Gizzard Lizards... I've fought all kinds of monsters. They've got nothing on me.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">I've dealt with mummies, yetis, dragons, medusas... All kinds of monsters helping the zombie hordes. And in the end, they all burn.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="ghost" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I've burned Haunting Ghosts with my Sunburns before. This isn't anything new for me.</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I'm more used to defeating corporeal undeads, but hey, fire is fire! It'll burn ghosts just as well!&lt;br&gt;... Also this is a poker card game, not actual zombie fighting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="wand" role="target" />
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" oneShotId="504" marker="Wand1" dialogue-layer="over">I see you have a wand, ~target~! I know a certain rose who uses one as well to turn zombies into goats... I hope you don't turn any of us into goats.</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png" oneShotId="505" marker="Wand2">I haven't seen many wands myself... But a friend of mine uses one and she's totally cool! Real smarty, too! So I'll assume you're pretty smart as well!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="superhero" role="target" />
                <state img="#-happy.png" oneShotId="510" marker="Superhero1">It's always a pleasure to meet new heroes like you, ~target~! With both of us here, there's no danger we can't protect innocents from!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png" oneShotId="511" marker="Superhero2">So there are more superheroes outside of Suburbia... That's great! The more superheroes around, the more innocent lives we can save from the zombie hordes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="ninja" role="target" />
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" oneShotId="524" marker="Ninja1">You remind me a lot of a friend of mine, ~target~! He's also very nimble, and can disppear and reappear at will... Please don't disappear on us!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png" oneShotId="525" marker="Ninja2">I've seen both plant ninjas and zombie ninjas in my line of work. You can never know what to expect, and that's so on-brand for them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="gym_leader" role="target" />
                <state img="#-wink.png" oneShotId="550" marker="GymLeader1">Hey, aren't you one of those creature trainers that take care of plant monsters in your world? That's pretty hot, yo!</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png" oneShotId="551" marker="GymLeader2">I heard Pokémon trainers raise creatures with love and care... Some of those creatures being plants themselves, becoming stronger... Perhaps I could learn some things from you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="7">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <test expr="~target.biggestlead~" cmp="&gt;=" value="3" />
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I guess your luck had to run out eventually, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" dialogue-layer="over">I get how you feel. I've lost battles against the zombies that seemed already won, just because I ran out of good cards to play...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">What's wrong, ~target~? Have you lost your spark? </state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" dialogue-layer="over" font-size="smaller">This tends to happen to keep the game interesting, ~target~. Even where I come from, if you're doing too good at Arena, you'll soon face a much better opponent to stop you in your tracks.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="13">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">Did you forget how to play, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Do you need any help, ~target~? I can help you out if you need tips to pick better cards...</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">You really got up a tree, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Drat, you really fell out of the unlucky tree and hit every branch on the way down, ~target~...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="14">
                <test expr="~target.lead~" cmp="&gt;" value="1" />
                <state img="#-happy.png">C'mon ~target~, you're still in the lead. You can deal with this, right?</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">This is still your moment in the sun, ~target~. Don't be discouraged!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">You've got more lives left, don't you? Come on, ~target~! Press start and continue!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="High Card" />
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="1">If I just stay really quiet, perhaps the others won't notice that I also had a pretty bad hand...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8" id="15">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="socks" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(shoes)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-scared.png">Wait,  you can take off your socks before your shoes? Is that allowed?</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">How did you take off your socks before your shoes? Are you a ~target.ifMale(wizard|witch)~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="16">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="underwear" />
                <test expr="~target.wearing(underwear)~" cmp="!=" value="~blank~" />
                <state img="#-grin.png">You came here ready to surprise us, huh? Not bad!</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Ah, the ol' multiple layers of underwear. I'll enjoy peeling them off of you like humans peel layers of onions.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="19">
                <test expr="~clothing~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-worry.png">Are you sure you don't need those to see? What's the point of the game if you can't see the naked players?</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I don't know how you can remove your glasses, I wouldn't take off my goggles for anything. And I don't even need them to play, just to use my powers...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Correct me if I'm wrong, but don't humans need glasses to see...? And isn't this whole game about... seeing other players stripping...?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="18" oneShotId="15">
                <condition count="1" status="exposed" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png">And now the game starts heating up. This is where the real game begins.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Now this is what I came here for. Let's turn up the heat!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Finally some nude action. The game has turned real interesting...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Hehe... So... it's ~target~'s turn, right?</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Doo do doo... O-oh, is it ~target~'s turn to... touch himself? I didn't even notice... He can go ahead, I guess...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I've been waiting for this all day...&lt;br&gt;... I-I mean... I've been waiting for ~target~ to lose, not to see him... doing... you know...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You're up, ~target~! I haven't seen a human man jerk off before today, so this is gotta be quite the show for me!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-wink.png">Ready? Go!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Come on, ~target~! The show's on! Let's Rock!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">We're all waiting on you, ~target~! Give us a delightful show! Dazzle us with your shining bright!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Are you looking at me, ~target~? Don't tell me you're down bad for a literal flower.</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">There's no shame in defeat. At least you get to feel good about yourself in the process.</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Yup! That sure is a man touching himself in front of me! Just another regular activity in a regular day for regular humans, I suppose!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I can't believe I'm seeing ~target~ jack off! I didn't even knew him before this game!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">I wouldn't mind having one of those myself to try that out. I wonder if the same thing that turned me human could give me one.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">It's a bit... repetitive, isn't it? That probably means it feels good.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">I thought it looked like a mushroom... But now that I see you doing that, I can't help but imagine you being rough with a poor mushroom...</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png">Aren't you being a bit too rough with it? </state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I... kinda wonder how touching it would feel like...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-wink.png">And so the sun sets on you, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Did you enjoy yourself, ~target~? Did you manage to spread your seeds on the wind like plants spread their spores?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">That was pretty hot, ~target~. Remind me to lend you a hand next time.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Woah! That's a man eyaculating! So cool! So hot! So lukewarm!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Looks like we're gonna see some fireworks now!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Game over, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You're out of credits, ~target~! Time to face the bonus screen!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">And so... the sun sets on your game. But at least you'll get a pretty cool bonus, you get to masturbate in front of us!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Time to take your time on the spotlight, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Time to turn over a new leaf, ~target~! Yeah, you lost the game, but you can be a winner in your self-pleasuring!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Game over for you, bud.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-smile.png">You're at the flower of your youth, ~target~. Enjoy it at your fullest!</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I should take some notes!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">You could do that?... I mean, of course I knew how to do that. I'm sooo used to being a human and not a plant...</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">I didn't expect this to be all hearts and flowers, but... it's still pretty nice.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Talk about raising up the heat...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png" oneShotId="342">This is pretty hot... Now I get why my phallus-shaped friends don't mind... you know.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="343">Who would've thought you'd be in such a pickle right now...&lt;br&gt;And that you could use a pickle as well...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">And here I thought a sunflower superhero with fire powers was hot. This is way hotter.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png" oneShotId="344">They say the "sun-kissed" style is in vogue now, so... I might not be the sun, but I'm pretty close, if you wanna try it...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">... This is way hotter than I expected it to be...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You don't need any help, do you, ~target~? Plants and fertility go hand in hand. Or leaf in hand, if you prefer.</state>
                <state img="#-scared.png" oneShotId="363">I don't know why humans call &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; a "flower", I certainly wouldn't treat a flower like that...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You're so vibrant and full of life... You gotta give me the name of your gardener.</state>
                <state img="#-smile.png">It's actually nice to see ~target~ enjoying herself like this. You grow, girl.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Well, look at you, ~target~. All shiny and filled with joy, sparkling like a Christmas tree!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">You're shining brighter than the sun, ~target~! You really enjoyed yourself, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I'll have to get some tips from you, ~target~. You seem to be pre-e-etty good at this!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-worry.png">Really, now? I can't believe I'm the first one to go...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">So it's gonna be... me, I guess. You all played pretty well, I guess I have no other choice...</state>
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">So it's... me. Fine, I have no problem with it! I mean, I was kinda hoping to not be the worst player on the table, but you can't win 'em all!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-competitive.png">You've shown me a lot, now I'll show you how we do this on Suburbia.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Drat. Welll, about time I joined in, don't you think? Let me show you how us plants do it.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I bet you didn't know you'd be seeing a plant girl touch herself when you woke up today, did you? You're gonna see way more than that!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-starting.png">Alright, just give me a sec, okay? I'm not used to doing this with this new body...</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">I've been meaning to practice more with this body, so this &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; gonna be pretty educational...</state>
                <state img="#-starting.png">Heads up, this might get messy. I've done this with my plant body before, but not that much with this humanoid one.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition filter="undead" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-mast3.png">Touching myself in front of the enemy,,, Never thought I'd see the day...</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">If the other agents found out about this they'd be furious... They might want to... punish me...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">When I woke up today I didn't know I was gonna let a zombie on my lawn...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">These... fingers are doing pretty well, a lot better than leaves...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I wouldn't mind... someone embracing me, fusing our warmth together...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">What do you think, ~player~? Am I too hot to handle?</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I can feel the heat rising...</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">This is way hotter than I expected...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I think this feels even better in this body!</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I... might want to try doing more things with this body... than just pleasuring myself on my own...</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">If this is so good, how come we aren't doing it with more people...? Us plants share everything, maybe you could do the same...?</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png" oneShotId="176">I don't envy mimosa pudicas at all, I &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/i&gt; want to be touched...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I can feel the heat... And it's oh, so hot...</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">... I gotta tell the other agents about this...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I wanna lie down... But what kind of hero would deprive you from watching her for your own pleasure...?</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">How come I'm so wet...? Plants are supposed to keep the water in, not out...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Look at me and get your fill of chlorophyll!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="269">Horny for a flower? God, you are a beautiful person.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png" oneShotId="274">&lt;i&gt;Here comes the sun...&lt;/i&gt; ♫</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png">I hope you're getting some pleasure by watching me... I'm definitely getting some pleasure myself...</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I wonder which one of my friends would be better at this if they were human...</state>
                <state img="#-mast1.png" oneShotId="416">Tehee.. I'm a thirsty little flower...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">If I had known humans were so sensitive, I would've asked Rose to turn me into a human sooner...</state>
                <state img="#-mast2.png">I feel so hot and sweaty... And yet, I can't think of anything else but having someone else on top of me, sharing their warmth with me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" oneShotId="17">
                <state img="#-mast3.png">&lt;i&gt;He loves me... He loves me not...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-mast3.png">&lt;i&gt;She loves me... She loves me not...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">... I wanna grab on to someone and feel their embrace...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Uhn~&lt;br&gt; ... This is gonna sound dumb, but... I kinda wish someone would grab me from the back of my head and...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I want... I want to feel someone's fingers playing through my hair... Touching, caressing, squeezing it...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Mmh... To hear... the breathy whispers of someone on my ears... To feel them close while I feel their skin on mine...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">&lt;i&gt;Sssshh...&lt;/i&gt; ...I want to be filled with your seed...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="185">Fertilize me...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">Ngh... I need... your nutrients...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="187">Ahn... Pollinate me...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Hehe...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">I remember... That time the alien ooze caught me on the heights...&lt;br&gt;All those thick, slimy tentacles... Nngh...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">If only I could have someone... nibbling on my ears... my petals... caressing my leaves...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I... need someone to just... take me from my leaves and ravage me... Making me theirs, nibbling me, breathing all over my skin... So I could feel their warmth on me...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png" oneShotId="425">A heroine shouldn't put her pleasure over her duty... I must behave... I must... I...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">If only I had some... vines to help me... Touching me all over, caressing me gently, overflowing my emotions with their touch...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">I'm so thirsty... Nngh...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">... Fuck...&lt;br&gt;... &lt;i&gt;me...&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I feel something coming... Is this how humans feel their orgasms...? It's... getting there...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy1.png">... Almost... there...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">I think... I think I'm about to... Oh, fff...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png">Just a little more... Just a little... p-please... oh...</state>
                <state img="#-heavy2.png" oneShotId="438">I feel like I'm gonna burst... Like a piñata...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-finishing.png">I'm gonna... I'm about to... I can't... even.. t-talk...&lt;br&gt;Ah... Hnngh... Ngwah...~</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">I think I'm coming! I feel it! I fe-e-e-eel... iiiit...~</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">Sshhhhhh.... O-oh... M-mmh... Mnnh...~</state>
                <state img="#-finishing.png">A-ah... A-a-aaahhh....~!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-finished.png">... That... That was so... Intense... Oh beans...</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">... I... I can't... believe... how good that felt...</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">... I... That... Woah...&lt;br&gt;This needs to happen... more... and often.</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">... My Gaia... That was... that was just... jeez...</state>
                <state img="#-finished.png">... Jeez... I... didn't think that'd be so... hot... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-worry.png">Is this gonna take too long...? I don't mind waiting, but don't have all the thyme in the world. I need to be somewhere else at tree o'clock.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I hope the other agents are taking care of my Zen Garden...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="61">Hey, ~player~! You're gonna join the fight against the zombies, right? If you do, send me your ID so we can train together!</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png">Oh drat, I hope Dave doesn't fill my spaces with mold colonies before I get back...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Soooo, ~player~. What kind of garden hose setting do you prefer? There's center, shower, flat, jet, mist, soaker...</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Here's a quick tip. If you're depenent on meds to keep you going, stock up on them! You never know when a zombie invasion might break out.</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">Have you ever played tennis? If you're in the middle of a zombie apocalypse, you're gonna be bashing a lot of heads, so you better get used to that tennis elbow...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="93">We had a lot of fun taking off our clothes today, didnt't we? If this were a zombie apocalypse, always remember, the only clothes you need are enough so the bites won't get to ya. Leather jackets, a few layers of heavy clothes, or just... tape some magazines around you!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">A lot of people think surviving a zombie apocalypse needs you to be good at fighting zombies. Not really! You can just run away, or stall them, or find other ways to defend yourself, like growing yourself a really good garden!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="146" weight="0.05">This was a pretty fun game, ~player~! If you want to keep having fun with me, why don't you download Plants vs Zombies Heroes from your phone's app store, play the tutorial, earn some gems through daily quests and ad watching, and then search through the internet for videos showing the step by step process on how to dowload and modify the game's files, specifically with the modified card_data_172 file, so you can put it on the game's folder to make all the recommended decks cost only 10-20 gems each, so you can have access to several of the most powerful cards and deck archetypes of the game without spending a single penny and not contributing to Electronic Arts' butchering of my franchise?</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">If you're afraid of a potential zombie apocalypse, you need all the info that you can get! Remember that gas goes bad, tires deflate and the rubber gaskets in cars rot! Cars will be good for a while, but after that you better get horses or bikes!</state>
                <state img="#-worry.png" oneShotId="283">Now that I think about it, I've fought all kinds of zombie animals lately. Parrots, seagulls, chickens, dinosaurs, weasels, dolphins... Though I've heard dolphins are pretty bad even when they're alive.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png" oneShotId="536">Let me give you an advice straight from the Tree of Wisdom! If you've got unspent sun, you should be planting more Sunflowers on the front! We're no nuts, but against the zombie hordes, every bite counts! And if we survive, we keep on giving sun! That's a win/win!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You better get in touch with your green thumb, you know. Once the apocalypse hits, plants will always be around to help you out, if you know how to best use them to suits your needs.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="undead" role="opp" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png">When it comes to dealing with the zombie hordes, I'm always at the top of the game!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Sorry, undeadies, but you're gonna stay under the ground this time. Plants win!</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">Score another victory for the plants against the zombies! I've been keeping this lawn safe since 2016 and I plan on keeping it that way!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Day and night, an agent of L.E.A.F always perseveres! </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Were you even trying, ~player~? This was way too easy! Get better and try next time, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Not a single point of damage! Not even a shield tick! Am I good at this game or what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Come on, this can't be the end! I barely got to take off my shoes! Even zombies have better stamina than all of you!</state>
                <state img="#-angry.png">I've battled zombies more lively than you, ~player~! Next time you better play for reals, I didn't come here just to see you touch yourself!</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I kinda wish I could've joined in on the fun... You know, stripping, teasing, masturbating... But I guess winning isn't that bad...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">Hey, no one holds grudges in here... right? You don't mind that I won easily and that I might win again the next time?</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I knew humans were really into feet but I didn't expect all of you to just orgasm and let me win once I showed mine... Ah well, I'll see if the next table has a free spot...</state>
                <state img="#-competitive.png">Sorry, ~player~. My feet are all you get this time. Why don't you get better at poker and then come face me again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Come on! You were so close! How about another game? Maybe I'll let you see my breasts then~</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">This was a pretty good game! You were close, but I'm just way more experienced with cards than the regular player. Anyway, see ya next game!</state>
                <state img="#-happy.png">Don't be discouraged! I got this good at card games by playing a lot of them! Keep playing and you'll have a better chance next time!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">I was gonna flash you and let you take a peek, but... Nah. You gotta earn this, ~player~. Get good.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well... You weren't so bad, ~player~. If you really wanna get better at the game, why don't we... practice in private? We can talk about it next game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Aw, and you were so close. What's wrong, ~player~? Couldn't take the heat? Don't worry, not even zombies can handle me.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping2.png">Are you sure you didn't lose on purpose just to have me see you masturbating? &lt;br&gt;... Sure, whatever you say. We'll see each other next game, then.</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">That was pretty close... I guess I just got lucky this time. Perhaps we could try again... next game?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-whistling.png">Winning feels nice, but... I kinda wanted to, you know... Y-you know... &lt;br&gt;Well, there's always next game...</state>
                <state img="#-bashful.png">I guess winning is nice... But I was hoping to be able to touch myself like you did...&lt;br&gt;I... wouldn't be opposed to playing with you again soon...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I bet you were wondering what color my nipples were, weren't you, ~player~? I don't even know myself! But next game, maybe we could learn... together.</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">Come on, ~player~! You were so close to see me fully naked! You can totally get it right next time!</state>
                <state img="#-whistling.png">I guess you were pretty close this time... Don't be discouraged ~player~. I'm sure you'll get it right... next game.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8" id="12">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <test expr="~self.place~" value="2" />
                <state img="#-competitive.png">That was real close, ~winner~! Next time, I'll make sure to take you out first!</state>
                <state img="#-wink.png">You won, ~winner~. But next time, I'll be ready! You can be as sure as the sun comes up that I'll be!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-blush smile.png">I actually had a lot of fun, everyone! If you wanna play again, you can always count on me... If you're not bored, that is...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">We had our good fun, didn't we? I bet we could learn all sorts of things about each other if we play another game. What do you think, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-grin.png">That was epic! We definitely gotta play again sometime! Tell you what, maybe I'll bring one of my friends next time!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">What an epic match. You've earned my respect, ~winner~. If you ever need a partner to fight the zombie hordes. I'm your sunflower.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
