<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>bella_goth</owner>
    <height>5"10</height>
    <age>Adult (29 days from becoming Elder)</age>
    <pronunciation>bell-uh g-aa-th</pronunciation>
    <othernotes>Table of Contents&lt;br&gt;[1] Introduction&lt;br&gt;    [1.01] Guide&lt;br&gt;    [1.02] Version History&lt;br&gt;[2] Getting Started&lt;br&gt;    [2.01] Create a Sim&lt;br&gt;[3] The Real World [Where you make TV]&lt;br&gt;    [3.01] Starting&lt;br&gt;[4] Season 1&lt;br&gt;    [4.01] Buried by the Mob&lt;br&gt;    [4.02] What Digs Beneath&lt;br&gt;    [4.03] Aliens Arrived&lt;br&gt;[5] Season 2&lt;br&gt;    [5.01] Blackout!&lt;br&gt;    [5.02] A Brand New Scent&lt;br&gt;    [5.03] The New Cola&lt;br&gt;    [5.04] There Was This Mummy&lt;br&gt;[6] Season 3&lt;br&gt;    [6.01] Triassic Trouble&lt;br&gt;    [6.02] The Doomed Earth&lt;br&gt;    [6.03] It All Came to an End&lt;br&gt;    [6.04] A Very Special Reunion&lt;br&gt;[7] Stores&lt;br&gt;    [7.01] Skills&lt;br&gt;    [7.02] Saloon&lt;br&gt;[8] Mini Games&lt;br&gt;    [8.01] King Chug Chug&lt;br&gt;    [8.02] Car Commerical&lt;br&gt;    [8.03] Bigfoot Loves Chickens&lt;br&gt;    [8.04] Cattle Cleanup&lt;br&gt;    [8.05] Canyon Jumping&lt;br&gt;    [8.06] Chop Shop&lt;br&gt;    [8.07] Keelhaulin' Cards&lt;br&gt;[9] Plot Twists&lt;br&gt;    [9.01] Twists!&lt;br&gt;[10] Social Moves&lt;br&gt;    [10.01] Friendly&lt;br&gt;    [10.02] Romantic&lt;br&gt;    [10.03] Intimidating&lt;br&gt;[11] Telephone&lt;br&gt;    [11.01] Calls&lt;br&gt;[12] Errands - Summary&lt;br&gt;    [12.01] Season 1&lt;br&gt;    [12.02] Season 2&lt;br&gt;    [12.03] Season 3&lt;br&gt;[13] Hidden Wants - Summary&lt;br&gt;    [13.01] Season 1&lt;br&gt;    [13.02] Season 2&lt;br&gt;    [13.03] Season 3&lt;br&gt;[14] Random Plurges&lt;br&gt;    [14.01] Characters&lt;br&gt;    [14.02] The Cast&lt;br&gt;[-] Questions and Answers&lt;br&gt;    [--.01] Q&amp;A&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;[A] Contact Information&lt;br&gt;[B] Webmaster Information&lt;br&gt;[C] Credits&lt;br&gt;[D] Sites FAQ is on&lt;br&gt;[E] Copyright&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[1.01] Guide&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hi, everybody. By now, you should know me on the Sims 2 arena, I have a large&lt;br&gt;range of guides on those games. Anyway, welcome to my fifth guide. Well, first&lt;br&gt;of all, this is not the Sims 2 from PC transferred to the GBA. Well, that &lt;br&gt;could happen, but the time to create all that data and transfer it to GBA will&lt;br&gt;be impossible, unless, a GBA cartridge can hold about 4 gigs of memory. This &lt;br&gt;is basically a follow up of the Urbz - Sims in the City, which was my second&lt;br&gt;guide. Although many consider the Urbz was a better game, this will entertain&lt;br&gt;you for quite some time. Have fun!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[1.02] Version History&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Version 0.1 [4/11/05]&lt;br&gt;My fifth guide. Lets begin. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Version 0.2 [5/11/05]&lt;br&gt;Finished most of the walkthrough&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Version 0.3 [6/11/05]&lt;br&gt;Finishing the rest.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Version 0.4 [18/12/05]&lt;br&gt;Fixing up the nitbits.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Version 0.5 [20/12/05]&lt;br&gt;Added ASCII art to title.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Complete [26/1/06]&lt;br&gt;Finishing off bits and pieces.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[2.01] Create a Sim&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First things first. All you have to do to start is to create a Sim. Give you&lt;br&gt;Sim a name. Well, that is how people know who you are. Press select to change&lt;br&gt;your capital letters into non-capital letters&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After you finish, click on the done key. Now onto phase 2. You have to give a&lt;br&gt;gender to your Sim. After the gender, you have to give a skin tone to your Sim&lt;br&gt;so make him / her any colour you like.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, phase 3. You have to select a hair style for you little Sim. You only &lt;br&gt;have four choices so pick one. Now, you can pick the hair colour of your &lt;br&gt;little sim. Change the direction on the pad to change the colour. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phase 4 and you select what type of shirt you want your Sim to have. Then you &lt;br&gt;get to customise your shirt. Pick any colour and move on. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Phase 5 and it involves what leg wear you want your Sim to have. It is &lt;br&gt;basically the same as phase 4. After that, choose what colour your shoes are.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now you get to choose what aspiration you want your Sim to have. There are &lt;br&gt;three aspiration as opposed to the 5 in the Sims 2 for PC. You get to have &lt;br&gt;friendly, romantic and Intimidating. You get ratings for having conversations&lt;br&gt;that involve your aspiration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, confirm and you can enter the outside world.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[3.01] Starting&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After Mr Boss finishes chucking a hissy fit, you get your first orders. Press&lt;br&gt;Start to find out.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go Upstairs and Explore the Town&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After you see the house that you will be living in, go outside and you will&lt;br&gt;see Dusty Hogg, a character than came from The Sims Bustin Out, and the Urbz&lt;br&gt;Sims in the City. You will have your first, proper conservation with this&lt;br&gt;biker. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Have a nice look at that chat screen. Get used to it, you will be seeing it &lt;br&gt;a lot. For every successful interaction, the rating bar, on the right will go&lt;br&gt;up. For every negative interaction, the rating bar will go down. Your &lt;br&gt;objective here is to complete this conservation by filling up the diamond.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, after you finish, you will have new plot points.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy a piece of furniture from the Pawn Shop&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have 499 Simoleons to spend at the pawn shop. Move up the road and you &lt;br&gt;will have a cutscene of the pawn shop. Enter it and Dusty will be in there. &lt;br&gt;You will be told that the shop gets more stuff everyday so keep checking. The&lt;br&gt;things you need right now is a bed and shower. They are the move important at&lt;br&gt;this current point. After you buy the stuff you need, you will finish and get&lt;br&gt;a new plot point&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use the Toilet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Hurry home to use the toilet. You will be filled in on the performance meter&lt;br&gt;at the bottom of the screen. Hurry home to use your newly installed toilet.&lt;br&gt;When you arrive at your green toilet, you see a green alien. Now that is &lt;br&gt;weird. Guess aliens have to use toilets as well. Well, talk to him. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are forced to leave the bathroom. Then you are told by your boss that the&lt;br&gt;alien is Burple, an alien actor he hired to stir things up. Now you have some&lt;br&gt;more orders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intimidate the alien off the toilet.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now start the conservation with intimidating conversation. Just annoy and &lt;br&gt;insult the alien until the diamond is full red. After that, Burple will go &lt;br&gt;away and you recieve new plot points&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Fix the toilet&lt;br&gt;Meet Daddy Bigbucks in the boardroom downstairs&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First of all, go to the toilet and choose repair. The toilet will turn white.&lt;br&gt;Now, use the toilet. Time to move on. Go downstairs. To open the door, you &lt;br&gt;have to go to the valve to open it. Open the door and move in. Now, you get&lt;br&gt;to make Commerical Breaks. Its like a mini game where you earn your money. You&lt;br&gt;will be made to do them every now and then so get used to it. You will be told&lt;br&gt;that while you were busy, Dusty wanted you. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to the Saloon to see what Dusty wants&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Before you go, you get a Cell Phone. Before you go, place down the items. You &lt;br&gt;should know how to do it. Go to your inventory and select the item. Then move&lt;br&gt;the D pad and place it. Use R and L to rotate it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now head to the saloon, its near the pawn shop. Its after the gate by the way.&lt;br&gt;You get a welcoming party. Enjoy!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Episode Complete.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;At the end of the episode, you get rated by the Goths. You use the rating &lt;br&gt;points to get things like upgrades.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[4.01] Buried by the Mob&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars *&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Mobster Frankie Fusilli has a favor to ask of just about everyone in town. &lt;br&gt;Where do your loyalities lie?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you move towards the door, you will get a message from Jimmy "The Neck". &lt;br&gt;It looks like he won't move so lets give him some insults. This guy takes a &lt;br&gt;while to intimidate so what your moves. After that long conservation, you get&lt;br&gt;some new plot points.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find and return the briefcase to Jimmy "The" Neck&lt;br&gt;Invesitgate the pawn shop and the Saloon for clues&lt;br&gt;Gain Frankie Fusilli's confidence&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets head to the saloon. When you enter it, you will find a pile of sand to &lt;br&gt;the left hand side. You'll investigate the pile. Talk to Dusty and he'll tell&lt;br&gt;you about his broken freezer door. Remember this for now. Head over to the &lt;br&gt;pawn shop. You might as well check what is in store. When you head to the &lt;br&gt;store, go to the left and open the door. You'll see another pile of sand, this&lt;br&gt;time with some paint and glass. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have completed this plot point. Head to Frankie's house for the next one.&lt;br&gt;He is below your house. Wow, what a nice house. Enter the house, through the&lt;br&gt;door and give him a What's Up. His daughter has been down for the last few&lt;br&gt;weeks and you have to cheer her up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Make Friends with Ara Fusilli&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ara is next to the casino, north of the pawn shop. She won't move an inch with&lt;br&gt;the What's Up button and she doesn't look too happy. Give her a friendly &lt;br&gt;conservation and make her happy. After that, you get a new plot point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get something to distract Giuseppi Mezzoalto so Ara can get to the Casino&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;So to the pawn shop and get the paddleball for 250 Simoleons. Give the paddle&lt;br&gt;ball to him as a gift and he'll be distracted. Such a simple thing, so easily&lt;br&gt;amused. Before you do anything, head to the Zoo, two screens west and talk&lt;br&gt;to the Zookeeper and ask for an errand. We'll do this later.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, head back to Frankie and his house. You and Ara make up a great story and&lt;br&gt;you get a new plot point. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Speak to Jimmy the Neck about what you learned&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Jimmy is next to your house so talk to him. After you have a nice chat, you&lt;br&gt;get a shovel and a new plot point.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dig in the desert and bring the briefcase back to Jimmy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now to finish off some unfinished business. The errand you needed to do. To &lt;br&gt;give the plug to Kayleigh, you need to go to the power plant. You have to go &lt;br&gt;to the parking lot and up those stairs. After you are on the platform, head to&lt;br&gt;the room at the far back. Give the item to her and you have finished the&lt;br&gt;errand for this episode. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For the hidden want, you need a mechanical point to fix the freezer. Head &lt;br&gt;south from your house and go across the foot bridge and talk to the guy. You&lt;br&gt;can buy the mechanical book for 175 Simoleons. Read the book and head back to&lt;br&gt;the Saloon. Fix that door for the hidden want to be done. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After you have fixed the door, head back to where you bought the book. Head&lt;br&gt;south and you will find a pile of sand. Dig there with your shovel and head&lt;br&gt;back to Jimmy. Give him a Whats Up and you finish the episode and get the&lt;br&gt;Super Drencher Tool&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[4.02] What Digs Beneath&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars *&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Something strange is lurking under the arid sands of Strangetown. Is it a &lt;br&gt;friend ... or a foe?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You begin this episode with Jimmy going on about how elephants sat on him. &lt;br&gt;You sure it wasn't the other way around Jimmy? Anyway, you see a giant white&lt;br&gt;rat. Jimmy finds it cute. Then you see another one. Where are they coming from&lt;br&gt;you wonder?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigate where all the rats are coming from. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First of all though, head to Frankie's house and search the chimney. You will&lt;br&gt;find the Microfiche so give it to Jimmy, thats is your hidden want complete.&lt;br&gt;While we are sidetracking, we might as well get the errand out of the way. Go&lt;br&gt;east from the main town as talk to Jebediah. He wants you to give a luxury&lt;br&gt;chair to Mrs Hogg. She is normally at the power plant so find her and give it&lt;br&gt;to her. That is the errand done for this episode. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, back to the main quest. Head north of the town and go west to enter the&lt;br&gt;salt mines. After you talk to Lord Mole, you will be encountering Penelope &lt;br&gt;Redd and she will ask you about the moles and she thinks that they are going&lt;br&gt;to make some suicidal weapon of mass destruction. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pluck the spines of a flowering Spiny Cactus&lt;br&gt;Acquire a chuck of fissionable plutoium&lt;br&gt;Find a pair of rubber waders&lt;br&gt;Get a pile of scrap iron&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway, head to the workshop north of you and talk to Optimum Alfred and you &lt;br&gt;will start to play Chop-Shop. After that, you realise that you are not strong&lt;br&gt;enough to get the iron so you have to get Jimmy. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find someone strong to help rip out the iron&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Be friendly to Jimmy and he will follow you to the factory and help you rip&lt;br&gt;out the iron. Now we have the iron. Head to the pawn shop and buy those gloves&lt;br&gt;for 450 Simoleons. You will need it to pluck needles. Head south from your&lt;br&gt;house and go to a cactus. Pluck those needles. That is another one completed.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head to the Casino. Talk to Luthor and for a small price of 300 Simoleons, you&lt;br&gt;will recieve a chuck of plutoium in the mail. Is that safe? While you are &lt;br&gt;there, talk to Pepper Pete and he will tell you where you can find some waders&lt;br&gt;that he lost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dig Up the waders in the field behind the factory. &lt;br&gt;Pick up the plutoium behind the City Hall.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To get the second objective, go to the mail and pick up the note. Then head to&lt;br&gt;city hall, go behind it, near the tunnel and go pick up the plutoium. Now for&lt;br&gt;the waders. Go behind the factory, via the right hand side and dig the patch&lt;br&gt;of sand. Now you have the waders and the final objective&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Return to Lord Mole with all of the items&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Simple. Go to the mole and give him the items. Make sure that your aspiration&lt;br&gt;meter is full, the hidden want and errand complete for the full ratings. You&lt;br&gt;will go to a commerical break before you enter. After you enter, you will face&lt;br&gt;a showdown with Penelope or the Mole. Choose what team you will side for.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Choose who to side with by talking to Penelope Redd or Lord Mole&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Choose who you want and you will play a strange human mole whacking game. If &lt;br&gt;you sided with the mole, have to hit the humans, and vice versa. The result &lt;br&gt;of it will end the episode. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[4.03] Aliens Arrived&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars ****&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy the Weirdness Plot Twist to unlock.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The shrewd Emperor Xizzle launches a full scale invasion ... with a twist: you&lt;br&gt;may not be able to find his army. Be careful!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You talk to Dusty whether you should build a dirt track here or not when Tank&lt;br&gt;comes along acting pretty weird. He wants you to deliver something.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Give Tank's "bonquet" to Kayleigh.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets sidetrack here. The Errand for this level is from Ava in the Gothic &lt;br&gt;Gardens and she wants you to deliver a bottle of green goo for Penelope. So,&lt;br&gt;lets head off to the Gothic Gardens, west of the nuclear power plant and find&lt;br&gt;Ava. She will give you the errand and you have to give it to Penelope. Thats&lt;br&gt;the errand done.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Back on the task at hand. Dusty and Kayleigh are at the power plant discussing&lt;br&gt;what Tank is up to as he seems a bit weird. Dusty also has the bonquet of &lt;br&gt;flowers and when you give her your flowers, Kayleigh decides to confront Tank&lt;br&gt;at his barracks.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Confront Tank at his barracks about his gift&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you arrive at Tank's barracks, you see Tank, denying that he was the &lt;br&gt;person that wanted you to give the flowers. Then, Tank walks in. Another Tank!&lt;br&gt;Then, the other tank runs out and you see that it was an alien imposter. You &lt;br&gt;have to sort out alien from human.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Check the Canyon and Dam areas for a way to reveal alien impersonators&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you go to the dam, you find that aliens what water. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Drench those aliens.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Pull out the drencher that you got from Jimmy earlier, and start firing! Once&lt;br&gt;you fire on an alien, they reveal their plans to destroy ... a dance club?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to the Dance Club to save it from the aliens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Opposite the factory is a dance club, with a music note on it. Enter it and&lt;br&gt;try to save it from the aliens. Its a trap and you are captured and place in &lt;br&gt;the salt mines. Talk to the Lord Mole. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Enlist the aid of Bigfoot and Optimum Alfred to defend the town. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Lord Mole suggests that you move to the north western corner and dig a &lt;br&gt;hole to escape. You will be at the dam and kill the aliens. When you dig out&lt;br&gt;of the hole, go to the factory and you will find Optimum Alfred who wants you&lt;br&gt;to do a favour for him.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clear the Factory of aliens, then speak to Optimum Alfred&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First of all, go to the Dance Club and kill all the aliens. That will complete&lt;br&gt;your hidden want. Then, do the same at the factory and speak to Optimum Alfred&lt;br&gt;who will guard his shop. Then talk to Bigfoot, he is near the tunnel that &lt;br&gt;leads to the power plant. After you talk to Bigfoot.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Return to Lord Mole&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head back through the tunnel you made and talk to him. After you talk to him&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Clear the Dam of aliens, then speak to Lord Mole&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Yep, were going on a water shooting spree. Kill every alien in sight. When you&lt;br&gt;finished with the aliens, report back to Lord Mole for the final kill.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stop the aliens at their ship near Jebediah Jerky's Ranch&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head over to the ranch and pull out your water pistol. Follow the bottom &lt;br&gt;pathway to the staircase and keep following the trail. Now, see that orb on &lt;br&gt;the ground? Use it and it will make you an alien. Now enter the ship. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Disable the aliens' weapon in the computer!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head over to the computer and rewire it and watch as the emperor blows it all&lt;br&gt;up. Watch the cutscene and that is the end of Season 1. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[5.01] Blackout!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars **&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A suspicious power failure at the Power Plant raises question of sabotage. Is&lt;br&gt;the guilty party one of your friends? Or are greater forces at work?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You start off by talking to Pete and Kayleigh with Pete having a crazy idea to&lt;br&gt;build a sundial with chewing gum when BOOM!, there is an explosion at the &lt;br&gt;power plant. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigate the explosion at the Nuclear Plant&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Time to break off the main task. Lets run the errand shall we. Head down to&lt;br&gt;Frankie's house. He wants you to deliver a black and white lava lamp to Luthor&lt;br&gt;so find Luthor and give it to him. He should be lurking at the dance club that&lt;br&gt;is near the mines. Then, head off to the Ranch and Jebediah wants to get some &lt;br&gt;green goo or whatnot. We'll have to come back later. Now head to the Nuclear &lt;br&gt;Power Plant. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bring 10 Nuclear Fuel Rods to Momma Hogg&lt;br&gt;Ask about town about the little insignia&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Once you finish the conversation, you will get a phone call that Kayleigh has&lt;br&gt;fallen ill. Head to the medicial centre near your house. After that little &lt;br&gt;chat, you return to your quest. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Look on the floor for those fuel rods. It are all over town so keep looking. &lt;br&gt;Go to the pawn shop later and talk to Ava. She will tell you what the insignia&lt;br&gt;is and tell you that Kent Hackett used to be Chaz Dastard. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Anyway, when you have the 10 Nuclear Fuel Rods, go back to the Medicial Centre&lt;br&gt;and give them to Momma Hogg. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With Kayleigh in a strange mood, you have to find Kent. He is in the warehouse&lt;br&gt;so go there.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigate the Warehouse&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go south to the warehouse where Kent is. Then you see something is wrong.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find a way past the locks and enter the Warehouse&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The vents normally open with picking the locks of the middle, then the left&lt;br&gt;and then the right. Failing to pick the right one will land you in prison. &lt;br&gt;When you finish picking the locks and enter, you will see all those fuel rods&lt;br&gt;that Kent is hoarding and you pass out. You end up in hospital and you are &lt;br&gt;told to find someone with Safety Suits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recover Kent's nuclear rod stockile&lt;br&gt;Get the radiation protection from Penelope Redd&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First, go to city hall and talk to Penelope. She says that she can make the &lt;br&gt;whole suit if you get her some Skin Cream and some thorium. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get the Skin Cream from Misty Waters&lt;br&gt;Find Thorium in the Salt Mines&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go to the salt mine and talk to Lord Mole. He tells you that you need to use&lt;br&gt;your Super Drencher on the salt walls to find the metal or gold. Then, go &lt;br&gt;around the mine and soak all the purple crystals. You will find the thorium in&lt;br&gt;the end. If not, keep looking. Now to get the skin cream. You will find Misty&lt;br&gt;in the Gothic Garden but you have to cough up about 1000 Simoleons. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you have finished, go back to City Hall and give the items to Penelope. &lt;br&gt;Then head to the warehouse. Then Commerical Break. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you come back from the commerical break, go and take all those nuclear &lt;br&gt;fuel rods. On the base of the warehouse, take the bottle of green goo and &lt;br&gt;give it to Jebediah, who wanted it earlier remember? That should complete the&lt;br&gt;hidden want for this episode. When you pick them all up, you recieve a phone&lt;br&gt;call that Kayleigh is better. So to the factory and give the 45 Nuclear Fuel&lt;br&gt;Rods and that will complete the episode.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Episode Complete! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[5.02] A Brand New Scent&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars **&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Kayleigh Wintercrest's sweet new perfume has surprising effects on the single&lt;br&gt;men of Strangetown.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You start off with you talking to Honest Jackson, who has fallen for Kayleigh&lt;br&gt;and her perfume. You get your orders after Jackson stops his love talk and&lt;br&gt;gives the orders&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Use the Pawn Shop Telescope to spy on the eligible bachelors of Strangetown. &lt;br&gt;Look at all those 6 locations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dust Vale - Tristian and Giuseppi talk about horses&lt;br&gt;Death Gulch - Nothing&lt;br&gt;Nuclear Plant - Emperor Xizzle talking out loud&lt;br&gt;Canyonero Grande - Nothing&lt;br&gt;Strangetown Zoo - Jebediah and Sancho talking about beetles&lt;br&gt;Wastelands - Auda and Ara&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After you finish spying, you have an new objective&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go see Honest Jackson at City Hall.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;But first, time to sidetrack. The hidden want is started by going to the right&lt;br&gt;room in the casino and talking to Misty Waters. Now, head outside and talk to &lt;br&gt;Penelope. Then, head to the Gothic Gardens to talk to Ara and head to Ara'a &lt;br&gt;House and talk to her. Then head back and talk to Misty and finish that want.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talk to Honest Jackson and he is basically making you take out all those other&lt;br&gt;competors to get to Kayleigh. First, we do the errand for this episode. So to&lt;br&gt;the Salt Mines and talk to Lord Mole. He will give you a map which you have to&lt;br&gt;give to Penelope. Give it to her and that will finish the errand for this &lt;br&gt;episode. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ruin Sancho's gift for Kayleigh&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When you head to the Zoo, you will find that Jebediah has information about&lt;br&gt;the beetle. Head to the ranch and talk to him. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ask Jeb what he knows about the Desert Fuzz Beetle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will find Jeb at his ranch. Talk to him. Jeb says that when dry, the &lt;br&gt;beetle is a cute thing. When wet however, it will be the nastiest thing &lt;br&gt;around. You know what to do.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Soak the Desert Fuzz Beetle with your Super Drencher&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head back to the zoo and go past Sancho. The beetle looks like a overgrown&lt;br&gt;mouse with blue fur. Time to drench it. When you drench it, it looks like a &lt;br&gt;overgrown green beetle. Too bad Sancho, better luck next time. After that, its&lt;br&gt;time to report to the head boss.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go see Honest Jackson at City Hall&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, go see him. He wants to ruin another person in the running. His mayor is&lt;br&gt;turning evil. And its terrorism!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ruin Adua's reservations at the Casino&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, head outside and go to the Casino. Talk to Pepper Pete and he'll say &lt;br&gt;that ruining the reservation is none of your business. Well, time to do it the&lt;br&gt;dirty way. Well, start a friendly conservation with him and he'll agree that &lt;br&gt;he'll stop Auda's reservation. Thats 2 down. Time to see the Mayor.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go see Honest Jackson at City Hall.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, the mayor has fallen for Kayleigh good and you have to ruin another &lt;br&gt;suitor, Tristian. Time to stop the horse ride. Well, talk to Tristian who is&lt;br&gt;at the ranch and he will say that Kayleigh hates the mess. Giuseppi is &lt;br&gt;cleaning the mess. Lets see what we can do. Giuseppi is still cleaning the&lt;br&gt;mess and confirms that Kayleigh will dump him if she sees the mess. Time to&lt;br&gt;make it dirty. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get manure from Jebediah Jerky to spoil the clean barn&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Well, talk to Jeb and he'll say that you can get some manure but not to get&lt;br&gt;greedy because he nearly didn't make his quota. You will be forced to play&lt;br&gt;Cattle Cleaner and you get paid for it. You get some manure. Time to spoil &lt;br&gt;the barn. Go to the barn and soil it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go see Honest Jackson at City Hall&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets see what he wants this time. He wants you to take down the final person,&lt;br&gt;the Emperor Xizzle. Lets head to the Emperor's last location, the Nuclear &lt;br&gt;Power Plant. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find out what Emperor Xizzle's plans are, and foil them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now you see a cut scene with the emperor who wants some make up&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Acquire Make-Up from warehouse. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets head down there. Talk to Kent and he will give you some expired make up&lt;br&gt;from 1986. Thats 19 YEARS!!! Lets head back to the Nuclear Plant and give him&lt;br&gt;some make up. Heh, he looks funny when he is invisible. Time to see the mayor&lt;br&gt;again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go see Honest Jackson at City Hall&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;I really think this guy should join the mafia. See that mayor and he wants her&lt;br&gt;phone number? Head outside and we cut to a commerical break. After the nice&lt;br&gt;game, you see Kayleigh and see wants to dump the perfume. You have to find &lt;br&gt;someone, who isn't made of flesh and bones to dump it. Time to see Alfred&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find the perfume in the Kayleigh's office at the Nuclear Plant&lt;br&gt;Ask Optimum Alfred to dispose of the perfume safety&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Maxis, spelling error. Anyway, head to the office and find the control panel. &lt;br&gt;Look for the hatch and you will find the perfume. Time to see Alfred and he&lt;br&gt;will dispose of it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Episode Complete!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[5.03] The New Cola&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars ***&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A delicious new cola with a secret formula has an unexpected effect on your &lt;br&gt;Sim. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okay, you start with Ava and Dusty arguing over a ladybug swarm. Then Tank &lt;br&gt;shows up with a 6 pack of Cherry Guava King Chug Chug cola. He drinks it and&lt;br&gt;you will be placed in a mini game. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;After that, you drink the cola and your SHRINK!?!, meanwhile, you see Kayleigh&lt;br&gt;at the power plant with an invoice of 500 nuclear fuel rods that are spent. &lt;br&gt;Now, you see that you have shrunk and you have to get to normal size.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find a way to return to normal size!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okay, follow the only path and Tank follows you. After a while you will see &lt;br&gt;some ladybugs. They look big and mean.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Defeat the Lady Bugs blocking the path&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You realise that water doesn't effect them so move to your left. Then you see&lt;br&gt;that there is some repellent on the floor. Fill up your drencher with it and &lt;br&gt;fire on those bugs. That should get rid of them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;More ladybugs on the trail so have your gun, I mean, water gun, I mean, bug&lt;br&gt;repellent gun equipped. Then, the lights go out, and Tank starts running.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find Tank!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;First of all, kill the ladybugs attack you. Then find Tank. If those ladybugs&lt;br&gt;attack you, you will lose performance. To regain that lost performance, there&lt;br&gt;will be some jelly beans on the floor that you can eat. Eat them and find Tank&lt;br&gt;before its too late. Kill those bugs and go down the rope.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;More ladybugs. They just don't quit do they? Kill those bugs and enter through&lt;br&gt;the wall. Kill those bugs guarding Tank and rescue him. Time for another job.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intimidate Tank into Fleeing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Switch to your hand and start to intimidate him. Once you finish, he gives in&lt;br&gt;and start moving north. Wow, we see the black ladybug. Lets kill her. Its he&lt;br&gt;hidden want but I kill her cause she looks ugly. Anyway when you finish the&lt;br&gt;bugs and attack her, she will retreat so kill the two ladybugs that she &lt;br&gt;summoned and she will come down again. Repeat until she dies and that is the&lt;br&gt;hidden want done. By the way, there is no errand for this round. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets go back to Tank and make him follow. Try being friendly or intimidate &lt;br&gt;him if he doesn't follow. Head up the shoelace rope and you will see that a &lt;br&gt;can of that cola has been spilt. Do we drink it? &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Investigate the Broken Bowl&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets drink the Glug Glug cola. There no harm in that is there? Drink it and &lt;br&gt;you will be back to normal. Then Tank makes Dusty drink the cola ...&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Episode Complete&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[5.04] There Was This Mummy&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When things start disappearing in Strangetown, your Sim vows to unravel the&lt;br&gt;cause.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars ****&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Buy the Mystery Plot Twist to unlock this episode.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You talk to Penelope about being a lion tamer and that she gave that up to&lt;br&gt;join the FBI. Then Luthor comes up saying that he lost his gold medal or that&lt;br&gt;someone stole it. You have to find it since Penelope says this isn't a &lt;br&gt;Federal matter.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find Luthor's gold medal&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head outside the dance club and you will see Bigfoot, who says a toilet paper&lt;br&gt;man took his favourite teddy bear *sigh* guess we have to find that too.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find Bigfoot's teddy bear&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head off to the main town and you will see that Honest Jackson says that &lt;br&gt;Penelope has been captured. Well, that is another thing we have to find. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Find Penelope Redd&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Go down the road and talk to Giuseppi. He will talk about the amount of sand&lt;br&gt;on the road. Lets dig it up and see. Down the road, is Ara. She says that she&lt;br&gt;hears a large sound in the desert about 7 pm and 5 am in the morning. Time&lt;br&gt;to investigate.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head down the cliff road near the Ziggurat and you will see a mummy. He says&lt;br&gt;he can't be scared. Lets just see about that.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intimidate the mummy to get into the Ziggurat&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Intimidate him. Then he lets you into his home. You find the gold medal and &lt;br&gt;then some blood sucking flies come along. You need to get rid of them&lt;br&gt;to rescue Penelope. Lets find a creature expert.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Get some strong insect repellent&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Time for the hidden want and errand. Note that the mummy follows you. Head to&lt;br&gt;the warehouse where Kent says it is on fire. Well, use your Super Drencher to&lt;br&gt;stop the fire. Hidden Want complete.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Head up to the town and Luthor will find his medal and all is good and well. &lt;br&gt;The errand is from Kayleigh, who is in the Saloon and wants you to deliver a&lt;br&gt;radioactive couch to Frankie. Thats the errand for this level.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Now, according to the mummy, we have to find a creature expert. Looks like &lt;br&gt;Sancho is our man. He can get some repellent, but he needs !?! 2000 Simoleons,&lt;br&gt;thats a lot. Time to start earning some money. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Give him the money and you get some repellent. Now to spray the flies.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Spray the tsetse flies in the Ziggurat&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets head there and spray some flies. Kill the flies and advance further into&lt;br&gt;the home. Well, you see that Penelope is missing. Head outside and there is&lt;br&gt;Penelope. Seems she got out alive. You are about to see the mayor, when its &lt;br&gt;time for a Commerical Break. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We are back and we are talking to the mayor. The mayor seems happy to find&lt;br&gt;that Penelope is back. Then Bigfoot wants his teddy. Seems like we have to &lt;br&gt;keep moving. Mummy can tell if we are far or near so lets go. The bear is &lt;br&gt;near the ship, where the guy sells books. Is south of him, near the cactus. &lt;br&gt;Dig at the pile of sand. Then you will give it to Bigfoot and thats the end.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Episode Complete!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------------&lt;br&gt;[6.01] Triassic Trouble&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Oops! Honest Jackson has misplaced a dinosaur. Or, rather, its bones. Your Sim&lt;br&gt;can help him recover the pieces. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stars ***&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You are at the Saloon, when Jimmy wants you to go to Frankie and forgets what&lt;br&gt;he is about to say. Lets head to Frankie's house&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Talk to Frankie Fusilli at his house.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets get the errand first. Talk to Pepper Pete and he will give you an invoice&lt;br&gt;to give to Sancho. Lets do that and get the errand out of the way. Sancho will&lt;br&gt;be at the zoo. While you are at the zoo, talk to Sancho and he goes on about&lt;br&gt;a Megalodon Jawbone and how he wants to see one. Go outside and go near the &lt;br&gt;bridge. Go to the side of the bridge and there is a patch of firt you can dig&lt;br&gt;at. Dig there for the Jawbone. Then, go inside and give it to Sancho. That &lt;br&gt;will give you the hidden want for this episode. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;With that all said and done, lets head over the Frankie's House. Go in and &lt;br&gt;talk to him. Ara will be there and you decide to dig up Jeb's ranch. You can't&lt;br&gt;let him spot you says Frankie.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Dig up all the dinosaur bones on Jeb's Ranch.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lets ride there and dig it all up. Jeb won't be around so just dig up all &lt;br&gt;those patches of sand. We have to pillage the sand and get the bones and sell&lt;br&gt;it for a tidy profit. There are 5 seperate bones to collect on Jeb's farm so&lt;br&gt;make sure you collect them all. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;You will find a Dinosaur Tail Bone, a Dinosaur Spine Bone, a Dinosaur Skull&lt;br&gt;Bone, a Dinosaur Rib Bone and a Dinosaur Leg Bone.</othernotes>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="The Sims" id="4" priority="Noteworthy" min="0" max="0">
            <description>(April Fools character) Bella Goth is a sim from The Sims franchise. She speaks entirely in simlish. Other characters presumably do not speak simlish.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Ish knee oobatay?" id="6" priority="Prompt" min="0" max="8">
            <description>(April fools character) Bella is asking... something, in Simlish. Just make something up in response!</description>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <responses>
        <response id="2" opponent="yuno_uno" opponentId="167" />
        <response id="3" opponent="yuno_uno" opponentId="175" />
        <response id="11" opponent="petra" opponentId="169" />
        <response id="19" opponent="chie" opponentId="30" />
        <response id="20" opponent="kyouko_toshinou" opponentId="91" />
    </responses>
    <labels>
        <label id="1" label="" folder="Target Tags" sort="0" />
        <label id="2" label="" folder="Prompts" sort="0" />
        <label id="5" label="" folder="Target Tags" sort="0" />
        <label id="7" label="" folder="Target Tags" sort="0" />
        <label id="8" label="" folder="Target Tags" sort="0" />
        <label id="9" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="10" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="11" label="" folder="Prompts" sort="0" />
        <label id="12" label="7+ Rounds; error messages" folder="" sort="0" />
        <label id="13" label="" folder="Target Tags" sort="0" />
        <label id="14" label="" folder="Target Tags" sort="0" />
        <label id="15" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="16" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="17" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="18" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="19" label="" folder="Prompts" sort="0" />
        <label id="20" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="21" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="22" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
        <label id="23" label="" folder="Targets" sort="0" />
    </labels>
    <nextId>23</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="bellagoth_yuno_stiffyResp" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="bubblePos" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="chie_steak" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="ish_knee_oobatay" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="kirigiri" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="last_friday_night" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="petra_speechExplainedResp" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_ag" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_criticaldarling" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_criticaldarlingc" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_heris" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_jim" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_kirigiri" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_kyouko" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_mariS" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_slycooper" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="target_trixie" />
    </markers>
</metadata>
