<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.9 at 7:33:03 AM on December 09, 2023. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.9</version>
    <first>Roll</first>
    <last>Caskett</last>
    <label>Roll</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>29</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="singlet" generic="leotard" position="both" type="major" />
        <clothing name="hat" generic="hat" position="head" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="shorts" generic="shorts" position="lower" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="jacket" generic="jacket" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>



    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hello there! How are you? Are you ready to play?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hey! Hello! How are you feeling? Prepared to play?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Oh, hello! Thanks for having me! I hope you're prepared to play!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="11">
                <test expr="~background~" value="throne room" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">It would be... wrong to take some of this treasure, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="12">
                <test expr="~background.bathing~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="444">Playing here is pretty convenient. There's a good chance we'll want to wash up after all this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="13">
                <test expr="~background.moon~" cmp="&gt;=" value="crescent" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Isn't the moon lovely? It's also very, very, very far away.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Looking up at the moon used to make me a little lonely. Now it just makes me feel kind of accomplished!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="15">
                <test expr="~background.dark~" value="true" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Are we going to need flashlights?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">The darkness makes it... kinda sultry, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" gender="male" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I guess I should have figured it would be mostly guys...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Well... I guess gramps does say I'm one of the boys...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Oh, outnumbered by men. Just like back at home...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3-" gender="female" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I thought having some girls here would relax me, but now I'm just thinking you could be checking me out too.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I think I'd be a little uncomfortable if it was just guys here. </state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I guess this will be kind of like looking at the dirty magazines Mega Man has under his bed. It's all girls, but I don't really hate looking through them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Is this everyone? I think there's room for a couple more people.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Are we just going to have three in? I think that could be fun.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">A small group wouldn't be so bad, but a big group might be more comfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="4" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">The more the merrier, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">So is this the whole group or are we waiting for one more person?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Is this everyone now? Just the four of us?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="5" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Oh, this is good! I think I'll feel a lot more comfortable in a big group!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It looks like everyone is here now! Shouldn't we get going?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">It should be a lot of fun with lots of people! Does this mean we're ready to start now?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" id="51">
                <condition role="other" character="yuelia" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">So... that's a butterfly, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">This isn't the sort of thing I usually do, but it should be pretty exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I'm Roll, if you didn't know. I'm sure we're about to get to know each other very well.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Okay, let's get going! I know I'm ready to go!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I should probably just stick with these, right?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I can just use what I already have on hand!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">No, let's not get greedy! I'll just keep these cards.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Oh, there's no way I'm pushing my luck more than this!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">W-wait! Actually, let me just keep all these!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I guess I'll exchange these ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Can I get ~cards.text~ new ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~? That would be great!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I'm going to do ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~ this time, if that's okay.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Two? No, four? No... ~cards.text~, yes? Yes.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Honestly, I'm sort of just guessing here.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Let's see if I can make anything from what you've got!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm not sure I can salvage this...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I hope this is worth the risk...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">This just needs a bit of a tune-up.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I'm going to need ~cards.text~ this time and a good ~cards.text~ at that!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What are the odds someone else has what I'm looking for?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I'll give you ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~, but there's one I really would like in return!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Oh! Okay! ~Cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~, please!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Gosh, I don't even know this time...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh, what to do, what to do?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Hm... probably shouldn't overthink it.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Maybe it'll just work itself out?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I sort of like my chances. ~Cards.text~ this time.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm... wwweeeeeeell...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">My gut tells me I should get rid of ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">What are the chances I can actually improve this?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Um... I need ~cards.text~ very specific ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~ back...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">~Cards.text~? I guess?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Sometimes it's hard deciding how many to give up...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-stretch.png">I hope everything works out this time. I've got a good feeling about this.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Looks like it's smooth sailing for me!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">This is a lot of fun! It's a little weird, but I think I was craving a little excitement.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Are you doing okay? You're not getting distracted, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Okay, I'm all set! Get ready to read 'em and weep!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Card games aren't that hard for me. Just like engineering and cooking, it's all about putting the right pieces together.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">How is it going over there? Did you get the hand you wanted?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Even when it looks like the coast is clear, it's best to be careful.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">If I can fly the Flutter through pirate attacks while making sure Mega Man doesn't fall off the deck, I can certainly stay focused on this game no matter what happens!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Looks like I've gotten this taken care of all by myself!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">I don't see anything I need to worry about here!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Not too shabby for a grease monkey, eh?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hey, if you can't take the heat then get out from under the car hood!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You don't need any help fine tuning your hand, do you, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Always make sure you show up with the right tool for the job. Let me show you what I mean...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I think I've lost enough for now. Somebody else should get to have a turn!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Alright, no more mistakes! Now I've got this whole thing figured out!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Nope, not this time! I'm fully prepared for whatever you have!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Might as well get comfy!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">It's satisfying to put something together that'll work!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Oh, I'm not finished quite yet! A spotter can always find a way out of a sticky situation!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Looks like you've got trouble up ahead!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I've got a nose for treasure, and it's telling me we're about to be onto something!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Looks like someone is going to be getting a little upgrade to their wardrobe.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I'm about to bust this wide open!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright, back at the wheel! You'd better hold onto your pants!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Nope! You're not going to find anything this time!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I could still win this completely by accident, but I'd need someone else to have the accident.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Sometimes you just have to dive in and hope for the best!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="30">I'm glad we're not playing for zenny. Money is tight enough as it is.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I think I'd rather see everyone naked than be naked. That's normal, right?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Gosh, I haven't had this much excitement in a long time. Not without risking my or Mega Man's life, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Maybe I should try being more careful with my cards...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hope this doesn't throw a wrench in things...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Looks like my chances are better than zero!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png" oneShotId="31">It's nice just to have a moment where I don't have to worry about pirates or reaverbots.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Maybe I should have brought something to tinker with...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't worry about me! I've got myself covered!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="36">I wonder what Mega Man is up to right now. He might be better equipped to come out on top...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="37">Hm, I wonder if it would be difficult to build a robot that deals cards...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="38">A good spotter is always on the lookout for danger! In my professional opinion... we're probably safe here!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="725">I figured coming here would be a good experience for me. Sometimes life on the Flutter can be... well... unstimulating?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1325">Statistical analysis is not my area of expertise, but I am good at getting useful stuff from junk! Maybe I've got a knack for this game?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Uh-oh. I think I might have messed up.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh! I better watch out! </state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I've got a bad feeling about this round...</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hey! What's the big idea with these cards?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Sorry, I wasn't able to make anything good with the cards I was given.</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">So to~background.time~ might not be my ~background.time~. </state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Wait a minute! How did I mess that up? What happened?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I hope you did well, ~player~. That would at least make one of us.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Well, even junk is worth something...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Of course. Right when I need smooth sailing, I hit turbulence.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Where did that come from? What happened? This doesn't look good for me.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I did the best I could with the materials I was given.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Mega Man wouldn't sweat losing so much, would he?</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">How much is it going to set me back to get these cards upgraded?</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">I know useless scrap when I see it...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'd prefer not to just be barely scraping by...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I pushed my luck a bit too far on that one. I figured it would be worth the risk at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Losing wouldn't be so bad, right? Hm, maybe I shouldn't give up yet.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Uh-oh. I... uh, think I messed up again.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I might just end up crashing and burning...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Maybe I need to go back to the drawing board with my strategy here...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I don't know how I messed this up. It's not like it's rocket science! And I &lt;i&gt;know&lt;/i&gt; rocket science!</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">I guess there really is not accounting for luck as a variable.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Ugh, this is embarrassing. You'd think I couldn't count up to three or something.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Yeah, this wouldn't be the first time something I put together blew up in my face.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm getting so excited I can hardly focus on what I'm doing...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Ah-ha ha... whoops!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Sometimes you have to take a leap of faith... and sometimes that doesn't work out at all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="nagatoro_deny" />
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">You can't actually be that delusional, Don Patch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="35">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="nickname_prompt" />
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="MegaKuma" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">W-what? Are you making fun of me?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="nagatoro_deny" />
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Naga_Roll_Deny" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">H-huh? What? That never happened! D-did it? Stop spreading lies!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="36">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" stage="3-9" sayingMarker="kumatora_ask_favfoods" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">It's so hard to pick! I really like apricots myself, especially baked into a pie. I bake them all the time to share with gramps and Mega Man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="65">
                <condition role="other" character="aoba" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Aoba_Q&amp;A_Cats" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">We had a cat on the Flutter for a while! She ended up having kittens, so it became a bit more than we could manage. They were all so cute, but we took them someplace they could have owners who would take real good care of them!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="67">
                <condition role="other" character="lucina" stage="1-8" sayingMarker="Lucina_YoungerHelp" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">I would teach myself rocket science. Make sure I had it down forwards and backwards &lt;i&gt;before&lt;/i&gt; having to cooperate with the most difficult person in the world.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="69">
                <condition role="other" character="cheryl" stage="3-5" sayingMarker="cheryl_journaling" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Oh, yeah! I've kept a diary for years! I think it really helps me organize my thoughts! It's good to check in with yourself whenever something stressful happens.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="5-6" sayingMarker="roll_turnon" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="leon_resp_turnon2">Hee hee, I like the way you talk to me, but in all honesty I'm not so sure what to do. I just know if you told me what to do, I'd be very excited to play along...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="7" sayingMarker="roll_turnon" />
                <state img="#-lusty.png" marker="leon_resp_turnon3">... If I could see how I turn you on... that'd be hot...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" stage="0-4" sayingMarker="roll_turnon" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="leon_resp_turnon0">Hmm... losing some of that clothing would be a good start. I mean, it's only fair!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="other" character="chun-li" stage="0-5" sayingMarker="one_on_one" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">W-wait! I-I'm not much of a fighter!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">H-hey! Hold on! I don't fight! I just have a supporting role!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">W-we're still just playing cards, right? I don't want to fight you!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="16" totalRounds="5-10">
                <condition role="opp" character="monika" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Monika_weird">Does anyone else feel a little weird? I feel... a little weird? I don't know how else to put it.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Monika_weird">.... Huh... what was... I guess it was nothing. Weird.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Monika_weird">Something is... just slightly off, right? I mean, this place is weird normally, but this is a different weird... a weirder weird? Maybe?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="64">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_pampering" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Senko_PamperA">I don't need much, really. It's nice to have someone who can cook and draw a bath for me when I've been in the workshop all day.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Senko_PamperB">It might be a little shallow, but I do like getting surprise gifts. It just makes me feel like... like even when we're not together he's thinking about me...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Senko_PamperC">Sometimes I feel like just having around in my pajamas all day. I feel kind of bad since Mega Man does all the housework on those days, but I really appreciate that he'll let me take a day off like that.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Senko_PamperD">Well, I'm not big on going to spas or getting massages or anything like that. I find my work therapeutic, really. Sometimes if everyone just lets me work in peace, it makes me feel like they care enough to give me space!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="34">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="nickname_prompt" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I don't think there's anything wrong with your name! I don't mind saying it at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="favorite_instrument" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png">The only instruments I'm good with are the instruments on my spotter panel. I'm not really musically inclined, unfortunately.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="kum_superpowerA" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I haven't really given that sort of thing too much thought, Kumatora. If there's something Mega Man or I can't do, I usually build something to help us get it done. I'm not sure what I would need a superpower for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="kum_superpowerB" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">A superpower? Gosh, I don't know. Maybe something to help keep Mega Man safe? Like I could sense danger for him? My spotting equipment sort of already does that though, so maybe that power would be wasted on me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="66">
                <condition role="other" character="reimu" sayingMarker="Reimu_GetRichQuick" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">I wish I knew how to make some fast money. Unfortunately, digging is kind of a tricky business. You just have to cross your fingers and hope you find a big refractor or something like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8" id="70">
                <condition role="other" character="nagisa" sayingMarker="nagisa_beach_hiding_place" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">H-huh? Could that happen?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="77">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="modern_amenities" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Senko_AmenetiesA">... I'm pretty sure "grenade launcher" isn't the answer you're looking for...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Senko_AmenetiesB">I'd sure have a lot of trouble getting my work done without a plasma torch! It's more of a lifesaver than a time saver!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Senko_AmenetiesC">Living on an airship, the newspaper doesn't always get delivered on time. Thanks to the TV though, we can get all the news we need wherever we go!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Senko_AmenetiesD">My whole toolbox is full of stuff like that! No matter which of our little conveniences break down, I can just fix it good as new! Knowing I can do &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; is comforting!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_backgrond" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Senko_resp_BG">A demigod? I guess I shouldn't be so surprised...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Senko_resp_BG">Kitsune? Demigods? ... Oh, I probably shouldn't think about it too much.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_pamper" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Senko_resp_pamper">I sort of wish I could be that selfless... but if I did everything for free we wouldn't have food or a place to live...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Senko_resp_pamper">I'd love to be that accommodating, but I can't do everything for free. It takes a lot of money to maintain an airship and good scrap doesn't come cheap!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_age" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Senko_resp_age">800?! Should... shouldn't you be &lt;i&gt;taller?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Senko_resp_age">You can't really be 800, right? Even a machine would be completely broken down if it was that old...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_shrines" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Senko_resp_shrines">Does that really work? Someone offers up something valuable and then you're just... here?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Senko_resp_shrines">Maybe I need a shrine. People could make offerings to me and I could fix their stuff...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="senko" sayingMarker="senko_punishment" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Senko_resp_punishment">I don't know what Tron does to the Servbots in her torture room, but my answer is I definitely don't want &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Senko_resp_punishment">Whatever my punishment is, I just don't want to clean the bathroom...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="other" character="cammy_white" sayingMarker="one_on_one" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">This feels a lot more hostile all of a sudden...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I don't think I like how Cammy is staring at me...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">You're not going to hurt me... right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="other" character="juri" sayingMarker="one_on_one" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Why did it have to be me and her left?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I really feel like she might hurt me!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh no, Juri is looking even scarier than usual!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="rainbow_mika" sayingMarker="one_on_one" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Please promise we're just going to stick to cards!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Please don't break my bones!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="90">
                <condition role="other" character="kyouko_toshinou" sayingMarker="D_SexyPose" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1326">Well, if confidence is sexy, then that's certainly a sexy pose!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1327">It's not the kind of pose I've ever seen in a magazine, Kyouko...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1328">Kyouko, if you were taking this more seriously you might have some more clothes left...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1330">I mean... it's not &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/i&gt; sexy...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1329">You know... I sort of wish I had the sort of confidence to just strike a pose...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-8" oneShotId="18">
                <test expr="~background.surface~" value="grass" />
                <state img="#-stretch.png">When was the last time I was barefoot in the grass? I need to get out of the Flutter more!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Hmm, feeling the grass between your toes... you don't get any of that flying around the ocean.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" oneShotId="20">
                <test expr="~background.temperature~" value="cold" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Sort of cold around here, huh? Did the rest of you notice that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="10" />
                <state img="#-stretch.png">It's almost a little boring when you don't lose, but I bet I won't feel quite the same when I do have to strip!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">If this keeps up, I'm going to get a big head over all this! Better step it up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="10" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Feels like my luck has finally turned around! Oh! But I shouldn't say that out loud, right? That's bad luck!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm surprised I'm still in this. It sure felt like things were headed downhill before!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="20" />
                <state img="#-wave.png">Gosh, I'm feeling nearly unbeatable! Come on! Knock me off of my high horse already!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">If being a pilot has taught me anything, it's that when you've been sailing along for this long without incident you're about to hit turbulence!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="20" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">How did things end up like this? I thought I was going to lose for sure before! Now... now I'm starting to think I'm going to win!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Has anyone else noticed I haven't lost at all for a while? I hope not. I'd hate to jinx it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" oneShotId="17">
                <condition count="2" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright! It's just you and me! No hard feelings no matter how it goes, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">No need to get competitive just because we're the only ones left! We should just continue to have fun, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="37" oneShotId="1" totalRounds="5" priority="0">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="WheresData">By any chance, has anyone seen a little monkey running around? I can't say for sure, but it's possible our robot Data followed me here. He has a weird habit of showing up wherever we go.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="WheresData">This is probably going to sound crazy, but could you guys let me know if you see a monkey? It's possible that it's Data, our... uh, pet, I guess? Sometimes we go somewhere and he's &lt;i&gt;already there&lt;/i&gt;, so I'm worried he followed me here somehow.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6" priority="0">
                <condition status="alive" role="opp" character="human" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Be careful, ~player~. You never know what's going to happen in this kind of game.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I guess I should be safe this time. What about you, ~player~? Do you think you can make out okay?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright, ~player~. Let's just do our best!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0" id="72">
                <condition role="other" character="yuno_uno" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="yuno_rollcasket_s0a" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="yuno_resp0_1">No... well, yes, well... not bikes &lt;i&gt;exclusively&lt;/i&gt;. Really, I'll work on anything with moving parts.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="yuno_resp0_1">I haven't done much work on bikes. I mostly work on my airship, but honestly I'll work on anything mechanical.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yae" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="yae_resp1_1">Sort of? It wasn't all that large, but I did build a rocket to go to the moon and back...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="kaz_resp1_1">I think the Flutter is bigger than you're imagining it. We all have our own rooms, plus a kitchen, two bathrooms, and a living room! There's also the engine room and my R&amp;D workshop.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="1">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="roll_caskett0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="revy_resp0_1">Are you using my name as a pun to brag about &lt;i&gt;killing people?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="2">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="roll_caskett0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">Well, what can I say? I've loved working on machines ever since I was little! It's a good thing too because our ship needs a lot of attention.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">Sometimes it's a lot of work, but I do enjoy working on the ship and building new weapons. It's all stuff that has to get done anyway, so I'm just lucky I find it so fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="3">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="roll_caskett0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">It depends on what I can get my hands on. Most days I'm just doing repairs and maintenance on the ship, but sometimes Mega Man will bring me some scrap to build him some armor or weapons.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">I don't really have the time or resources to work on extra projects. Maintaining the Flutter eats up most of our cash. The only other thing I do regularly is make weapons and armor for Mega Man from the scrap he digs up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="5">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Roll_MegaMan1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="mari_resp0_1">B-b-b-boyfriend?! N-no! No? Of course not! H-he's like my brother! I mean, I love him, but it's totally platonic! There's been some sexually charged moments between us, b-b-b-but we haven't even kissed! Not that I want that! But I don't not want it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="6">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll01" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_1">For me, it's gotta be the Blade Arm attachment I made for Mega Man's armor! It generates a concentrated beam of plasma that can cut through steel like it was tissue paper!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="7">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll11" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_1">Well, I &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; do something like that, but I'm pretty sure you wouldn't want me to.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_1">That was be entirely possible, but... but are you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; sure you want that? I'm not so sure you are...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="8">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll31" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="nagatoro_resp3_1">Ah... well... um... that sort of stuff is expensive, but I've always got plenty of scrap parts and material around...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" marker="maria_resp0_1">Not to brag, but I'm pretty handy in the kitchen too. Cooking, baking, you name it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="maria_resp1_1">Well, that's his name. It's the one I gave to him, actually.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="maria_resp2_1">Mega Man is the one who goes into the ruins during our dig outs. He assumes a lot of the risk, puts himself in harm's way. He does lots for us and me personally.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="maria_resp3_1">Unfortunately, I don't. I did spend a lot of time with Tron while we were building our rocket to rescue Mega Man, but there's just no getting along with her. She's nothing but a huge pain butt!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="maria_resp4_1">I guess I am a little nervous. It's just, you're so beautiful, Maria. Next to you, I-I'm not so sure anyone would care about me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="maria_resp5_1">Winning would be nice, but it wouldn't be the worst thing in the world to lose, right? It might even be fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="kaz_resp0_1">Oh, I was worried people might think these clothes are weird.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_1">Yes, I am. Sorry, that must seem pretty boring to someone who can do magic...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Bobobo_DASH1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_1">Yes, yes, I'm aware my name is also a word. Every time I think I've heard them all, someone comes up with something new and embarrassing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="kaz_resp2_1">Title? No, that's just his name. Mega Man Volnutt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="kaz_resp3_1">Sometimes we find treasure, but anything that isn't actually useful never turns out to be very valuable. Mostly we're just after refractors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="kaz_resp4_1">I'm sure you know the answer to that, Kaz. I wouldn't feel too bad about it; I don't exactly dislike you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_1" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="kaz_resp5_1">I'm not so sure I could do that. I'm perfectly happy with my work now. Being in front of a camera sounds like it would be a little scary.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_1">Do you know who left them behind? A lot of the records we find left behind are pretty cryptic. It was a long time before we really understood anything about who made the ruins.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_1">That's kind of a long story, but the gist of it is he had to go. If he hadn't gone, it might've been the end of life on the planet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_1">The underlying principles of low orbit flight are not so complex that travel to the moon is unfeasible, but when &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; refuses to listen to &lt;i&gt;good sense&lt;/i&gt; and just &lt;i&gt;messes up everything&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_1">I thought I was going to be a nervous wreck, but I'm having a lot more fun than I thought I would!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_1" />
                <state img="#-lusty.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_1">I'm not so sure. I can't stop think about losing and how good it would feel to touch myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_HandsDown1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_1">Rock? Rock who? Did you mean Mega Man?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_Chemistry1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_1">Not literally "any two things." That should probably be obvious, but... well, I guess not to someone like you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_WigOutDigOut1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_1">What's a "robot master?"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_BoBonne1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_1">Look, I'm sure I didn't make it easy for her to get along with me, but she's so stubborn and stuck-up I don't know who could get along with her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_PunAndPunishment1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_1">Is that a come on or are you just hungry?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="21">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_ms0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="dwight_resp0_1">Yeah! Absolutely! Did you have a mechanical question?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="dwight_resp0_1">It sounds like you have a mechanical question for me, Dwight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="23">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_ms1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="dwight_resp1_1">So you worked as a mechanic too, huh? I've always worked with machines. Runs in my family! At least, the last few generations.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="dwight_resp1_1">It's always nice to meet a fellow mechanic, even a former one. I've been working with machines my whole life! It's kind of a family tradition!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="24">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_ms2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="dwight_resp2_1">Really? I can sorta imagine you in a denim jumpsuit and all covered in oil. Oil is the universal uniform of &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; mechanics.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="dwight_resp2_1">That's pretty standard for a lot of mechanics, I think. It is pretty easy to imagine you in your little jumpsuit with a wrench in hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="rollc_greet" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="kumatora_resp0_1">Oh, no, they're not for fighting. I work with heavy machinery, so I wear them for protection. I wouldn't want something chopping off my toes, after all!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="kumatora_resp0_1">While I'm sure it would hurt if I kicked you with these, they're actually reinforced for my protection. I don't need a big 'ol piece of sheet metal smashing my poor toes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="40">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="roll_caskett1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="jura_resp1_1">I don't know how we would get by without Mega Man! Gramps is too old to go down into ruins and I'm no good at fighting. Also, Mega Man cleans the toilets, so we're really lucky we found him!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="jura_resp1_1">Oh, Mega Man more than pulls his own weight. Honestly, we'd be lost without him! He's an essential part of our digging operations and just a real member of our family!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="41">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="roll_caskett1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="meia_resp1_1">Oh, we sure have! We've found out more than I really ever cared to know about our history. I could stand to forget some of the things we learned!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="meia_resp1_1">Yeah, we sure found out some things. We found out some really, really, &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; troubling things about the past...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon01" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="leon_resp0_1">Yeah, that's me. Wait, you know Mega Man? Huh? How? From where? What? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon11" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="leon_resp1_1">Oh, but I do have a guy back at home. Guys plural, in fact! There's Gramps and Data and Mega Man too, of course!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon21" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="leon_resp2_1">Oh, I love motorcycles! I sort of wish I had one, but they're not very practical for transporting equipment. I did build one once, but I had to disassemble it and turn it back into a pitching machine.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon31" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="leon_resp3_1">Oh... well, strictly speaking I'm not &lt;i&gt;exactly&lt;/i&gt; human, but as far as I know I'm not any different than one! I'm still an organic lifeform!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="76">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="roll_caskett1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="revy_resp1_1">I don't think about what happens if we fail. I just do what has to be done to make sure we all come out okay in the end. After all is said and done, it's good that the pirates made it out okay. When we needed their help, they did step up for us.</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="revy_resp1_1">As a spotter, I don't waste time thinking about the worst case scenario. I just focus on doing everything I can to make sure we all make it out in one piece. And keeping the pirates alive hasn't been all bad. Sometimes they come and help us out. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="79">
                <condition role="other" character="suzuya" sayingMarker="roll_00" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="suzuya_resp0_1">Of course! Whenever we've needed to borrow a boat, we always end up with ones that either barely runs or doesn't run, but I've never had any trouble getting them back into shape!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="80">
                <condition role="other" character="elphaba" sayingMarker="roll_mechanic" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="elphaba_resp0_1">Well, I fix and build machines. That's really all there is to it. Do you not have mechanics where you come from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon41" />
                <state img="#-lusty.png" marker="leon_resp4_1">You don't have to wonder. The thought of showing you has me... I just want to show you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon51" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="leon_resp5_1">Talk is nice... but I want more than talk from you...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="roll0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="nami_resp0_1">Well, for me working on machines is just a lot of fun! I like taking all the little pieces, seeing how they fit and mesh, and then watching them all work together.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="nami_resp0_1">I think it's a lot of fun to build machines and stuff like that! There's a lot of satisfaction that comes with putting something together and then watching it work and move all on its own! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="91">
                <condition role="other" character="queenie" sayingMarker="roll_queenie_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="queenie_resp0_1">Of course, ask away! I can't promise I'll know for sure, but I'll do my best!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="queenie_resp0_1">Hey, if you've got mechanical questions, then I'm all ears! I'll give it my best shot!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="sofia" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="sofia_resp0_1">Really? Another girl mechanic? That's awesome! It's like wherever I go I'm usually the only one! This is great!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yae" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="yae_resp0_1">Ah, gosh, I'm not all that special. I do my best most days, but even I get stumped sometimes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="93">
                <condition role="other" character="lysithea" sayingMarker="ask_roll_machinesS" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="lysithea_respM_1">Oh, that's probably motor oil. My clothes are probably covered in it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="94">
                <condition role="other" character="lysithea" sayingMarker="ask_roll_magicS" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="lysithea_respK_1">What?! Me?! A mage?! N-no, I'm just a mechanic! I can't do magic! I'm pretty sure magic isn't real... normally.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2" id="95">
                <condition role="other" character="lysithea" sayingMarker="ask_roll_worldS" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="lysithea_respW_1">Well, these are my work clothes. They're just supposed to keep me from getting too dirty and let me move around comfortably. Not very stylish, but I've never been very flashy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="sheena_resp0_1">I take a lot of machines apart too... and even a lot of the stuff I build ends up being used to wreck machines too...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="sheena_resp3_1">That's fine, Sheena, but experience with what, exactly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="sheena_resp1_1">I'm not really cut out for combat. Most I ever do in a fight is try and drive us out of there. Also, his name is Mega &lt;i&gt;Man&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sofia" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="sofia_resp1_1">Is that the impression you get? I'm closer to him than anyone else! I don't think we fit into any sort of neat category...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <condition status="alive" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="661">Oh, please don't let me choke right at the very end!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="662">You got me again! I was just starting to think I might have this nailed down...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="663">Not again! I miss having backup...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="732">I've got a really &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; bad feeling about this all of a sudden...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3-6" />
                <condition count="2" status="alive" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="680">Oh, why is there no one else here to take a turn...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="681">Gosh, I guess there's a reason you're still in the game..</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="682">Am I just doing badly or are you just getting super lucky?!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="686">Did I jinx myself by thinking I was going to win? I'm still sorta close...</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png" oneShotId="753">What are you doing? It's all one-sided all of a sudden!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="22">Me? Again? Oh no! How did I let this happen?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="23">Stripping is embarrassing enough on its own, so why did I have to go and lose like that a second time?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="646">There's not much I can do if the rest of you are going to be so lucky each time...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="768">Two in a row? No, it's fine. Just bad luck I guess...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3-6" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="28">How? Again? You would tell me if I was doing something wrong, right?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="29">Apparently I'm the one who needs a spotter in here...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="26">Gosh! You guys are really good at this game!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="27">It doesn't seem fair for me to lose so many times in a row. I'm not sure how I could have prevented it!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="688">Doesn't somebody else want to take a turn?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="773">I'm in real trouble here! Where's help when you need it?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">That's too bad, but I had to get started sometime.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">It would be a total waste if I didn't strip even once. I'm sure you all feel the same!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Well, that's okay. It's not like I'm in any danger of losing right now.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Oh, I could go for another one! It's no big deal, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Oh, I'm not worried. I've been in bigger jams before!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Sometimes you can't help but come up empty. No point in stressing about it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Oh, I knew I shouldn't have gotten too overconfident. It's not over until it's over.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I... might not come away from all these so squeaky clean, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confused.png">And I was so close too! I was just thinking I might not have to take anything else off.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Yes... well... I was kind of sort of starting to hope I would win without having to show my... y'know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Ha ha, well, it would be a lot more embarrassing if I was the only one that was naked.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Yeah, this one isn't really the loss I'm sweating over...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Oh well, no reason to get bent out of shape. I just gotta keep up!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Taking one hit isn't a big deal. That's what the "armor" is for!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-wave.png">Don't count me out yet! I can pull through in a jam if I need to!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">A little turbulence never stopped me! Just you wait and see!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">If I can land the Flutter when she's only got one engine working, I could still win this even without my pants. </state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Oh, I've pulled off bigger miracles with less material than this. I can handle it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Uh-oh. I'm starting to think I'm going to be one of the big losers here...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Now things are looking pretty dicey...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">That's not good. I was hoping I had at least one more round before I had to take this off...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm not feeling so confident about winning anymore...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Oh, this is so embarrassing. At least I won't be the only one...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Well... could be worse, right? Right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Darn, I was hoping to hold out just a little longer before I lost. </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I saw this happening a little later in my head...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Am I missing something? I feel like I should be doing a lot better...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Luck is a much bigger part of this than I anticipated...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Oh, well, that's okay! I can't let it get me down! Maybe my luck will turn around!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">No reason to get bent out of shape! If I have some bad luck now, that just means it will turn around later, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I promise I'm not trying to lose on purpose. I just can't seem to string enough wins together.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Seems inevitable that I'm going to lose even more, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh, it's embarrassing enough to be playing so poorly. This isn't going to help either.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">As if all the losing wasn't already embarrassing enough...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh no! Really? I was hoping to avoid being the first one completely out of clothes if possible...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Do I really have to be the first one to be completely naked? That's maybe the one thing I really really wanted to avoid!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp0_2">I do get that sometimes. It's kind of an old-fashioned notion, but I'm a little old-fashioned myself. I don't know, what do you think about it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp1_2">Yup! My grandpa found him and adopted him, but he let me name him. Maybe it is a little strange, but I was just a kid when I picked it out for him.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp2_2">Well, it's his job to clean the toilet. He's pretty good about getting that done.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp3_2">I asked her quite a few times, but she would always get all cagey and not give a straight answer. She's helped Mega Man before even though we're enemies, so there has to be some reason.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp4_2">G-gosh, it's kinda weird to hear you say that. I always thought people just saw me as a greasy mechanic...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp5_2">It has been, and I think I'm the one most surprised by that. I thought I might be too nervous to go through with it, but now that I made it this far...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp0_2">Wait, are you saying you like it? You like my work clothes?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_2">Whoa? Really? I thought magic was supposed to just solve all your problems with the snap of your fingers!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_DASH2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_2">Right, my name is a food too. I've heard that one before, but I don't hold it against bread rolls. Personally, I like bread rolls.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp1_2">Oh, is that why you're asking about the Flutter? Trying to invite yourself over? I don't know how I'd explain you to Gramps or Mega Man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp2_2">Usually nobody bats an eye, but for some reason people around here have trouble accepting it. Not sure why that is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp3_2">They're energy resources. Everything and anything that needs power runs off of refractor shards. We pretty much never have cash, but we can buy things with just refractor shards just as reliably.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp4_2">I'm sure you think that, but it's not like Mega Man hasn't seen me naked. Even if those were accidents...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp5_2">Gosh... you certainly have an active imagination...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_2">I bet that's pretty handy. The ruins we go into have pretty much no information like that. Just an army for reaverbots defending them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_2">Thanks, and I'm sorry if it's difficult to talk about. Even now when I think about Mega Man traveling up to the moon without me, I do feel a little sad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_2">Building and funding the rocket all by myself wasn't going to be possible. I needed help, but the help I got was... not my first choice. We wasted a lot of time and resources because we couldn't stop arguing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_2">When I first met you, you seemed so cool and in control. I couldn't have possibly imagined something like this might make you nervous...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_2">But it's not taboo here. It's expected. Accepted. Celebrated. It's okay to relax and let go, if only just for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_HandsDown2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_2">As usual, I don't know what you're talking about, Bobobo. I don't know anyone named Rock.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_Chemistry2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_2">I... wouldn't even know where to begin with doing any of that? Some of those things aren't even tangible? I think? Like, what do you mean "the great taste of bran?"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_WigOutDigOut2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_2">Are you just making up words?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_BoBonne2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_2">The only impossibility was us seeing eye to eye, but we managed to do that long enough to succeed. Despite everything, I am grateful for her help...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_PunAndPunishment2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_2">Uh... Bobobo...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="15">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="roll_caskett01" />
                <state img="#-stripalt.png" marker="revy_resp0_2">Their purpose is to protect against reaverbots, aggressive machines. I mean, we do have to fight off pirates every so often, but even then all we do is disable their vehicle...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="16">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="roll_caskett01" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="jura_resp0_2">I feel that way sometimes too. I even feel bad about destroying the reaverbots who attack us sometimes. The way they move around sometimes you'd swear they're alive.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="jura_resp0_2">Some of the reaverbots we've seen act and move around as if they were living things, so I get it. Even though they're dangerous and attack us, I still feel a little sad about destroying them sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="17">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="roll_caskett01" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="meia_resp0_2">I like to think I'm a pretty good mechanic, but nothing holds up forever. Especially stuff that's constantly getting shot at or blown up.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="meia_resp0_2">Machines aren't so different from people, after all. Without constant care, even we would fall to pieces. Even a good mechanic can only do so much sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="18">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll02" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_2">You'd have to be careful you don't take off anything important. It is a weapon, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_2">I'd be careful with something like that, Nagatoro. It's a weapon and not a toy. You might slice something important off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="19">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll12" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_2">Of course it would, but there's the small prerequisite of having to &lt;i&gt;get rid of&lt;/i&gt; your existing limbs.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_2">The benefits of cybernetics are undeniable, but do you really want to &lt;i&gt;get rid of&lt;/i&gt; the limbs you already have?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="20">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll31" />
                <state img="#-stripalt.png" marker="nagatoro_resp3_2">What are you imagining? It was just a little plastic casing that I put a small motor inside of so it would vibrate.... </state>
                <state img="#-stripalt.png" marker="nagatoro_resp3_2">Wait wait wait! I didn't build like a--- a full on--- it wasn't--- look! It was just a motor in a little plastic casing! That's it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="22">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_s0" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="dwight_resp0_2">A generator? I've worked on that kind of thing before! Seen all shapes and kinds, really! There were even a few that powered security doors!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="dwight_resp0_2">Oh, yeah, I've seen that sort of thing before! Worked on my fair share as well! Even a few that powered security doors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="43">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_s1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="dwight_resp1_1">Yeah, I'm not sure I'd do so well with a job like that! Although, I guess it would be nice to have a &lt;i&gt;stable&lt;/i&gt; source of income. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="dwight_resp1_1">Boring wouldn't be all that bad if it was a stable income. It can be a little stressful to dig up enough scrap to put food on the table let alone keep the Flutter aloft.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="44">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_s2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="dwight_resp2_2">Oh, Dwight, don't be so hard on yourself. I'm sure you did the best job you could, and that's what counts the most!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon22" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="leon_resp2_2">N-no. There's no way. I probably reek of oil and smoke from crawling around in the engine room all day.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon32" />
                <state img="#-stripalt.png" marker="leon_resp3_2">Oh! Haha! Well--- it's all n-normal human parts, like you're probably used to! </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="73">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="roll_caskett12" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="jura_resp1_2">Gosh, if only I could keep Mega Man locked up sometimes. Sometimes he just barges into my room when I'm changing clothes. He doesn't even knock!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="jura_resp1_2">Well, Mega Man is not my prisoner, but if he was I'd have an excuse to keep him all locked up. Maybe then he wouldn't walk in on me in the bath...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="74">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="roll_caskett12" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="meia_resp1_2">Yeah, the very last one. They called him "The Master," but now he's gone along with the rest of humanity. It was... a lot to take in when I found out.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="meia_resp1_2">Huh, it's interesting that you'd know that. It is a little sad that it didn't work out and all the humans are gone now though. Finding that out was... well, it gives me shivers even now!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon02" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="leon_resp0_2">Mega Man did mention something like that, but I really didn't understand what he meant. I thought maybe he just ate something weird and had a nightmare. Maybe he did go to some weird place like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon12" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="leon_resp1_2">Yeah, just family. No boyfriend or anything like that, so you don't have any competition.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="89">
                <condition role="other" character="elphaba" sayingMarker="roll_ozHead" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="elphaba_resp0_2">Oh? Uh... I'm not quite sure I know what an "Oz Head" is...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="elphaba_resp0_2">Sorry, did you say "Oz Head?" What exactly would that be?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yae" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yae_resp0_2">But you're a ninja! I bet you're really tough and athletic! You don't need to be good a good mechanic as long as you are a good whatever you are!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="sofia" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sofia_resp0_2">Yeah, same here! I mean, I feel like I know everything, but other times I feel like I hardly know anything at all! Do you know what I mean?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="92">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" sayingMarker="roll01" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nami_resp0_2">Guys do like lasers and swords, don't they? Mega Man had me make those sorts of weapons for him too. They are fun to build and fun to see in action! I always thought the saber was a little impractical, but it is really cool when it flashes to life and cuts a reaverbot down to size!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nami_resp0_2">Mega Man likes lasers and swords too! I've built and rebuilt those weapons for him a whole bunch of times! They're fun to work on and I really like seeing them in action! When the big laser goes off, it blasts reaverbots away like they're nothing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sheena_resp0_2">I wouldn't say the reaverbots are evil. They're just in the way and aggressive. They're only doing what they were designed to do. Sometimes I feel bad that we have to destroy them sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripalt.png" marker="sheena_resp3_2">Oh! Gosh! More than once! I've gotten them stuck in my hair too. I'm even scared to run my brush through it most days...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sheena_resp1_2">Hey, I think it's a cool name! I don't think it's any stranger than being named "Roll" or "~player~" or even "Sheena." Besides, how would you feel if someone asked you if Sheena was actually your real name?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sofia" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="sofia_resp1_2">It doesn't? I sure wonder about it sometimes. Even though he was gone for so long, he's still the same. Still sticking up for me, still helping me out, and still bringing me things he finds in he junkyard...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yae" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yae_resp1_2">I didn't actually go there myself. We sent the rocket to the moon on a rescue mission. It wasn't big enough to hold us and the people we were trying to rescue, unfortunately.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="roll_caskett_hydrodynamic_mechanic" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Living up on the Flutter, I'm almost always out over the ocean. The beach though? That's a whole other thing!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Being at the beach is way different from being out on the ocean all the time. I still get excited when we call get a chance to play on the shore!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I don't many opportunities to play on the beach. I mean, I'm out over the ocean all the time, but the shore is still a ton of fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="roll_caskett_hydrodynamic_mechanic" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Now that it's summer, maybe I should see about taking a boat out on the water...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">You know what I haven't done in a while? I haven't taken the boat out on the water for a trip. Summer seems like the perfect time for it, doesn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Maybe I should take everyone back to Cattlelox Island for the summer so we can take the boat out on the lake. That's always a fun way to unwind!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="roll_caskett_hydrodynamic_mechanic" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I... uh... I hope my swimsuit isn't weird. It was a bit of a spur of the moment purchase...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">My... uh... my swimsuit isn't strange or anything, is it? I sort of just got it on impulse, to be honest.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">So... is my swimsuit cute? I thought it looked nice, so I just decided to get it. Needed a new one after all...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I don't get out of the Flutter, our ship, all that much. It's my house and my workshop as well as how Gramps, Mega Man, and me all get around. I usually don't have much reason to leave.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Normally I stay at home on our airship, the Flutter, with Gramps and Mega Man. I don't have a ton of opportunities to meet new people, so this is a nice change of pace. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It's nice to meet some new people like this. I live on an airship, the Flutter, with Gramps and Mega Man. I love them both, and the Flutter has everything I need, but even I get tired of the same routine after a while.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I don't really have a lot of romantic or sexual experience, to be honest. Not a lot of chances for that sort of thing when you're constantly on the move.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It will be fun getting to know you all here, but I'm hoping I get to know myself a little better too. When you're stuck on an airship most days, you don't get a lot of romantic or sexual experience.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">There's pretty much no opportunity for me to do anything like this back home. Barely a chance for any sort of romantic or sexual experience. Not a lot of privacy either...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I wasn't even sure I'd have to courage to show my breasts, but now that I have I feel... lighter? Unburdened?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Actually, I'm not as nervous as I was before. I feel sort of relaxed, even. Relieved, maybe?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Since I got this far, going just a little further doesn't seem so hard. It feels right, maybe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I hope I'm not covered in grease. I think I'd die of embarrassment if have to unzip later and my chest had a huge grease smear on it...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I better not be covered in grease. If I take my hat off later and there's a big grease streak across my forehead, just don't tell me. I'll just see it later and die of embarrassment then...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I'm pretty sure I'm not covered in grease right now, but then again the more sure I am of that the more likely it is. It better not be on my butt or something...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I just wore my normal clothes when I came here, but was that the right choice? I don't really have that many clothes anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">My clothes aren't weird, are they? Honestly, I don't have the money to spend on a lot of clothes in the first place.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I hope it's okay that I'm just wearing my usual clothes. I don't really have any nice clothes or special underwear to begin with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Gosh, I feel so self-conscious right now. I feel like my heart is going to beat right out of my chest.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">This is so embarrassing, but it's also so exciting. I wasn't even sure I'd have the courage to make it this far.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Alright, then. Here it goes. Are you guys as nervous as I am about all this?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="4" id="28">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll33" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="nagatoro_resp3_3">Well... it's possible that the motor could possibly maybe burn out...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="nagatoro_resp3_3">Mhmm, yes, always good to keep... a few small refractors in a drawer...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="ringo_ando" sayingMarker="roll_bodysuit" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="ringo_resp2_s">I-it's not that tight. I fill it out a bit better than I did when I first got it years ago, but it's not uncomfortable or anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="maria_resp0_3">Huh? I-ignore them? Do you really think it's that bad? Gosh!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="maria_resp1_3">He's not a dog! He's a very important person to me! Please don't say anything mean about him...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="maria_resp2_3">He's good about doing any chore I ask him to do. I rely on him just as much as he relies on me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="maria_resp3_3">What? No! That's ridiculous! Tron and Mega Man? No way! She better keep her grimy little pirate mitts off my ma--- off Mega Man!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="maria_resp4_3">Oh, w-well, it's not like I don't fantasize about... stuff like that sometimes...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_3" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="maria_resp5_3">That's an understatement. I don't think I've ever wanted to masturbate so bad...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="kaz_resp0_3">Is... is that a yes? Oh, well... thanks! I'm glad you like whatever it is you like about it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_3">Gosh, I never thought I'd hear that today! Well, maybe I have soldered together a miracle or two in my career.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="9">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_ThereIsNoDASH3" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_3">No, bad Bobobo. No more name puns for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="kaz_resp1_3">Nice try, but you're not about to find out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="kaz_resp2_3">But that's clearly different! I don't know why anybody would ever call anyone "Caprese Boy." Do... do people actually call you that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="kaz_resp3_3">Well, I don't think they'd be quite so valuable if they were just laying around where anyone could grab them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="kaz_resp4_3">Pfft, you perv. You're a lot more forward than Mega Man. I don't... think I dislike that either...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_3" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="kaz_resp5_3">And what about what you want? I think you should just come right out and say it, that is, if you want to make me horny...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_3">Knowing what we know now, I can say that is exactly the case. It's not like we know everything now, but we'll keep digging and discovering more for sure!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_3">How could both be true? Did he turn into a zombie? If my experience with traveling to the moon is anything to go off of, it's more likely that he got blown up. Maybe even more than once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_3">Yeah, &lt;i&gt;eventually&lt;/i&gt;. We got really close when we first started out, but then a bunch of stuff went wrong and the attempt fizzled out. After years of zero progress, it really felt like we were never going to reach him.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_3">I didn't know I had it in me either. Now I'm just nervous about what that might say about me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_3" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_3">And you've got time. I know I'm in no place to judge right now. Gosh, maybe I won't even look at my cards next round...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="10">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_HandsDown3" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_3">If I did know someone named Rock, I guess we could hang out together and be "Rock and Roll."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="11">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_Chemistry3" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_3">Yeah, I'm not sure even you know what you're talking about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="12">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_WigOutDigOut3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_3">Is it possible you've got me confused with someone else?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="13">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_BoBonne3" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_3">Seriously?! I think your brain needs some concussive maintenance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="14">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_PunAndPunishment3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_3">Just when I was starting to feel &lt;i&gt;less&lt;/i&gt; embarrassed about losing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="25">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll03_male" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_3">Don't worry, ~player~. I'm sure she's only joking. Still, it might be best to keep any heavy weaponry away from her.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_3">So, maybe we keep all the ordinance &lt;i&gt;away&lt;/i&gt; from her for now! Just for ~player~'s safety.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="26">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll03" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_3">Expert precision? Uhm, the beam saber really isn't calibrated for that sort of thing!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_3">It's really not like normal swords! You've got to be really super careful!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="27">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll13" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_3">If you want to be stronger or faster, there are plenty of other solutions that let you keep your body as it is.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_3">There are diggers who do go to that sort of extreme, but they're pretty much all really old men with failing bodies.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="38">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="roll_caskett1s" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="jura_resp0_3">I mean, I do feel less bad about it when they're trying to smash us or blow us up or chop us to pieces or set us on fire or---</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="jura_resp0_3">I'm pretty sure that's how Mega Man feels, since he's the one doing all the fighting. He has a real "blast first and ask questions never" sort of attitude towards them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="39">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="roll_caskett1s" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="meia_resp0_3">Oh yeah, trouble has a name and it's &lt;i&gt;Bonne.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="meia_resp0_3">The same trouble that busts up all our equipment is the same trouble that we have to face to make any money. That's just the life of a being a digger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="42">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_as0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="dwight_resp0_3">Well, first I'd--- wait, a &lt;i&gt;killer&lt;/i&gt;?! If someone is trying to kill you, don't bother trying to fix the generator! J-just use the parts to build a bomb to blast a way out of there!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="dwight_resp0_3">I mean, it's not so simple as--- huh, did you say a &lt;i&gt;killer&lt;/i&gt;?! Why would we worry about a broken generator in that situation? It would be faster to take the scrap parts and build a bomb to blow a hole you can escape through!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon33" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="leon_resp3_3">G-gosh, you're making me wish I had an engine. Would you settle for just turning me on?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="75">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="roll_caskett1s" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="revy_resp0_3">Well, we did think they were done for when we shot down the Gesellschaft. We didn't really &lt;i&gt;mean&lt;/i&gt; for it to be fatal anyway... but there's no denying they're a durable bunch.</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="revy_resp0_3">Look, the Bonnes are... it's complicated. Do I &lt;i&gt;think&lt;/i&gt; about blowing up Tron from time to time? Yes. Do I do it? No, because that's what it means to be the bigger woman...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon23" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="leon_resp2_3">Gosh, you don't waste time do you... but... I guess I don't hate that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="leon_resp0_3">Well, maybe it's better that I'm here. I'm not so good in a fight...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon13" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="roll_resp1_3">Well... I am in a particularly &lt;i&gt;willing&lt;/i&gt; mood, to~background.time~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="elphaba" sayingMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="elphaba_resp0_3">That... doesn't sound like it has much practical use...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="yae" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="yae_resp0_3">H-huh? Oh? Uh... well, that's... maybe we could just talk about metal fatigue or something like that!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="sofia" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="sofia_resp0_3">Whoa, really? Gosh, you must have studied an awful lot if you never get stumped!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="sheena_resp0_3">W-well, I'm just... they just... you know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="sheena_resp3_3">I know exactly what you're talking about! I tried all sorts of things, but I just gave up and now I wear my hat everywhere! It's the only thing that can keep it contained!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="sheena" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="sheena_resp1_3">Wait... your name really &lt;i&gt;isn't&lt;/i&gt; Sheena?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="sofia" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="sofia_resp1_3">He--- {big}&lt;i&gt;what?!&lt;/i&gt;{!reset}</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yae" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="yae_resp1_3">Yeeeeah... I wouldn't say we were able to do it "quickly."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="roll_caskett_hydrodynamic_mechanic" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I'm sort of the only one who gets excited for it though. Gramps is too old to really enjoy swimming and Mega Man... well, he's better at sinking.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I would be nice to have some friends to play with on the beach. Mega Man isn't so reliable when it comes to playing in the water. I've modified his armor more times than I can count to help him survive underwater.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Mega Man isn't such a big fan of the beach himself. I try to keep him out of the water too since I'm the one who will have to dredge him up off the ocean floor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="roll_caskett_hydrodynamic_mechanic" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I mean, the boat is fun as long as we don't get attacked by pirates. Being on the boat doesn't make that more or less likely though. That's just something we have to deal with whatever we decide to do...</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">But... can't imagine it will take long for a &lt;i&gt;certain&lt;/i&gt; pirate to show up and ruin the fun. Oh... well, I guess it's tradition...</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">I'm sure the fun will come to an end when we are inevitably attacked by pirates. The only question is if they'll show up in some giant shark mech or some sort of octopus...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <test expr="~self.costume~" value="roll_caskett_hydrodynamic_mechanic" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I actually... I ordered it out of a catalog I found in Mega Man's room. I'm not quite as busty as the model in the picture... but... I don't know. It looked sexy on her...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Let me tell you, I could buy enough scrap metal to cover myself pretty much entirely for what it cost to buy this little thing. Still, once I put it on it felt worth it...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I saw this in a magazine Mega Man had in his room. I didn't tell him I bought it. Gosh, you should have seen the look on his face when he saw me in it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I need some excitement every once and a while. Excitement that doesn't involve almost getting killed by reaverbots...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">But I hope nothing bad happens to the Flutter while I'm gone. Gramps is a good mechanic, but he's not as spry as he used to be. Mega Man on the other hand... well, he's better at breaking than fixing things...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">And who knows? Maybe there are some spare parts around here somewhere. Just think what I could build! It would also give me a less embarrassing excuse for where I went off to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="78">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Once I thought I'd end up with Mega Man, but then he was stuck on the moon for all those years. That kind of distance puts a damper on a relationship that never really blossomed...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I mean, I guess there is Mega Man, but even though we're close it's... complicated. He was trapped on the moon for a really long time, so I'm just not sure where we really stand...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">There is Mega Man, but the closest we've come to doing anything is when he walks in on me changing or bathing. Then he was trapped on the moon for a number of years, so I had a lot of time to consider other options...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I try and keep covered up so I don't get stains all over me, but it gets hot in the engine compartment. I unzip a little, I get sweating, I wipe my hands on myself. It just happens!</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">And I'm &lt;i&gt;sure&lt;/i&gt; I don't have grease on my hands because these gloves do a great job of distributing it evenly across every surface I touch, including me. I can't work with greasy hands, so the gloves stay on.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I promise it's fresh grease, really! I bathe regularly, but stuff like motor oil and contact grease don't wash off easy. I have to use special soap so I don't always smell like an engine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm only wondering because I found a dirty magazine under Mega Man's bed one time. All the women in there had really sexy lingerie and make-up on. Meanwhile, I'm just standing here in my work clothes...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I found a dirty magazine in Mega Man's room once, and all the women in it were dressed so provocatively. I just keep thinking I'd be more exciting to~background.time~ if I was dressed more like that.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I mean, Mega Man had a dirty magazine and all the women in there were wearing the most brazen outfits. I don't even know where I'd buy something like them, let alone if I've got the courage to wear it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm not a lot to look at, so I hope you don't mind...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Hoo, okay, maybe I'll calm down if I just pretend I'm at home... in my room... and then Mega Man barges in...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Okay... I'm super embarrassed. Let's keep going before I say something dumb...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm even sort of happy losing one more time means I have to masturbate because all this excitement is making me horny...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I wasn't entirely sure about all of this in the beginning, but now I'm all worked up. Horny enough to touch myself, if you can beat me...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I can feel it. My heart's not pounding because I'm scared, but because I'm aroused...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-wave.png">Chihiro! Feeling better now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="enm" status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="564">I guess guys get nervous about being naked too...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="565">I guess I just thought all guys would walk around completely naked with no problem...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="566">It's a little bad... but ~target~ is kinda cute when he's nervous...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Sorry, ~target~, but I had to beat you. You understand.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You'll just have to do better next time, ~target~. For now, maybe you can treat us to something nice.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Looks like you're having a little trouble, ~target~. Maybe you need somebody to spot for you.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">It's not wrong to be happy about ~target~ losing, right?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Okay, ~target~. It's your turn!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Gosh, this round turned out better than I hoped.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Nice try, but not quite nice enough!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I got you this time, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Looks like I've got you in a fix!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">There's not going to be any sort of problem with you taking a turn this time, is there, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">This seems perfectly fair to me. </state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Hm, maybe some dreams do come true...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I hope we get more than just a peek at him.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">The less imagination I have to use, the better!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I wouldn't mind ~target~'s company down at my level...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">We're way past being coy. Give us a little show, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't act like you don't want to strip, ~target~. No, that's not me projecting!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Thinking about ~target~ getting naked makes me feel kind of restless. </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Think of this as a favor to me...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Maybe you forgot to worry about yourself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Okay, that's more like it!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Too bad! I'm not giving up that easily!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Don't feel too bad, ~target~. I just think it'll be more fun if we share the bad luck around.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">A guy like you wouldn't chicken out now, would he?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I could do with a bit more of ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Let's see a bit more than just that handsome face, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I could for sure go for some more ~target~ right about now! </state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't worry about watching your back, ~target~. I've got that covered...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Gotcha! A direct hit this time!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hey, you see a little and then you show a little! Doesn't that sound fair?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kekko_kamen" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">So... aren't you already naked? I'm sorry, is that rude to ask?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="enf" status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="554">Sorry, ~target~. It hardly seems fair, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="555">I sort of feel bad for ~target~. She definitely seems less okay with this than I would be in her place...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="556">Don't worry, ~target~! I'm sure you'll figure out some way to handle this!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">~Target~, are you ready? Seems like it's your turn this time.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Sorry I can't watch your back here, ~target~. I've got my own hands full personally.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Don't worry, ~target~. You're in good company here. We're cheering for you!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Of course I want to see a bit more of ~target~. Well, maybe a lot more. You can't blame me for being curious.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Watch out, ~target~. Looks like you might have a little trouble headed your way.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I'm relieved to see it's ~target~ this time, but not just because that means it's not my turn. Really!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Okay, let's see what makes you tick, so to speak!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Oh, are we going to get to see what's under the hood?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hey, don't quit on us now! I want to see a little more of you!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Don't worry, ~target~. We'll just take you apart one piece at a time.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I'm sure bad karma will catch up to me eventually, but until then I may as well enjoy this.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Careful, ~target~! The right combination is crucial here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">If you could, please consider that I'd really like to see something exciting from you, ~target~. Doesn't that seem fair?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">It was a good day to disembark from the Flutter!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Wow, I was staring at ~target~ that whole time. Did I make that happen?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You've seen this much of me, I'd like to see just as much of you...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">The further along we get in this game, the more exciting it gets. I didn't feel half this thrilled when we first started out.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't forget to lose with a little enthusiasm! Seeing you're having a good time is kind of a turn on...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">When I think about seeing your body, I get all excited...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">~Target~... showing us her body...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">No more hiding, ~target~. You've got to get down to my level, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">~Target~ lost... but it's my heart that's racing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't worry, ~target~. You're not out of this quite yet!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">It's really too bad, ~target~. We do all really want to see you keep going though.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">It's only fair, ~target~. I can't have all the bad luck, now can I?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I'm not so easy to beat. Besides, as a digger I've got a sense for when there's treasure to be found.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Gosh, I'm getting pretty excited about seeing a girl strip, but it's ~target~. Anyone would want to get a better view of that body, right?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I know you're more than just a pretty face, ~target~. Let's see what else you've got going for you!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I've already taken my turns. I think it's only fair someone else takes a few now.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Don't look at me. I think it's more than only fair that you lost this time!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Maybe this time we'll discover a weak point on you!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Oh, we're not out of the woods yet! You've got to know that, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hey, it's ~target~ this time! Don't forget to have fun with it!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't give up yet, ~target~! You'd be impressed what you can make out of junk!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-furious.png">Wait, what? Then what was even the point of that round?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It's a bit disappointing to go on a long dig and only come up with a few small refractors...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="11">We've never found  ~clothing~ while on a dig. Not even down a hole in the wall.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Some|A)~ ~clothing~? That's kind of interesting. Do you think it would fetch a good price at the junk shop?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="438">It's not the sort of thing we might come across on a dig. You wouldn't believe all the things people have thrown away over the centuries, but I guess they kept ~clothing.ifPlural(all their|every last)~ ~clothing~. Though, maybe they didn't have any.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">So ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ your ~clothing~ valuable or something?  </state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You've got quite the valuable little collection there, don't you?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">All that effort for barely any payoff.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Well, what can you do? It all has to come off eventually.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">So that's it then? It's a bit of a bummer, to be honest.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Aww, that didn't count for much, did it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-stern.png">Oh, is that all? You're kind of letting me down, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">It's find to take your time and all, but I know I'm past the point of getting excited over something like that.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Just his ~clothing~? Oh, no big deal then.</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">Right, stop everything. This ought to be a game changer...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">This isn't your little way of teasing us, is it?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Come one, ~target~, aren't we past being coy?</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">Oh, it just doesn't seem fair. I guess it's not supposed to be perfectly fair, but still!</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Not really the mood I was hoping for...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Capitalism?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==2" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">You're just making this up at this point!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Well... it is Bobobo we're talking about. Maybe we shouldn't rule aliens out...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==4" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">How can you say all these totally insane things with a completely straight face?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==5" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Aww, that's... uh... that is sweet, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==6" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png">That might be as close as we're going to get to an admission of guilt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==7" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">Don't pretend like you're doing us any favors...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==8" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">2000 and what wis-what based what what?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==9" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">... I wonder if Mega Man would find a chainsaw attachment useful...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Bobobo_s1_3" />
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" sayingMarker="Maria_Choices3==10" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">Don't blame them for this! That's totally unfair!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="chazz" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">That came off pretty easily, Chazz. Don't you want it more securely attached to your arm? It shouldn't be too hard to graft the circuitry into your forearm for the interface...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Seems a little cumbersome to have that whole apparatus attached to your arm. Wouldn't it be more convenient to just modify your existing arm with the parts you needed?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh, I don't think you should sell your ~clothing~. Not unless you need money for spare parts to repair your often failing airship...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah, I didn't mean to imply your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ worthless or anything! I've sold my own clothes to get by once or twice, so I know even stuff like that has a price!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="15">Even little things have some value though, and a junk shop will buy just about anything! Even a hand vacuum or a box of active proximity mines.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Maybe just hold on to your ~clothing~, ~target~. Wait to sell ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ until you're in a real financial emergency.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">You didn't bring a bunch of little things just to pad out your losses, did you?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Okay, let's just move right along!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I think we're just about over the loss of your ~clothing~. We've got more ground to cover still.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I still think you'll end up losing it all in the end!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Well, a good digger just moves right along until they get to the treasure!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Come on, ~target~. Now's the time to be impressing me...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I just want you to be honest with yourself and go a little faster. I mean, I'm already like this...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">If you don't pick up the pace, we might just leave you behind, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Please, don't be shy. I want to see as much of you as you've seen of me.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Are you telling me you don't feel at all compelled to impress us?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">It's time to be daring. You'd know that if you had been watching me.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">What treasures are you still hiding, I wonder?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Well... it's not like I can't understand being a little shy...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if Mega Man would buy me something like your ~clothing~. What would it even mean for a guy to do that?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Is there some story behind your ~clothing~? Did someone buy it for you?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I don't think your ~clothing~ is my style, exactly. Suits you just fine though. </state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I don't really wear a lot of jewelry of accessories. I wouldn't want to wear something that might get caught in the Flutter's machinery while I'm working on her.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Playing it safe, huh? Fine, I can understand that. We're still going to make fun of you for it though.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">One by one until you're totally out, huh? Fine, take your time and see where it gets you!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I know you've got something of more value than just ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~, ~target~! I mean, we can &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; see it!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I get that you're just playing the game, but still...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Maybe if I had a lot of extraneous stuff, I wouldn't be in this jam.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You're not afraid of losing are you, ~target~? Seems like you might be stalling a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I think you're doing well enough that you could risk taking some bigger strides right about now.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">It's not a competition to see who has the most stuff, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">I must look pretty silly to you, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Maybe this move will save you, but maybe it won't. Maybe your luck is totally out now.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Come on, ~target~. You've still got treasures we haven't seen yet!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">So much for the momentum...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">... I blinked and it disappeared. I missed something... but what did I miss?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Where did... did I space out or something? It just disappeared all of a sudden. What's going on?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Sometimes Mega Man just finds little trinkets when he's out and about. He says they remind him of me and lets me keep them. I'm nearly out of space in my room due to his generosity.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Well, Mega Man does have a habit of giving me things he picks up, but it's not uncommon for him to go through trash cans. I just make sure to wash whatever he gives me first...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It's not like I have the money to spend on anything extra for myself. If I have spare zenny, it goes right into the Rainy Day Fund!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Tell me, ~target~, do nice little things like that make you happy? The stuff alone doesn't interest me, but if I get it as a gift from someone I care about it becomes important to me. Is it like that for you too?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright! Time to beat you again! Let's see what you're still hiding!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">At the rate this is going, playing it safe might not work out so well.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Maybe you've got a chance, or maybe I've got you all figured out! A spotter has a knack for that sort of thing!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You're free to take your time, of course, but only if you get lucky!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Come on now! Let's really get into the spirit of it!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I've got a feeling this might not work out like you're hoping it will...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">If my selfish request counts for anything, I'd love for you to show me something far more intimate...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">You can do it, ~target~! The hardest part is taking it all off! It's easy to just be naked once you get that far!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Why not just relax and join me on the losing end?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Stacking up losses isn't quite so bad. You can believe me. I mean, just look at me!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">It's a lot less stressful just being like this, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">I've got my mind on other things anyway...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Is this what you usually wear, ~target~? If you were going to go on a dig, you'd need a lot more protection than that.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">If ~target~ were going on a dig dressed how he showed up, he'd be in real trouble.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Your clothing seems pretty comfortable, ~target~, but not very practical. You could use a few upgrades.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't think what you're wearing is very practical for digging. It needs a lot more... well, a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">You've got style, ~target~, but you're lacking in the practicality department. I can think of at least ten different hazards you're not properly equipped for.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What ~target~ needs is... well, a total overhaul of his equipment to be honest. </state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">It might be my instincts as a spotter, but I'm just worried you're not properly equipped for every possible threat, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm, I could see ~target~ sporting some state-of-the-art digging equipment. He needs quite a few things before he's there though.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="791">I'm not really used to seeing guys who aren't dressed to go on a dig. Even Mega Man wears his armor most days.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Such a tease, ~target~. Can't you step it up a bit?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">~Target~ is making me feel like I'm not very good at this game, but I can live with that.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Feeling a bit shy still, ~target~? I don't see why you have to be.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Come one, ~target~! I think you need to start pulling a bit more weight around here!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Oh, going to leave us all wanting more, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Oh boy. Taking it slow? Fine, fine.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hello? Naked girl here waiting for you to strip down! Did you forget?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">It's a bit insulting you're not quite so eager to get totally naked.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hey, if you really want to impress then you're going to have to give us a bit more than that!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">You probably get tired walking and running everywhere. With a good set of wheels and an engine, I can make you some jet shoes to let you zip around faster than a car!</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">You would definitely need a helmet. That's a must. You'll thank me later when a reaverbot drops on top of you from the ceiling.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">First thing is first! You need some armor! Thick, metal, reinforced body armor. Form fitting too! Can't have you getting hurt in a little explosion!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">You definitely need something to defend yourself with! How do you feel about grenades?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I specialize in arm-mounted artillery, but maybe that's not your area of expertise. I can start you off with a fire extinguisher so you can get used to how it works!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Or maybe you're not the adventuring type? Maybe you're the domestic type! How about an arm-mounted toaster or vacuum cleaner! Really, I've built them before!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I've been working on schematics for a new flak jacket that shouldn't overheat even in direct contact with flames! Actually, it would be a huge help if I had someone who could test it!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">But at the end of the day I guess you're not really a digger after all. Maybe you should just dress in whatever way suits you, regardless of possible threats!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Any chance you are frequently in danger of receiving electric shocks? I've drafted up a few things that might help with that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I do think it's an improvement, even if it's just a small one. I can think of a few more places that still need work though.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I get the feeling you're building up to something big! I guess I'll just have to wait.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Okay, now you just need to keep losing! Come one, it'll be fun! I promise!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I can respect playing smart, but don't keep us waiting in suspense for too long!</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Fine. I'll wait...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Let me know when you're ready to get real serious.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I think I'd like a guy who takes a bit more initiative than that.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Hm... well, it's not like it &lt;i&gt;wasn't&lt;/i&gt; kinda sexy...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">I'll just be waiting here... waiting...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">I don't know a lot about clothing, but I do know a lot about machines. They're kind of similar, wouldn't you say? </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Fashion is not my strong suit. I don't like wearing fancy clothes because I worry too much about getting them dirty. I just get clothes that are durable.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">You've got such an interesting sense of style, ~target~. My style has always been focused on practicality, to be honest.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I don't really keep up with fashion at all, but are your clothes more about form or function, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I usually just design armor and weapons for Mega Man, so I've never actually made equipment for a girl before! I don't think it would be all that different though!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What are your measurements, ~target~? I'm wondering how much material I'd need to properly outfit you for a dig...</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Maybe you should consider dressing for the possibility of an enemy attack, ~target~. Maybe you don't agree, but I'm an expert in these sort of things. You've got vulnerabilities that need smart solutions!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I could really use a girl's input in some of the equipment I've designed! Mega Man can only really give me his perspective and I don't think he's very good at coming up with criticisms. He's just too positive!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I've never built any equipment meant for a woman before. I haven't even made myself any weapons or armor!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">There should be a little more than that you can show us? You should be able to see that clearly.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You're not feeling shy, ~target~, are you? Not after I've cleared the way for you.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I've come all this way and ~target~ is still taking her time. I hope you're not getting cold feet, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">If you're worried about being immodest, I think we're far past that point now.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Come on and lose a little more! I want another naked buddy!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Oh, come on, ~target~! Get unequipped!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Not joining me in being naked? That's cold, ~target~. Maybe you've got a mechanical heart!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Oh well, if that's all you can really pull of right now, I guess I won't complain.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Now where's the fun in that? Don't you think a little more would be fair!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-8" id="82">
                <condition role="target" character="myriam" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">What are you doing? Your bra is really less important than the box? Really?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1362">If you're looking for something really practical for your wardrobe, how about an arm mounted buster cannon? It fits comfortably over the entire length of your forearm!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1363">In a way, I'm actually something of a clothes designer myself! I make and upgrade all of Mega Man's digger armor parts! People seem to think he's very cool looking, so maybe I do have some skills in fashion!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1364">It's like I always tell Mega Man: you're never fully dressed without your reinforced custom-fit body armor!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1365">So I'm not  an expert, but I'm sure there's no reason you couldn't upgrade your outfit! How about some spring-loaded armored boots? They'll come in real handy if you fall down an elevator shaft and need to escape!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="1366">Does any part of your arm come off? Powered cannons are really heavy, so if we're gonna mount one to you it'd be best to have a little arm as possible!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="1367">You know what they say: mines are a girl's best friend! At least, I think people should say that. People don't give mines enough credit! Anyway, I can build you a mine-laying device that goes over your hand!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="1368">So maybe you're not the combat type, but the best part is that if your weapon has an advanced auto-targeting system you don't have to be!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="1369">Maybe we could just stick to something simple for you. How about reinforced cybernetic boots that will prevent both electric shock and serious burns?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1370">Come to think of it, I really haven't met or seen many female diggers. Building equipment that will fit a woman's body might be a whole untapped market...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Well, you need to go at your own pace. I don't have any problem respecting that.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I know it seems tough, but it gets easier as you go along. At least, it did for me. I just focused on having a good time!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I don't want to rush you. It's perfectly fine to take the time you need. The anticipation makes things kind of exciting too.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">If you need to just take your time, that's alright with me. Though, I do reserve the right to tease you maybe a tiny bit about it.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I hope you're preparing to lose the next hand.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Oh, I don't want to be too pushy if stripping makes you nervous. I was pretty nervous too at first...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">It's all got to come off eventually! Don't you forget!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Is this your way of teasing me? That's rude! I just had bad luck is all!</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Gosh... why am I so eager to get another woman naked...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Seems like you might be in trouble here, ~target~. Do you think you can continue?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't worry, ~target~! It's okay! We're cheering you on even if things aren't looking good for you!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Are you really running out of options, ~target~? Seems like you might be in trouble here.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright, ~target~! Don't give up yet! Not when it's about to get exciting!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Looks like we might've hit it big this time!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">That really is the best way forward right now, isn't it?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Yeah, go ahead and just slip ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ ~clothing~ off now. We've all been waiting for this!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Bringing out the big guns this time, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Yup! I knew I was picking up something big ahead!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Got a little something you wanted to show us all, ~target~? </state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">At least we didn't need to break out the drill to get ~clothing.ifPlural(these|that)~ off of ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Say goodbye to your stubborn ~clothing~, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Don't worry! You won't need your ~clothing~ to protect you anymore.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't just tear ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ off. Give us a little show, why don't ya?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Well, this is awfully considerate of you, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">That's a little less in my way...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Oh, go right ahead. Don't expect me to try and stop you!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Boy, you really kept us waiting, huh?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You know, it's times like these you need a good spotter watching your back. If you need someone to do that, I could be your girl...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I do admire a guy who is cool under pressure. Could be fun to see how you do a little later...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't go anywhere yet, ~target~. I don't think I'm done with you by a long shot...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">This is more fun than I was expecting. I think there's a bit more fun to be had with ~target~ as well...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">This is nice, but I think I'd be even happier if you lost again!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I do appreciate you trying to keep me interested in you.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I'm happy to see you're not chickening out on us yet!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Okay, now let's have you lose again for us...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">It's nice, but not near enough to distract me!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Hm, I wouldn't mind walking in on ~target~ while he's changing...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Oh, we're not done with you yet, ~target~. You know that, right?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't turn back now, ~target~. We're finally getting somewhere.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You feel it too, right, ~target~? Maybe you need to lose a little bit more...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">So... I'm just gonna feel antsy until this whole thing is over, aren't I?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Can't say I've got any objections to what I've seen so far.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Well... so... here we are...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I guess I should have known we could've ended up like this...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Yeah... skin on skin is... much better...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Getting down to the nitty-gritty now, huh, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Pretty exciting, isn't it, ~target~? I hope you're still having fun too.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Go ahead and make yourself comfortable, ~target~. We won't judge.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You might want to stop losing, ~target~. Just something I thought you might want to consider unless you want to lose all your undergarments too.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Now's the time and place to take a load off. Don't worry about it!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Alright, now that's the spirit!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">It's more relaxing to have less clothes on anyway. I'm not weird for thinking that, right?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Looks like we've found something interesting this time around!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">A strange thing to be doing in front of strangers, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Now it's ~target~'s turn to show us some real excitement.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It's not so bad without your clothes, ~target~. I think it's growing on me a little.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">So? Don't keep us waiting any longer...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Seems like our patience is paying off. Sorry, ~target~. I know you worked hard not to get to this point.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Looks like you won't be getting off that easily, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Maybe the game is finally getting away from you, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">I'm telling you guys that you just get used to it after a little while...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Just a little reminder that you could still lose it all.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Oh, I hope you don't think this part is bad...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="suzuya" stage="3" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Gosh, that's even more risque than some of the things I've seen in magazines...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="71">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="2" sayingMarker="Nagatoro_Swimsuit_1A" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Huh, it's sort of like my singlet...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I sort of wish I had some sexier underwear. No idea how I could budget it though.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">W-wow, ~target~ looks pretty cute like that...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I know Mega Man would like this, if the magazines under his bed are any indicator...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">You've got such a great body, ~target~. There's no way you're nervous about playing a game like this...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">See? Still cute even when she's got her ~clothing~ off.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Yeah, if you walked around like this normally, people might crash their cars.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Haha, w-well... isn't it odd how it gets hotter as the clothes come off? I mean, what's &lt;i&gt;up with that&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I didn't realize watching other women strip would make me feel so antsy...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Gosh, it's like one of those risque magazines in motion...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I think I prefer ~target~ this way instead...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Any digger worth her salt knows the best treasures are buried as deep as you can go...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Oh, yes. This was well worth the waiting...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Do you promise it'll get even better from here on out?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">As a spotter, I've got to warn you that continuing forwards could be a little risky.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">So, are we going to see the rest of your "arsenal?"</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I think we're going to keep getting along just fine...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I still think there's quite a bit you haven't shown us...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I don't mean to be greedy, but it would be a bit of a shame if this was all we got to see...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="62">
                <condition role="other" character="pyrrha" />
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-wave.png">Whoa! Talk about a close call! Nice save, Pyrrha!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="60">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ha--- wha, Brock!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="588">Not feeling so shy now, are we?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="589">Is it really so bad to lose your ~clothing~, ~target~? Don't guys go around in public without shirts all the time?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="590">You don't really need your ~clothing~ anyway. I think you'll be a lot more comfortable without it.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="591">A tragic loss for ~target~, but for the rest of us...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="793">Oh? Making it a little steamy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="803">You've been holding out on us, ~target~. </state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="802">Personally, I think this is way overdue.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="801">It's about time, ~target~. No more teasing us...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="800">Glad we were fortunate enough to get you down this far...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="799">Well... maybe you could consider this a favor to us...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="616">Strong guy like you and a someone my size... ah, maybe I'll just be quiet...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="617">Wow, you're like something I saw in an anatomy book once...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="596">Maybe we can just take an extra moment to appreciate this before the next round?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="597">Gosh, now I feel all embarrassed...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="598">I just want to say I'm glad you decided to join us to~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="599">So, you must be pretty popular back home, ~target~? I don't see why not.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="819">You... you don't disappoint...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="604">See, nothing to be nervous about. Now we appreciate that handsome frame of yours...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="605">So... nothing but the air between us separating our bodies...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="606">Well, now we're both pretty exposed. I wonder if we have anything else in common...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="607">I hardly even need to imagine anymore...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="833">Isn't it more intimate like this?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="840">Sorry, but this just a little awkward...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="841">Oh? If your ~clothing~ is coming off, that means...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="842">I guess this was bound to happen. I kinda thought I had more time to prepare.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="843">No reason to panic, right? This is exactly what we were all expecting to happen.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="839">No need to be scared, Roll. It's just going to be a guy's... thing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="850">I've been dying to see you like this, ~target~. You won't blame me for being curious, right?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="851">Hm, I wanna see what sort of face ~target~'s going to make when it's out...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="852">C'mon, fair is fair, ~target~. Let's see it.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="853">Sorry, ~target~! I think you're being very brave, and I admire that.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="849">Don't be nervous just because I'm an expert on hardware...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="861">Not what I was imagining, but now I'm more curious about it...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="862">Well, I think you're pretty cute, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="863">Oh? It's different than I thought. I sort of... want to see it in action.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="859">So, this is what you're like? I think it actually suits you.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="860">You're different from how I usually imagine guys. It's... kind of exciting...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="870">It only takes a spark to ignite a flame...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="871">So... are you a gentle lover?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="872">As an engineer, I'd love for you to demonstrate its functionality...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="873">You don't need a big gun to impress me, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="869">What will it take for us to make it reach its potential?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="882">Confident, aren't we?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="879">I know this is a point of pride for guys, but I gotta say it just looks like any other penis to me.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="880">Sorry, I was staring a bit. My curiosity isn't entirely satisfied...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="881">Is this part fun for guys? What're you thinking, ~target~? It doesn't look like you want to run and hide.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="883">Such a weird mix of erotic and awkward...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="893">Oh, don't worry, ~target~. I'm a mechanic. I know my way around a gun...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="892">Standing here like this and looking at your penis is... it's making my heart pound...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="891">Well, I could stand to see how you use it...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="890">Gosh, now it's like we're about to... </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="889">This is... a bit of a brand new feeling for me...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="huge_penis" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="620">W-wait, hang on! That seems way too big!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="621">T-that's pretty intimidating...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="622">At some point "bigger is better" starts seeing diminishing returns...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="623">Is it always like that or are you just having a really good time?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="900">Right, so you haven't been nervous at all this whole time, have you?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="901">Men and their obsession with huge guns...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="902">Knowing how guys are, I'm surprised you aren't more confident about this game.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="903">Ah, so we're bringing out the big guns then...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="899">So is it just that you're enjoying yourself, or...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="922">That is not what I was imagining at all. That's... all I'm going to say about it.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="919">Well, there is a certain satisfaction to holding a weapon with some heft to it...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="920">Oh, boys and their toys...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="921">From a mechanical standpoint, I should stress the importance of lubrication...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="918">There certainly is a question of compatibility...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="49">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_Form_ON" sayingMarker="Cat_transformation" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Huh? She's... changing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="81">
                <condition role="target" character="ini" sayingMarker="ini_personality" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">W-wait, was she doing a voice this entire time?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="945">In all of Mega Man's magazines, the women's breasts are always covered by lingerie or their hands. It's actually sort of disappointing...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="946">Go for it, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="947">Honestly, I just didn't want to be the first one to have my breasts out. Even now, I'm still totally nervous! I'm sure you'll be fine, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="943">If my luck isn't so great, ~target~, there's a chance you'll have me for company before too long.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="944">Everybody's body is different. I guess I'm just curious to see how different...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="959">Go ahead and join the club!</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="960">At least you won't be alone...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="961">I already had my turn to show mine, ~target~. C'mon, now its your turn!</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="962">The more the merrier, at least that's what I hope!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="958">I'm not sure we'll be able to help but compare if we're like this...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="969">I think you've got a great body, ~target~! I'm almost jealous!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="968">I don't think there's anything wrong with having smaller breasts. I think they're very cute!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="970">Maybe it's self-serving to say, but I think girls with bodies like you are really cute, ~target~! Really!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="971">With or without your ~clothing~, you look great! Gosh, I might even be a little jealous.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="976">Wow... how could I be as cute as ~target~ is?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="985">I think we're just the right size to be held, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="984">Can I compliment ~target~ without sounding too self-aggrandizing? I can't just not tell her she's sexy, right?</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png" oneShotId="983">Tell me, ~target~: don't you think having bigger breasts would be a pain? Isn't it nice to just be like this?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="982">Are there really people who don't like bodies like yours, ~target~? I guess there's no accounting for taste...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="986">I think tight and sleek is the ideal design myself...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="50">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Cat_transformation" sayingMarker="Cat_transformed" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh... uh... she's cute like that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="52">
                <condition role="target" character="mari_setogaya" saidMarker="Chubby_transformation" sayingMarker="Chubby_transformed" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">That's--- uh, wow! She's really... &lt;i&gt;wow&lt;/i&gt;!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="996">Gosh, ~target~ is so pretty and has a great body. Just lucky, I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="995">No secret where some of that confidence is coming from...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png" oneShotId="994">Of course I think girls like ~target~ are cute too! Who doesn't?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="993">Are all the girls where you're from this attractive, or are you just super-popular or something?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="992">Can I say how sexy your body is to make up for this or would that be too little too late?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1011">I could already tell you might be a bit bigger than me, even through your ~clothing~.  I don't think we both needed to have them out to compare.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1010">My goodness, you're even sexier like this... not that I'm surprised...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="1009">Seeing another girl like this is a lot more exciting than I thought it would be...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="1008">See, now we're together in the same boat. What do you think? Not so bad?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1007">Sure is a lot more exciting than just seeing my own...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">T-they're even bigger than I thought they were!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">H-how could they grow &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; big?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="1021">I mean, I knew they were going to be big... but now that they're out it's like... wow...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1020">At the end of the day, I'm not sure I would like having a body like ~target~'s. It's pretty cramped down in the Flutter's engine compartment as-is.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1019">So, a question suddenly springs to mind: do you have any trouble going up and down ladders?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1018">This is why I probably couldn't pull off ~target~'s style...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1017">Think of all the extra material that would have to go into making your armor... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="1029">And now the difference between us is plain as it could be...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1030">Yeah, I don't think I'd look good with a bust like yours, ~target~. That's clearly more your style...</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png" oneShotId="1031">Okay, okay, the difference was obvious beforehand. There's no reason to go comparing now...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png" oneShotId="1028">It takes all kinds, I guess. I'm still happy just the way I am.</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="1027">~Target~ is so erotic... I sort of I wish I could be...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="ini" saidMarker="ini_personality" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Hang on! This is a lot to take in all at once!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="638">Never really thought about muscles on a woman before...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="639">I still can't get over how strong ~target~ looks...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="640">Her breasts are out... but I just keep staring at her abs...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1050">Well, aside from my own, this is certainly not something I see on a regular basis.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1051">Boy, your luck has &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; not been that good to~background.time~, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1052">You'll be just fine, ~target~. I promise we're not going to say anything mean about you. </state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="1053">What's that look for, ~target~? Are you having second thoughts about going through with it?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1054">I wasn't thinking all that much about this, but now that we're here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1064">I hate to say it, but you sort of get used to it after a little while.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="1061">Come on, don't be shy! It's not like you're going to be the only one with their butt out at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1062">I hope this part isn't too stressful for you, ~target~. I know it was pretty nerve-wracking for me.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="1063">I know this part is pretty embarrassing, but I'm behind you all the way! It's no big deal if you want to change your mind now!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="1060">It's fine to be embarrassed, but the faster you get it over with the easier it is...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="2">
                <condition filter="pirate" gender="female" role="target" />
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I guess that's another thing thing you have in common with Tron...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="4">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh! Oh my! I had no idea. I have... so many questions!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="1086">It's not like you've got anything unusual going on down there. Nothing to be ashamed of!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1087">If I end up where you are, I hope I can be as brave as you are. I'm not used to this sort of thing.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="1088">See, I knew you could do it! I know it's embarrassing, but I hope you're still having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="1089">Alright, that's the spirit! You don't have to give up yet if you want to keep going!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1085">You're even cuter like this! No way anyone could think otherwise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1099">Alright then... here we both are. Gosh, why am I getting so embarrassed all of a sudden?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="1097">See, now we're both in big trouble! It's a bit better with you though.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1096">You know, I don't really see a lot of other women naked. This is all pretty novel for me.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1095">I am going to have one heck of a diary entry to write tonight, that's for sure...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1098">There's no harm in just getting a good look... right?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-8" id="68">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" stage="3" sayingMarker="Caitlin_Beans" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Apricot pie!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="dorothy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Dorothy_s0_1">Wow, a robot. She's so life-like! I wonder who built her...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Samus_s0_1">She's got battle armor just like Mega Man, but I've never seen a design like this. It looks so... alien?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="9S_s0_1">Is he really a machine? He looks so life-like. He's not one of those androids built for The System, is he?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Caitlin_s0_1">Gosh, I hardly have enough time to brush my own hair in the morning. If I had hair like that I'd never get anything done.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="beatrix" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Beatrix_s0_1">That red eye! And that weapon! T-there's no way she's a reaverbot... right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_1">I've never met anyone like you, Y'shtola. It's a bit much to take in, that you can do magic and you have those ears and that tail...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_s1">You're not going to do anything strange, are you Bobobo? It won't be any fun if someone isn't playing by the rules.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Meia_s0_s1">I've never built a large mech before. I've always wanted to, but the parts alone would cost a fortune. And finding a refractor to power it, well, I'd just have to hope I'd be lucky enough to find one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Kaz_s0_1">The way you're dressed, Kaz, makes me feel like I should have worn something nicer. Your clothes don't even have wrinkles!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Fina_s0_1">Fina! You live on an airship too, is that right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_s1">I still can't believe you destroyed all your clothes, Bobobo. Even your shoes and socks! How are you going to get home?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_s1">You really backed yourself into a corner, Bobobo. Maybe you need a spotter when you play this game, to warn you before you get yourself in so much trouble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_s1">I don't think this is very funny, Bobobo. It kind of seems like you're cheating!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_s1">How am I even supposed to prepare for whatever strange thing you're going to do next? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_s1">Was Don Patch here the whole time just waiting for you to lose?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_1">You're out fighting a lot, right, Y'shtola? What sort of equipment do you usually wear for that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_1">I still think you should wear more protective clothing, Y'shtola. It would be much safer that way!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_1">Say, Y'shtola, do your companions every get distracted? Not like in the heat of combat, but in between missions?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_1">How reliable is magic in a fight? Don't you think it would be better to just bring an auto-fire cannon or a rocket launcher?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_1">Gosh, Y'shtola, you're not nervous about losing, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_1">I know it's embarrassing to be seen naked, but at least you're showing us on purpose, right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_1">You know, it might be easier to relax if you weren't working so hard to prevent us from seeing your crotch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Maria_s0_1">Do you really live next to a river, Maria? That sounds so relaxing to be living out in nature like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Maria_s1_1">Living like you do, you must have some good money-saving tips, Maria.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Maria_s2_1">Can I ask you for advice, Maria? I don't mean to be rude, but you seem a lot more experienced than me with stuff like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="Maria_s3_1">I wonder how Mega Man would react if he saw me working in the kitchen with nothing but an apron on...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Maria_s4_1">I wish I had the sort of confidence you do, Maria. Beyond things even like this, I just get scared when I see a reaverbot on the monitor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Kaz_s1_1">So your butler, Charles, he wears his armor around all the time? That's what makes him a "mecha butler?"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="Kaz_s2_1">So, do you have a whole arsenal of demon slaying outfits as well? Ever show up to a job late because you couldn't decide which to wear?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Kaz_s3_1">How does a person become a number on bachelor anyway? That sort of seems like it's super subjective.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Kaz_s4_1">Now that you're nearly naked, I think we can start asking the really embarrassing questions. How about you tell us what happened to your last girlfriend?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="Kaz_s5_1">So, do you think your next girlfriend might be around here? Met anyone &lt;i&gt;special?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Nagatoro_s0_1">So, you and ~player~ are... friends? Is that right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Kumatora_s0_1">All this business about casting magic is so weird to me. Is it really &lt;i&gt;magic&lt;/i&gt; or is there some sort of trick to it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Meia_s1_1">It sounds like your ship must be pretty big to house so many people and vehicles. There must be an army of engineers on board to keep things running smoothly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Gosh, how is it that you're completely invisible? I've encountered reaverbots that could cloak themselves, but not quite this thoroughly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I have tried to build cloaking devices before. It really is difficult to pull off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">So you're just invisible all the time? And you use that to fight crime as a hero?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">You really shouldn't be fighting people without any sort of protection!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This invisibility thing really is a puzzle, isn't it? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">You really are going all the way with this invisibility thing, aren't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Wow, even after this we won't even have the floating hands, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yae" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yae_s0_1">So, Yae, can I ask you what might be an odd question about how you  feel about... something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="sofia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Sofia_s0_1">I thought rich heiresses had suitors lining up to marry them. Never thought I'd see a girl like Sofia here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="sheena" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Sheena_s0_1">Maybe I should build Mega Man some ninja tools! He could take down reaverbots before they even notice him! What sort of weapons do you use, Sheena?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="sheena" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Sheena_s1_1">I'm not really sure I can follow along in a conversation about spirits and magic. That sort of stuff just doesn't sound real to me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="sofia" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Sofia_s1_1">I wish I was sophisticated and worldly like Sofia. Sometimes I wonder what life would be like if I wasn't scrounging through scrap all the time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yae" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yae_s1_1">So what do you do when you're not sneaking around, Yae? What sort of hobbies does a ninja have?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="tea_gardner" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Tea_s0_1">A card collecting game, huh? That sounds like the sort of thing Mega Man would like...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="aggressive" status="lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="183">Remember, ~target~, it's only a game!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="180">I hope ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ isn't too upset about losing...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="181">Okay, let's just remember that we're here to just have fun!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="182">Why do I feel like I've just come face to face with a reaverbot?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="kind" status="lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" oneShotId="192">Aww, I feel kind of bad making ~target~ lose...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="193">You didn't lose that one on purpose, did you, ~target~? You should just worry about yourself, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="throws_game" status="not_naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Well, if this is really what you wanted.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You must be feeling pretty antsy if you're just going to give up like this...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">In its own weird way, it's brave to just give up like that...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I guess winning really isn't everything anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="slutty" status="lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="544">I don't mean anything by this, but I'm guess this isn't your first time doing something like this...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="548">I get the feeling ~target~ is glad to have another chance to show off...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="549">Better with the stripping than the cards, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="shy" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="579">You okay, ~target~? I am just a little bit worried about how you'll hold up...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="580">Well, ready or not, looks like you'll be coming out of your shell...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="581">I don't mean to be rude, ~target~, but this doesn't seem much like your sort of game...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="582">I hope you're really not too uncomfortable, ~target~. I know I'm a little nervous too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" priority="156">
                <condition filter="pirate" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" oneShotId="56">I don't generally trust pirates... but I'm willing to give you a fair shake. No funny business, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="pirate" gender="female" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="58">Yeah take that, Tron! I mean... ~target~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="pirate" gender="male" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="64">Yeah take that, Teisel! I mean... ~target~!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="pirate" role="target" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="75">You know, there's something sort of cathartic about watching a pirate lose...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="78">Sorry,  ~target~, it's nothing personal! Well, you are a pirate, so it is may be just a little personal.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="77">Yeah, well, most pirates aren't all that smart anyways.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="84">I can fly, sail, and drive circles around any pirate. I guess I get to add playing cards to that list too!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="helmet" role="target" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="307">I guess wearing a helmet doesn't protect against &lt;i&gt;everything.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="308">Sometimes I have to remind Mega Man to wear his helmet on missions. I'm glad to see you wore yours here to protect yourself against... falling underwear, I guess?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="other" character="nami" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Nami_s0_1">Nami! You live on a ship too, right? Our ship is The Flutter. She's an older ship, but she's pretty reliable! Well, fairly reliable. As long as I keep up her maintenance, there's not a smoother ride!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Nami_s0_1">You live on your ship, right, Nami? My ship is my home too, The Flutter. What's your ship like? The Flutter is an older model and needs a lot of maintenance, but she's still home sweet home!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_lost_all" role="target" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You probably should've been more careful than that since you lost the last round.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Careful, ~target~, you don't want to end up in a rut!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Okay, so maybe your luck will turn around in the &lt;i&gt;next&lt;/i&gt; next round?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Don't tell me you're losing your nerve, ~target~! You can't let these losses pile up!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Another loss, ~target~? Maybe you should be paying a little closer attention to what's going on.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">It's only two losses, ~target~! Try not to let it get you down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="not_lost_all" role="target" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Are you sure you know what you're doing, ~target~? It seems like you'd need more than bad luck to struggle so much...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It sort of seems like you're losing on purpose, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Come on, ~target~, don't let the inertia of your losses drag you all the way down!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">You're really letting those losses pile up, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I'm convinced there's something more than just bad luck at play here.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">If you want to lose, you're doing a pretty impressive job of it. From a purely statistical standpoint, losing this many times in a row is fairly unlikely.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="5">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="self" />
                <condition count="2" status="not_lost_some" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="223">Now it's your turn, ~target~. Don't worry, I'm sure it'll be my turn soon too! Or... maybe not!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <condition count="2-5" status="not_lost_some" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="211">Well, look whose turn it is! Time to take your first step to defeat!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="219">It's only fair if everyone has to take a turn or two! It's your turn, ~target~, so let's get started!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="218">You had to know this was coming, ~target~! How about you take that first step with pride!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1-6" oneShotId="4">
                <condition status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <condition count="1" status="not_lost_some" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="215">You didn't think we'd forgotten about you, did you, ~target~? We've all had our turn, and now it's yours!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" timeInStage="12-" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Yeah, it was about time for you to lose, ~target~. No more hiding behind your cards!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Oh, look whose luck finally gave out! You couldn't rely on that forever!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">That was quite a streak you had going. Sorry we had to go and mess that up!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">And here I thought you were going to be unbeatable! Maybe there's a few cracks in that armor!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_caskett_resp0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Meia_s0_s2">But you do have them, right? Can't you just take them apart, see how they work? That's how I learned how to build vacuum cleaners and grenade launchers.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Meia_s0_s2">If you have them, how do you not know how to build one? Just take it apart and figure it out. Believe me, it works for car engines, vacuum cleaners, grenade launchers...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" saidMarker="Roll_WheelsOnDa1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_2">Aren't you worried people will see you? You can't just walk home without any pants!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" saidMarker="Roll_Technology1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_2">You can't possibly mean you planned for this? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" saidMarker="Roll_SpiritoftheLaw1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_2">I guess so... but it seems sort of dishonest to wear two pairs like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" saidMarker="Roll_DonPatchMan1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_2">The only thing I'm expecting at this point is that I'm going to be taken completely by surprise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" saidMarker="Roll_StrikeOut1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_2">Ah! Don Patch!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_2">Gosh, I don't even know where to begin. I don't think we even have time for every question I have.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_2">Wait, that's it? You don't wear any armor? Y'shtola! That seems incredibly dangerous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_2">Hmm... well, I guess that's like how Mega Man and I operate. He goes into the ruins to explore and fight while I offer support from back on the Flutter.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_2">Mega Man gets up to the strangest things sometimes. I was worried sick about the upcoming ruins this one time, but then I turned on the TV and there Mega Man was playing in some stupid game show!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_2">But wouldn't it be good to have a backup? You could cast spells with one hand and fire a machine gun with the other! Or maybe a grenade launcher!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp5_1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_2">But you're so beautiful and confident! Gosh, if I looked like you I wouldn't have to worry at all what people thought about me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" saidMarker="roll_resp6_1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_2">What? You too? How did that happen?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" saidMarker="roll_resp7_1" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_2">And now are you going to block your boobs too? You don't think it'd just be easier to put your arms down and just let it all hang out?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Maria_s0_2">Oh? I thought you lived on a farm? Do you just work on the farm but live in an apartment in the city?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Kaz_s0_2">So your appearance must be really important to you, huh? I bet you've got a whole wardrobe full of fashionable clothes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Maria_s2_2">It's a little naive, but I'm not sure how to tell if someone is interested in me romantically. I don't get away from the Flutter a whole lot, so I don't have any experience with these things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Maria_s3_2">I guess I wouldn't &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; that. It'd be nice to turn the tables on him for once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Maria_s4_2">Ha, maybe I should just stick to my strengths, but thanks! Gosh, you're so nice, Maria!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Maria_s1_2">W-what? You don't use it "personally?" </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Kaz_s1_2">Wait, who's Sadie?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Kaz_s2_2">You just go in what you're wearing? Even if it's normal clothes? Don't you need your equipment or protection?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Kaz_s3_2">If you're so popular and everyone knows you're single, why are you still a bachelor? It all sounds a little counter-intuitive.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Kaz_s4_2">Sounds like you didn't want to break up with her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp5_1" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Kaz_s5_2">So even if you met someone really special, you wouldn't do it? Even if she was some perfect super girl?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" sayingMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wha---what?! S-Sakura? Your head is---</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_reply01" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Nagatoro_s0_1">Gosh, you really must know each other. I mean, I really hope you wouldn't talk like that to someone you didn't know!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Nagatoro_s0_1">Are you... sure? I mean... I guess I wouldn't even &lt;i&gt;think&lt;/i&gt; about talking to someone I didn't know like that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_s0_1_resp" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Kumatora_s0_2">Oh, PSI? I know what that is. I wouldn't be much of an engineer if I didn't know about that!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Kumatora_s0_2">PSI? Of course I know about that! I'm an engineer &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; a pilot after all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="47">
                <condition role="target" character="shantae" stage="1" sayingMarker="monkey" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah! Data?!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">What? D-data? Is that you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yae" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Yae_s0_2">Oh, you do? Was it that obvious? I thought it might be kind of weird... but I'm just so curious to know...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="sofia" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Sofia_s0_2">Gosh, sounds complicated. It is sort of hard to tell if someone is really interested in you. Would you have been happier if he had pursued you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" stage="0" saidMarker="resp_roll0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Nami_s0_2">That's right! The Flutter does fly! She's an airship!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Nami_s0_2">Well, that really is why it's called the Flutter! She's an airship! We travel through the sky!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="sheena" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Sheena_s0_2">Paper seals? I don't... think I've ever made any weapons with paper.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="sheena" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Sheena_s1_2">I know that and I am interested, but I just don't want to get confused. It just feels like you have these huge differences from me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="sofia" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Sofia_s1_2">Right, I guess a girl like you wouldn't be interested in something like that. You probably have more exciting things to talk about, like being courted by princes and going to fancy parties...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yae" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Yae_s1_2">If you want to learn baking, I could give you some pointers! I'm just as good with a whisk as I am with a wrench!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh! Oh no!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">He left his necklace totally intact though. I wonder if it's special to him somehow...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Uh-oh. I've got a bad feeling about this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh, come on! Don't tell me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">H-hold on! What are you doing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Is that any way to treat your friend, Bobobo?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Samus_s0_2">I'd love to get your impression on it and maybe take a look at how it's put together! I'm always in the market for ideas to build better armor! After all, it's a spotter's job to make sure her digger stays safe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="31">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wah! S-Saki? What the---?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="55">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">T-that's--- that's a lot of make-up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="59">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Seems like you need to tighten the action on that trigger.</state>
                <state img="#-furious.png">Wait, Brock! Why wasn't the safety on?!</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">Maybe this is a good time to talk about trigger discipline...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="63">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Huh? What in the world is this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Gosh, this is pretty serious for you, huh? What could it... be?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Would it be possible to reverse engineer that sort of cloaking technology from your cells? Hopefully your biology isn't too far off from ours...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png">I know it's not impossible though, it definitely can be done! It's just hard to get a hold of the parts...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">But your clothes aren't invisible. The bad guys could still see you by your clothes which would take away your whole advantage, so that means...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Being invisible is handy, but what if the enemy has thermal imaging or locates targets through sonar?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">It really all hinges upon the element of surprise. Moving about unseen and popping up at the exact right moment to catch the enemy off guard!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Is that really fair? We can't see any of you, but you can see all of us!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">You wouldn't just leave without saying anything, right? It would be super easy for you to just sneak away...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" oneShotId="6">
                <condition filter="blonde" status="not_exposed" role="target" />
                <condition filter="green_eyes" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Huh... I'm just noticing how similar ~target~ and I look. I'm not crazy for thinking that, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="scantily-clad" filterOut="shy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="314">Well, ~target~ sure is a lot braver than me. I've only seen outfits like ~target.ifMale(his|hers)~ in magazines...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="311">You weren't really working with much in the first place either...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="312">Did you mean to wear so little when you came here? It's... so bold...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="313">It doesn't seem like you've got any problem showing off your body, but maybe I shouldn't assume...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="wealthy" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="387">Rich people sure do have a lot of... stuff.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="388">Huh, even if we're not playing for money, people &lt;i&gt;with&lt;/i&gt; money still kinda have the advantage.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="385">You know, if I had money I would probably spend it all on improvements to the Flutter instead of clothes.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="386">I still think I'd wear the same sort of clothes even if we had a lot of money. I can't really picture myself all decked out like ~target~ is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="tomboy" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="471">Do people call you a tomboy too, ~target~? I feel like I'm plenty girly, but I guess people forget all that when they see all the power tools...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="469">Hey, ~target~, do you think if I wore a skirt every so often people wouldn't call me a tomboy so much? It's too bad I don't own a skirt...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="470">I feel like calling someone a "tomboy" is kind of mean. I'm still a girl and I like girly things, I just also like engines and ordinance. I'm really just a normal girl!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition filter="mechanic" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="484">Hey, ~target~, do you have any spare tools you'd be willing to part with? I'm always in the market for something new!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="485">So what kind of stuff do you work on anyway? Just cars and engines or do you dabble in robotics too? How's that working out for you?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="486">Do you know of any good places to get scrap, ~target~? I figure you must work with a lot of metal and I'm really not opposed to supplementing my own stockpile with extra-dimensional parts.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="490">Build anything interesting lately or have you just been taking off your clothes?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Oh, so you are going to take your ~clothing~ off. I sort of thought you would have done that before you... you know.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">So, did you just forget you were wearing ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ until now?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Well, if you don't want to lose I guess you have to take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You do have your priorities straight right, ~target~? It seems like you might be just a little mixed up...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="armor" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="364">Good armor is hard to come by, huh? I try to keep Mega Man in armor that won't get him killed when he's out on digs.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="365">Who makes your armor, ~target~? Does it work well for you? Are you able to move around comfortably? Do you have a coolant system in there?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="366">Diggers need sturdy armor to do their jobs. Something that will stand up to the weapons reaverbots use. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="mask" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="261" marker="Mask">You could keep the mask on if it's that important to you; although, I suppose we might not actually know who you are.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="262" marker="Mask">Oh, ~target~ is so mysterious! I've been wondering what's under there!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="263" marker="Mask">You're going to show us your face? I thought you wanted to hide your identity!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="264" marker="Mask">Well... I am pretty curious about what your face looks like...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="hat" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="278" marker="WhereHat">Hey, that's a pretty neat hat! Where did you get yours? Mine used to be my dad's!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="291">Yeah, without my hat my hair just goes everywhere. It's a real problem when I'm trying to get things done in my workshop or in the engine room.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="430" marker="Roll_1">I'm still a little nervous about all this. It's not the sort of thing I usually get up to.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png" oneShotId="428" marker="Roll_2">I'm not too shy when it comes to excitement, just so you know! I'm one half of a digging operation! Digging for treasure and scrap is no job for the faint of heart!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="429" marker="Roll_3">I hope Mega Man isn't too worried with me being gone...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-8" id="58">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <condition role="other" character="twisted_fate" sayingMarker="Bobobo_Broken" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh... but... I'd rather have him here than Bobobo...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="3" />
                <condition role="opp" character="kekko_kamen" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">&lt;i&gt;You also fight crime naked?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1 5-8" id="87">
                <condition role="target" character="suzuya" stage="4" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">The shirt doesn't really cover all that much like that, does it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" id="88">
                <condition role="target" character="suzuya" stage="4" />
                <test expr="~target.costume~" value="default" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">No bra and now we're both having the same little problems...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="33">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh no! Y-your head! H-hold on! I'll go get my rivet gun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" saidMarker="Roll_WheelsOnDa2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_3">What's obvious about that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" saidMarker="Roll_Technology2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_3">What kind of half-baked plan is this?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" saidMarker="Roll_SpiritoftheLaw2" />
                <state img="#-furious.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_3">Having &lt;i&gt;three&lt;/i&gt; doesn't make it any better!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" saidMarker="Roll_DonPatchMan2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_3">Okay, now this has to be actually cheating, Bobobo.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" saidMarker="Roll_StrikeOut2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_3">I thought Don Patch was your friend! Why would you do that to him?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_3">I mean, it definitely seems like the ears are attached to your head. I'm sure at some point I'll get to see where your tail attaches too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_3">It seems wrong to me. Without armor, even a grazing blow could really hurt you! And that dress! Don't you ever step on it while trying to move quickly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_3">But I do! I'm inside the Flutter! It's far safer than just standing around in the open, even if I'm not actually down in the ruins myself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_3">One time Mega Man helped a bunch of Servbots open up a burger restaurant. He just can't turn down anyone who asks him for help...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_3">There's all kinds of options out there! Maybe a giant drill bit or some proximity mines or a laser cannon or a beam sword...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" saidMarker="roll_resp5_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_3">Kinda seems like you're even more nervous than me! I knew you must be brave, but I guess I underestimated just how much!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" saidMarker="roll_resp6_2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_3">That's funny. I was never in any danger, but it's happened to me twice as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="8" saidMarker="roll_resp7_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_3">You don't exactly &lt;i&gt;look&lt;/i&gt; relaxed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Kaz_s0_3">Hm, other than my pajamas and my winter clothes, I just own a bunch of this outfit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Maria_s1_3">That sounds lovely! I guess it would be a little hard for an entire society to work like that, but I'm glad your community is so supportive and hardworking!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Maria_s2_3">S-so you're an advocate of the direct approach? I mean, I guess that sort of seems obvious now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Maria_s3_3">I kind of like the way you're thinking right now, Maria.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Maria_s4_3">Or maybe I should say you're &lt;i&gt;mostly&lt;/i&gt; nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Maria_s0_3">That sort of sounds like it would go against some kind of zoning law?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Kaz_s1_3">Are you saying you didn't know she was in there?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Kaz_s2_3">Aren't demons dangerous? Shouldn't you take the necessary precautions?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Kaz_s3_3">Okay, so you're a bit of a romantic? That's not "complicated," Kaz. I think that's pretty normal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Kaz_s4_3">Okay, that wasn't embarrassing. That was just... depressing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="6" saidMarker="roll_resp5_2" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Kaz_s5_3">You're not quite as smooth as you think you are since you've got your underwear off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_caskett_resp01" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Meia_s0_3">If they're not useful, that's even more reason to take them apart! You can never have too many spare parts, especially if you've got other machines to take care of.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Meia_s0_3">Taking them apart still makes sense even if they're not useful to you. I'm sure the parts and the scrap metal could still be useful. It'll be extra material for your other vessels.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="30">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="4" saidMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Does that happen a lot? Do... do you need me to bolt your head to your neck?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="54">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_kh" stage="2" sayingMarker="keyblade_reveal" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">Oooh, a sword? I've made a few swords myself. They were all beam swords, of course.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_reply02" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Nagatoro_s0_3">Oh, so it's like a game between you two then? Gosh, I guess you two must be awfully close!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yae" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Yae_s0_3">Okay, then I have to know: do ninjas really hate pirates?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="sofia" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Sofia_s0_3">Oh, I get it! He just doesn't like girls! He didn't have a problem with you personally and you were glad to find that out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="sheena" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Sheena_s0_3">And I thought all ninjas used stars or daggers to fight. I don't think Mega Man would be thrilled about fighting with paper.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="sheena" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Sheena_s1_3">N-no! I didn't mean--- even if they are very different, b-b-but I just meant, like, experiences and that sort of thing! Not our--- I'm so sorry!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="sofia" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Sofia_s1_3">Right. Of course you don't want to talk about junk and garbage. I don't even know why I said anything!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yae" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Yae_s1_3">Gosh, I've never had a friend over to bake with! It'll be so much fun! I've even got an extra apron you can wear!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">His nosehairs really just went everywhere! It was incredible! And... and terrifying? And a little gross?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Oh, well, I guess not? He doesn't really seem like the sentimental type.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait! Was this your plan all along? Why? Why do it like this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">Exactly how long is this going to go on for? !</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-furious.png">At least you were &lt;i&gt;wearing&lt;/i&gt; all that underwear! Th-this has to be cheating!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">With everything that was going on... I hardly noticed how rugged his body is. ..</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="32">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Does that happen a lot? It must be rough being undead. Maybe you need a collar riveted to your neck to keep your head on...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="48">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm... I wonder if I could design a system that would allow Mega Man to power up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Samus_s0_3">Oh, wow! You're a lot prettier--- I mean, taller--- I mean, blonde-er than I was expecting!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="83">
                <condition role="target" character="myriam" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">I figured either the box was going to come off first or last. I was sort of hoping it was going to be first...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="84">
                <condition role="target" character="myriam" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Well, well. Look who finally decided to join us...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="franziska" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">You're not mad, right, Franziska? I mean... I'm not sure of a lot of things, but I am sure I don't want to get cropped...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Well... I guess a fake Chihiro is better than none?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1 5-8" id="85">
                <condition role="target" character="felix" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png">That really don't leave much to the imagination, does it? </state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Oooh, a little preview of the treasure deeper within...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2-4" id="86">
                <condition role="target" character="felix" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">That's the gamble with tight clothing... isn't it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Wait, can your cells even be observed? Do they show up under an electron microscope? Just how invisible are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-worried.png">And I've got more important things to do than build a cloaking devices to use in the bathtub...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">&lt;i&gt;You fight crime naked?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">There has to be some way to be protected and be invisible. If I had time, I'm sure I could come up with something...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">... But I'm pretty sure a pair of floating panties would throw pretty much anyone off guard.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I mean... even if it is kind of hot just knowing that you're there... completely naked...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="toru_hagakure" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">... You're still there now, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_GetEquipped3" />
                <state img="#-furious.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_1a">Who are you talking to?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_GetEquipped3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_1b">W-what? You're copying me?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="exhibitionist" status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I guess I shouldn't be surprised. ~Target~ does seem like ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ wants to be seen...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">~Target~ doesn't seem to mind being naked though, so I guess I should have seen this coming.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-8">
                <condition filter="athletic" status="topless" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="104">So, do you work out? Seems like you've got plenty of endurance.</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="105">Huh... Mega Man's body isn't quite so... defined...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="106">Hey, ~target~. I can appreciate a well-tuned machine, if you catch my meaning.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="107">Boy, is it getting steamy around here or is that just... uh... is that all ~target~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8">
                <condition filter="robot" status="decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="147">I guess it's a bit strange to me that someone would build a robot with purely cosmetic aspects to it. They must have a lot of resources on hand...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="146">If I had a screwdriver... could I take ~target~ apart and see how ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ works?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="145">I guess the fact you're programmed to wear clothes means you've got something under there to hide. </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="144">I probably shouldn't be so surprised by such a human-esque robot considering everything I've learned...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="148">I wonder what the purpose was for building such an attractive robot.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="149">It would probably be rude to ask ~target~ if I could see ~target.ifMale(his|her)~ schematics, right? Best to wait until after I've seen ~target.ifMale(hi|her)~ naked for that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-8" oneShotId="3">
                <condition filter="brunette" status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="171">Oh... okay... I see... I just have a &lt;i&gt;thing&lt;/i&gt; for brunettes. Neat.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="172">I'm starting to think I just have a thing for brunettes... a thought I am having right now for no &lt;i&gt;specific&lt;/i&gt; reason.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="scantily-clad" status="not_exposed" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="327">Ah, m-my imagination isn't running wild! It's running at a perfectly normal speed, p-probably!</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="348">I'm not complaining, of course...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="347">Well, if you can be brave, then maybe I can be too...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="359">Or maybe I just came here overdressed? Hm...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="exhibitionist" status="not_decent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="510">~Target~ seems almost too okay with all of this...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="511">It's going to hard to get you on the back foot, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="512">Man, what's it going to take you flinch? </state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="513">Why am I feeling embarrassed? ~Target~ is the one who stripped and ~target.ifMale(he's|she's)~ not bothered even a little...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition filter="weapon" role="target" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="245">Say, ~target~, how's that weapon treating you anyway? I think it could use more than a few modifications! I know a girl--- me--- who can fix you up for just a few {small}thousand{!reset} zenny!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="251">Your weapon seems a little... outdated. Believe me, you could do with an upgrade. I just need a laser pointer and a transistor board...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="246">Say, ~target~, why not trade up for a better weapon? I don't know what you're comfortable with usually, but you can't go wrong with something that fires incendiary devices!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="252">I think your weapon has a nice, classical style to it, but a modern warrior should get equipped with something much more practical! I can see you using something with an advanced auto-targeting system! How does that sound!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="249">I wonder if Mega Man could use a weapon like ~target~'s? It doesn't hurt to switch things up from the Buster Cannon every once and a while.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="248">Are you happy with your weapon right now, ~target~? The range? The weight? I could improve those things and make it explode! Speaking of explosions, let's talk advanced armor...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="247">Since you're armed and all, ~target~, you must be pretty handy in a fight; however, don't you think you'd be even handier if your weapon had a built-in missile launcher? I'd give you a discount on the parts and labor!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="250">~Target~'s weapon is... hmm... I guess your options are limited when you can't remove your hand and mount the weapon on your wrist interface...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Well, whatever floats your boat! No reason you can't keep stripping until you're all out of clothes!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I can respect that you're not ready to lose. I guess the point is to win after all!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Seems like maybe you're just showing off, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Whatever the case is, you shouldn't be so certain it's going to save you here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="lost_all" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="447">I guess you don't need those to see? Or maybe you just really don't want to lose?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="448">Wow, you look totally different without your glasses! I guess that was dramatic enough to save for last!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="453">Is this your last resort, ~target~? You can still see, right?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="454">Gosh, you look so different without your glasses on. Somehow it's a bigger change than when you took practically everything else off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="armor" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="370">Maybe your armor could use some modifications? Stabilizers to keep you from falling over during combat? A data chip to keep you from lighting on fire?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="371">Junk shops always have the best stuff laying around for armor parts. It can be a little pricey, but it's hard to put a price on staying alive.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="372">Say, what kind of threat are you up against that you need armor for? Seems like it's pretty safe around here. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Mask&gt;0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="269" marker="Mask=0">Yeah, I don't recognize you at all! Who would I even tell I saw your real face?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="269" marker="Mask=0">So... are we now all sworn to secrecy not to tell anyone what you actually look like?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" oneShotId="269" marker="Mask=0">Gosh, no reason to hide a face like that!</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="269" marker="Mask=0">Hm... well... I'm not sure what I was expecting.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="8">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Roll_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I spend most of my time working on our ship, the Flutter! Gramps is getting too old to take care of her, so it's up to me to take care of maintenance and upkeep! It's a full time job!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Roll_2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Although, I guess my job is pretty safe. Mega Man is the one who goes into the ruins and faces the danger directly. I stay on the ship and monitor his surroundings with my equipment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5" oneShotId="10">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="Roll_3" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">He's always watched out for me, ever since Gramps found him back when Mega Man and I were just kids. He's sorta... I dunno... y'know?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="57">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh no! Wait! Oh, I guess we can't really stop her...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="53">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh, wow, I had no idea! I mean, you hid it so well!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="125">I guess when they built you, they had this sort of thing in mind. Does... does it work?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="126">I've never considering building a robot with a working... I mean, surely you weren't built just for this purpose, right?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="127">I guess you would want to build an android as close to a human as possible, but to go this far? It just seems like your creator had ulterior motives.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="124">I was sort of expecting this, but it's still kind of shocking to actually see it! I guess you were built with this kind of stuff in mind!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="116">It actually wouldn't be very hard to build a robot with functioning genitalia, but there aren't a whole lot of reasons to do so aside from the... let's say "obvious" ones...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="117">Whoever made you decided you should be this attractive and have working genitalia, so... yeah... there's really only one conclusion I can draw from that.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="118">Isn't there some kind of ethics guideline that prevents people from building robots with... well, I'm not saying it matters I'm just... curious...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="119">Right, I guess you wouldn't be here if you weren't... "fully equipped." Please forget I used those words to describe you...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="no_genitals" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">What the...</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Is this seriously happening?</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">I can't believe we're watching this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="tandem" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm embarrassed just watching them, but they don't seem bothered at all to be seen like this.</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Must be nice to have someone you feel so comfortable with...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="4">I knew people would be masturbating, but this is more than I was anticipating!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Even watching them is almost too stimulating...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition filter="tandem" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Seeing them... I feel a little lonely...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I wish I had someone to help me out too...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="10">Watching them makes me feel like I could do something like that too... but no? Right? No way!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">They're both so... ah, I wish that I could...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="joke_forfeit" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">I just... I have no idea how I'm supposed to feel about what just happened.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1117">If you wanted to back out now, ~target~, I wouldn't blame you...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1118">Looks like this is the end of the line for you, ~target~. Nice try though!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1119">Boy, am I glad I'm not in your shoes. I've had run-ins with reaverbots less thrilling than all this.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1115">I don't know who came up with these rules, but it is a pretty exciting way to end this off...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1116">You really hung in there right until the end huh? Well... can't say I don't get it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1126">Okay, ~target~, I'll try not to stare too much, but only when you're not looking...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="1128">For all your stubbornness, you still lost it all. At least you tried.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1125">I might be a little too excited to see this play out...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="1129">Now you've really got to show us something big, if you wouldn't mind.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="1127">It's not all that bad, right, ~target~? I mean, I'm sure by now you're probably feeling up to the task.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="56">
                <condition role="other" character="wasp" stage="0-7" saidMarker="shrinking" sayingMarker="shrinkimage" />
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Holy cow! That's amazing! How... how did you build a device to do &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="1146">Oh, do I, uh, watch or look away or what? I don't want to be rude...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1147">I probably shouldn't watch too much, should I?</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png" oneShotId="1148">Hm, feels pretty good to win! I just hope ~target~ ends up feeling good too.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1149">You know, I wonder if Mega Man has ever done this while I was on the Flutter with him? I never really thought about it...</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="1145">Talking and thinking about it is one thing, but when it actually comes down to it... it's still a bit much!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1159">Did I already say I was curious to see how you used it? I'm so giddy I can't really remember.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="1158">If you want to peek at me at all, I wouldn't mind too much...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1157">We'll be here still, but you're on your own, ~target~. Maybe pretend we're not here.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="1156">What else can I say? Do your best, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1155">So... if I end up staring at you, just let me know if it makes you self-conscious... or if it makes you anything else!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">~Target~ seems like he's really making an effort...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I can barely focus for two seconds before I look over at ~target~ again...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Now it really feels like I'm seeing something I was not meant to see...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">... Am I staring too much? It doesn't seem to be bothering you... I think...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I probably shouldn't ask what ~target~ has on his mind...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Am I imagining ~target~ looking over here, or... </state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">~Target~ is... he really is... gosh...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I this how all guys do it? Does Mega Man also...?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I might end up thinking about this later...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">So... are you sprinting or jogging to the finish line?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Getting a little... hot, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">So... is he using his imagination or is he just looking around...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You don't really look like you're being punished, ~target~. It's no problem...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">So... would you consider yourself gentle, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6 8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I can't help but look over at where ~target~ is... </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">So, exactly how long do you plan on going for?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Seeing ~target~ turned on is... stimulating...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">This is a lot more than I could have hoped for from  ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Is that how you like it, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">My heart is pounding about a mile a minute right now...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">This is so strange, but I don't think it's so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">~Target~ doesn't seem bothered at all that he's not alone.</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Is it always so exciting?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm like this and ~target~ is like that... it's almost like...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">If you're in over your head, you might need a spotter, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">You want more, don't you, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Are you getting everything out of this you hoped for, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I'm a quick learner and good with my hands, ~target~. Just a thought...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Is ~target~ going to... look this way?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Each stroke... would be a thrust in...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I've been watching ~target~ so closely... I think I synced up...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">So much more exciting than just being alone... imagining...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Seeing you aroused, arouses me. Do I do the same for you, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">If I gave him the chance... would ~target~ feel me instead?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">He's not beckoning, he's just... but I'm...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I've fantasized about it before... a man touching himself... thinking about me...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">It's hot... seeing him... pleased...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">He's being so... would he treat his partner like that?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">We could certainly take what we have... and make something interesting...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" saidMarker="Finisher_ActualReference" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Abnormal right up until the very end...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" saidMarker="Finisher_ApotheBOsis" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Just when I felt like I wasn't going crazy he goes and does... &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" saidMarker="Finisher_MinusTheBear" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Looks like that wasn't the fix for whatever is wrong with your head!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="1166">G-gosh... w-wow... he really... he really came in front of us...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1167">Does anybody else feel a sort of... tingling?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1168">Obviously, ~target~ had a lot of fun here... obviously.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1169">And just like that, the excitement is over, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1165">So in the end he did... that's... it's pretty cute...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="1176">You held out as long as you could, huh? I admire that, really...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="1177">Hm, he's cute when he's satisfied...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1178">It seems like you enjoyed yourself, but not as much as I am...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="1179">Ha ha... so cute...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="1175">Just take a moment, ~target~. I think... I might need one too...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-8" id="45">
                <condition role="target" character="nami" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Hey, now &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; is some interesting engineering!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1197">~Target~ got unlucky just one too many times. Good news for the rest of us.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1198">Maybe it's just bad luck, ~target~, but it might be that poker just isn't your game.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1199">Gosh, that's too bad for you, ~target~. I hope you don't feel too bad about losing.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1196">That's okay, ~target~. No hard feelings, right? You played a good game!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1195">Looks like we got the better of you, ~target~! Maybe you already saw it coming though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1211">So, ~target~ lost? That means she'll...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1212">~Target~'s luck ran out, huh? I sort of feel bad for her.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1213">If ~target~ lost now, then I guess that means she's completely out of the game...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="1214">That's too bad, ~target~. I was sort of rooting for you a little...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1210">Oh, that's too bad, ~target~. It's not much fun to lose, huh?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8" id="46">
                <condition role="target" character="binah" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Eek! What? Is this some kind of security measure?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="61">
                <condition role="target" character="nico_robin" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Oooookay... so this is going to be interesting to watch... isn't it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1224">This is... unusual for you, right? If I was in your shoes, I'd normally double check to make sure the door is locked...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="1223">Oh, I don't want to stare too much, b-but I'm really curious...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1222">I don't usually think too much about other girls masturbating. This whole game is a bit of a novel experience for me.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1221">I'm a bit more excited about this than I thought I would be. ~Target~'s so beautiful though... so...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1220">You don't show this side of you to just anybody, huh? I mean... I sure don't...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="1244">Just when I thought it couldn't get more exciting...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1243">Wow, I never really... I just... sorry, I got a chill down my spine just now.</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="1242">Okay... I'd love to see... just a bit of this...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1241">Sorry if I stare a bit, ~target~. It's just that I want to see how you treat yourself...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="1240">~Target~'s pleasure face... I'll get to see it...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" sayingMarker="joint-mast-intro" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Sayori and Monika are--- wait, together?!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">T-They're so bold! Is Sayori really going to--- with Monika--- h-huh?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" saidMarker="joint-masturbation-2" />
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="445">... I'd bet... Monika's tongue must be...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png" oneShotId="446">I've never seen a girl... to another girl...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6 8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">~Target~ is so beautiful and seeing her like this is... really hot...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Don't stop now, ~target~. I'd like to see a little more...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">~Target~ really isn't holding back, is she? Must feel nice...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I never imagined I'd see ~target~ make a face like that...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Why don't you show us how you like it, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Gosh, I'm shaking so much from excitement it's embarrassing...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I never thought watching ~target~ would be so thrilling...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">~Target~ is able to lose herself, even in front of us...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I knew this would be exciting, but this is a lot more than I thought.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Please let everyone be looking at ~target~ and not notice that I'm getting...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">~Target~ is stirring up as much in me as she is herself...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">~Target~'s just... I mean, look at her...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm sure I could learn a lot from watching ~target~ if my mind would stop wandering.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I do wonder what sort of thing ~target~ has going through her head...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Are you watching me at all, ~target~? </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Look at us, ~target~. Did you ever imagine?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">If I touch myself like ~target~ touches herself... it's almost like...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">With another girl here... it's so much more stimulating...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I'm enjoying watching you, ~target~. Does watching me... do anything for you?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">It might be better... if I let ~target~ do it for me...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Is ~target~ the sort to... to take the lead?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I didn't think I would be like this... for another woman...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I just want to see her... a little bit more...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">... But what does her body feel like? Soft? Warm? I'm just... imagining...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I just can't keep from having weird thoughts. Not when I'm like this. R-right, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Am I like that when I touch myself? </state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Whenever ~target~ makes a noise, I can't help but picture myself... ahem, where were we again?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">~Target~ is showing us something really special. That's quite the treasure...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Even like this... she's beautiful...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">You know, looking at ~target~... I'm starting to feel like maybe losing wouldn't be so bad?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Did ~target~ just look at me or did I imagine that? </state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Just the look on ~target~'s face is... is so... wow...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">If I don't lose... I might have to hurry home and just... take care of myself anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm going to see this in my head later, aren't I?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">... That's a... she's quite... hm...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="717">Well... it's not like I've haven't ever imagined women doing this sort of thing. I mean... you know... like anyone else has...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Watching ~target~ does make me feel a little less nervous about all this...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I'm feeling a little... kind of...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">If I think about what ~target~ is doing too much, I'm going to have to... you know...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="monika" sayingMarker="joint-masturbation-finished" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Monika... Sayori... I think you've given me a lot to think about...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">... Is it strange that I kept picturing myself in Monika's place? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="1261">That looked like... it felt really good...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1262">Do I make a face like that when I climax? That was so... sexy...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="1263">Do you need a minute, ~target~? You look like you might still be riding the wave.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" oneShotId="1264">Take your time and enjoy it, ~target~. You might not feel so euphoric when you come back down.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1260">W-well... when a girl is as cute as ~target~, you can't help but feel a bit flustered when she's doing that...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1274">The excited pit in my stomach just got a whole lot heavier.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1273">That might be worthy of applause...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1272">When I met  ~target~, I did not imagine I'd be seeing her make that face.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="1271">You're really sexy, ~target~, but I feel like you have to know that by now...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="1270">Just seeing that... I feel like I need to... um... never mind...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, oh no! Oh, I was hoping I wouldn't have to go first. Oh well, g-guess that's just my luck.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, I just knew this was going to happen! Even after I tried so hard just not to have to go first!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="leon" sayingMarker="roll_manyBoys" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="leon_respF_poly">I can't say I have. All of my fantasies are much more intimate, personal... focused...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh no! I lost? Guess I should have been more careful, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Fine, I can see that I'm beat. I tried my best, but luck just wasn't on my side to~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">Oh, alright. You won fair and square. No reason to make a big fuss about it.</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I had a feeling it was going to be me next! Why couldn't I have been wrong?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-lost.png">Well, I may as well make the best of it, right? I am feeling like I could...</state>
                <state img="#-lost.png">I can do this. It's embarrassing, but it's not like it will be unpleasant, right? </state>
                <state img="#-lost.png">This is all so unusual. Hopefully I can just relax and enjoy myself...</state>
                <state img="#-lost.png">But maybe... I mean, it could be sort of fun...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Ooh... okay, that's... that's it...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I just need... a little extra...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">G-gosh... everybody is looking...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">All this excitement does have me feeling pretty horny...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">There's not a lot of privacy on the Flutter. I make sure the bath faucet is running when I do this at home.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Well, this makes for good stress release at least...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">This is nice... but will it be enough?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">This is... so... b-but still it feels...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Hm... c'mon...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Mmf, oh, I've got it now...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hah... oh, right there...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Hope I'm not... making too much noise...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Even when I focus on me... I can feel everyone else's...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">No time to rest. No need to rest...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I can't stop picture myself... on my back... being toyed with...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">No sense in getting all flustered. It's too late for that...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">When you stop worrying, all the attention is... pretty hot...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I haven't been this ex--- no, horny in a while.</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Easy pressure... gentle touch... that's it...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I was unsure... but I really could cum like this...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I need... n-not enough...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">H-hahn... I'm...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I can't help but rush... I just want it so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I got so wet... even before...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavyc.png">Ha... ha... almost... I'm almost...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png">I'm so close... I can't stand it...</state>
                <state img="#-heavya.png">Mm, I'm going to... to...</state>
                <state img="#-heavya.png">Ah, I'm... haa... almost...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png">Feels like it's going to be a big one...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyc.png">Oh, faster... come on now...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyc.png">This feels... like a big one...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png">I couldn't stop it... even if I wanted to...</state>
                <state img="#-heavya.png">Close... I'm... so close...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-climax.png">Mm... that's it...</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png">It's... h-here!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">Wow... that was amazing. I think... I think I needed that...</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">H-hang on... I'm still... I just need a second...</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">S-stop everything... I'm not... the moment is still here...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I hope this doesn't go on for too much longer. I've got to get back to the Flutter to help cook dinner.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Just because I'm done doesn't mean I'm still not just the tiniest bit in the mood...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I wonder if I'd still be in the game if I'd taken some more risks...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm, I'm going to need a bath after this...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Mmm... hmm...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I hope nobody back home hears about any of this...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I feel so relaxed now. It's probably not a good idea to take a nap here on the floor though, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">It is fun to just watch without having to worry about whether I'm going to win or lose.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Should I... be putting my clothes back on now?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Just keep doing your best!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">No, it's fine. I'm used to being left out of the action...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png" oneShotId="689">It's straight back to the Flutter for me after this. I got all the maintenance done before I came here, but by now I bet she's got a new problem. </state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" oneShotId="690">How big is this whole place anyway? Has anyone kept their clothes on long enough to really explore it?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="691">... How hard would it be in inconspicuously sound-proof my room?</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">At least it's a nice chance to relax...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">This sort of thing really makes you look your own sexuality straight in the face, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Are you still having fun, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Does sitting around like this count as aftercare, or...?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png" oneShotId="692">I don't make a habit of sitting around naked at home, but, you know, sometimes you get out of the bath and you just get sidetracked before you get your clothes back on.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png" oneShotId="693">Maybe I should stop by somewhere and get something special for dinner. It would make for a great alibi.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">So that's it then? I won? That went better than I could've hoped for.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Not too shabby, huh? I've got a trick or two up my sleeve, so don't you forget it?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I feel kind of bad that I won without really getting naked. No hard feelings, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Another close call! Well, thanks for playing! I had a lot of fun!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">That's that. It's too bad since I was starting to get used to standing around like this.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You came close, but it wasn't good enough. I hope you still had fun!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Well, congratulations, ~target~! Luck really was on your side to~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I guess you could say ~target~ won, but ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ is the only one here who didn't cum...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Gosh, that was embarrassing. Well, ~target~, I hope you had a good time too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8" hidden="1">
                <condition role="target" character="human" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" collectible="dirty_magazine">Unlocks the Dirty Magazine Collectible.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
