<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.9.2 at 10:27:21 PM on March 01, 2023. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.9.2</version>
    <first>Roll</first>
    <last>Caskett</last>
    <label>Roll</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>29</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>



    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="singlet" generic="leotard" position="both" type="major" />
        <clothing name="hat" generic="hat" position="head" type="extra" />
        <clothing name="shorts" generic="shorts" position="lower" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="jacket" generic="jacket" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hello there! How are you? Are you ready to play?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hey! Hello! How are you feeling? Prepared to play?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Oh, hello! Thanks for having me! I hope you're prepared to play!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="3" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Is this everyone? I think there's room for a couple more people.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Are we just going to have three in? I think that could be fun.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">A small group wouldn't be so bad, but a big group might be more comfortable.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="4" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">The more the merrier, of course!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">So is this the whole group or are we waiting for one more person?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Is this everyone now? Just the four of us?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition count="5" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">Oh, this is good! I think I'll feel a lot more comfortable in a big group!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It looks like everyone is here now! Shouldn't we get going?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">It should be a lot of fun with lots of people! Does this mean we're ready to start now?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">This isn't the sort of thing I usually do, but it should be pretty exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I'm Roll, if you didn't know. I'm sure we're about to get to know each other very well.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Okay, let's get going! I know I'm ready to go!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I guess I'll exchange these ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Can I get ~cards.text~ new ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~? That would be great!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I'm going to do ~cards.text~ ~cards.ifplural(cards|card)~ this time, if that's okay.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-stretch.png">I hope everything works out this time. I've got a good feeling about this.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Looks like it's smooth sailing for me!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">This is a lot of fun! It's a little weird, but I think I was craving a little excitement.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">~Player~? Are you doing okay? You're not getting distracted, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Okay, I'm all set! Get ready to read 'em and weep!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Card games aren't that hard for me. Just like engineering and cooking, it's all about putting the right pieces together.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">How is it going, ~player~? Did you get the hand you wanted?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Even when it looks like the coast is clear, it's best to be careful.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">If I can fly the Flutter through pirate attacks while making sure Mega Man doesn't fall off the deck, I can certainly stay focused on this game no matter what happens!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I think I've lost enough for now. Somebody else should get to have a turn!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Alright, no more mistakes! Now I've got this whole thing figured out!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Nope, not this time! I'm fully prepared for whatever you have!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Be careful, ~player~. You never know what's going to happen in this kind of game.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I could still win this completely by accident, but I'd need someone else to have the accident.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Sometimes you just have to dive in and hope for the best!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I guess I should be safe this time. What about you, ~player~? Do you think you can make out okay?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm glad we're not playing for zenny. Money is tight enough as it is.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I think I'd rather see everyone naked than be naked. That's normal, right?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Gosh, I haven't had this much excitement in a long time. Not without risking my or Mega Man's life, at least.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright, ~player~. Let's just do our best!</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Maybe I should try being more careful with my cards...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Uh-oh. I think I might have messed up.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh! I better watch out! </state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">I've got a bad feeling about this round...</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Hey! What's the big idea with these cards?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Sorry, I wasn't able to make anything good with the cards I was given.</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">So to~background.time~ might not be my ~background.time~. </state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Wait a minute! How did I mess that up? What happened?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I hope you did well, ~player~. That would at least make one of us.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-6">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I pushed my luck a bit too far on that one. I figured it would be worth the risk at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Losing wouldn't be so bad, right? Hm, maybe I shouldn't give up yet.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Uh-oh. I... uh, think I messed up again.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-8" id="35">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="nickname_prompt" />
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="MegaKuma" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">W-what? Are you making fun of me?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="36">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" stage="3-9" sayingMarker="kumatora_ask_favfoods" />
                <state img="#-excited.png">It's so hard to pick! I really like apricots myself, especially baked into a pie. I bake them all the time to share with gramps and Mega Man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6 8" id="34">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="nickname_prompt" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I don't think there's anything wrong with your name! I don't mind saying it at all!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="favorite_instrument" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png">The only instruments I'm good with are the instruments on my spotter panel. I'm not really musically inclined, unfortunately.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="kum_superpowerA" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I haven't really given that sort of thing too much thought, Kumatora. If there's something Mega Man or I can't do, I usually build something to help us get it done. I'm not sure what I would need a superpower for.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="other" character="kumatora" sayingMarker="kum_superpowerB" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">A superpower? Gosh, I don't know. Maybe something to help keep Mega Man safe? Like I could sense danger for him? My spotting equipment sort of already does that though, so maybe that power would be wasted on me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="37" oneShotId="1" totalRounds="5" priority="0">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="WheresData">By any chance, has anyone seen a little monkey running around? I can't say for sure, but it's possible our robot Data followed me here. He has a weird habit of showing up wherever we go.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="WheresData">This is probably going to sound crazy, but could you guys let me know if you see a monkey? It's possible that it's Data, our... uh, pet, I guess? Sometimes we go somewhere and he's &lt;i&gt;already there&lt;/i&gt;, so I'm worried he followed me here somehow.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="kaz_resp1_1">I think the Flutter is bigger than you're imagining it. We all have our own rooms, plus a kitchen, two bathrooms, and a living room! There's also the engine room and my R&amp;D workshop.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="1">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="roll_caskett0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="revy_resp0_1">Are you using my name as a pun to brag about &lt;i&gt;killing people?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="2">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="roll_caskett0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">Well, what can I say? I've loved working on machines ever since I was little! It's a good thing too because our ship needs a lot of attention.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="jura_resp0_1">Sometimes it's a lot of work, but I do enjoy working on the ship and building new weapons. It's all stuff that has to get done anyway, so I'm just lucky I find it so fun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="3">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="roll_caskett0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">It depends on what I can get my hands on. Most days I'm just doing repairs and maintenance on the ship, but sometimes Mega Man will bring me some scrap to build him some armor or weapons.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="meia_resp0_1">I don't really have the time or resources to work on extra projects. Maintaining the Flutter eats up most of our cash. The only other thing I do regularly is make weapons and armor for Mega Man from the scrap he digs up.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="5">
                <condition role="other" character="mari" sayingMarker="Roll_MegaMan1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="mari_resp0_1">B-b-b-boyfriend?! N-no! No? Of course not! H-he's like my brother! I mean, I love him, but it's totally platonic! There's been some sexually charged moments between us, b-b-b-but we haven't even kissed! Not that I want that! But I don't not want it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="6">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll01" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_1">For me, it's gotta be the Blade Arm attachment I made for Mega Man's armor! It generates a concentrated beam of plasma that can cut through steel like it was tissue paper!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="7">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll11" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_1">Well, I &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; do something like that, but I'm pretty sure you wouldn't want me to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="8">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll31" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Ah... well... um... that sort of stuff is expensive, but I've always got plenty of scrap parts and material around...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-wave.png" marker="maria_resp0_1">Not to brag, but I'm pretty handy in the kitchen too. Cooking, baking, you name it!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="maria_resp1_1">Well, that's his name. It's the one I gave to him, actually.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="maria_resp2_1">Mega Man is the one who goes into the ruins during our dig outs. He assumes a lot of the risk, puts himself in harms way. He does lots for us and me personally.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="maria_resp3_1">Unfortunately, I don't. I did spend a lot of time with Tron while we were building our rocket to rescue Mega Man, but there's just no getting along with her. She's nothing but a huge pain butt!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="maria_resp4_1">I guess I am a little nervous. It's just, you're so beautiful, Maria. Next to you, I-I'm not so sure anyone would care about me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="maria_resp5_1">Winning would be nice, but it wouldn't be the worst thing in the world to lose, right? It might even be fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="kaz_resp0_1">Oh, I was worried people might think these clothes are weird.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_1">Yes, I am. Sorry, that must seem pretty boring to someone who can do magic...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Bobobo_DASH1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_1">Yes, yes, I'm aware my name is also a word. Every time I think I've heard them all, someone comes up with something new and embarrassing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="kaz_resp2_1">Title? No, that's just his name. Mega Man Volnutt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="kaz_resp3_1">Sometimes we find treasure, but anything that isn't actually useful never turns out to be very valuable. Mostly we're just after refractors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="kaz_resp4_1">I'm sure you know the answer to that, Kaz. I wouldn't feel too bad about it; I don't exactly dislike you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_1" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="kaz_resp5_1">I'm not so sure I could do that. I'm perfectly happy with my work now. Being in front of a camera sounds like it would be a little scary.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_1">Do you know who left them behind? A lot of the records we find left behind are pretty cryptic. It was a long time before we really understood anything about who made the ruins.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_1">That's kind of a long story, but the gist of it is he had to go. If he hadn't gone, it might've been the end of life on the planet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_1">The underlying principles of low orbit flight are not so complex that travel to the moon is unfeasible, but when &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; refuses to listen to &lt;i&gt;good sense&lt;/i&gt; and just &lt;i&gt;messes up everything&lt;/i&gt;...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_1">I thought I was going to be a nervous wreck, but I'm having a lot more fun that I thought I would!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_1" />
                <state img="#-lusty.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_1">I'm not so sure. I can't stop think about losing and how good it would feel to touch myself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_HandsDown1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_1">Rock? Rock who? Did you mean Mega Man?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_Chemistry1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_1">Not literally "any two things." That should probably be obvious, but... well, I guess not to someone like you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_WigOutDigOut1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_1">What's a "robot master?"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_BoBonne1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_1">Look, I'm sure I didn't make it easy for her to get along with me, but she's so stubborn and stuck-up I don't know who could get along with her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_PunAndPunishment1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_1">Is that a come on or are you just hungry?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="21">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_ms0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="dwight_resp0_1">Yeah! Absolutely! Did you have a mechanical question?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="dwight_resp0_1">It sounds like you have a mechanical question for me, Dwight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="23">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_ms1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="dwight_resp1_1">So you worked as a mechanic too, huh? I've always worked with machines. Runs in my family! At least, the last few generations.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="dwight_resp1_1">It's always nice to meet a fellow mechanic, even a former one. I've been working with machines my whole life! It's kind of a family tradition!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="24">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_ms2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="dwight_resp2_1">Really? I can sorta imagine you in a denim jumpsuit and all covered in oil. Oil is the universal uniform of &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; mechanics.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="dwight_resp2_1">That's pretty standard for a lot of mechanics, I think. It is pretty easy to imagine you in your little jumpsuit with a wrench in hand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="22">Me? Again? Oh no! How did I let this happen?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="23">Stripping is embarrassing enough on it's own, so why did I have to go and lose like that a second time?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">There's not much I can do if the rest of you are going to be so lucky each time...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3-6" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="28">How? Again? You would tell me if I was doing something wrong, right?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png" oneShotId="29">Apparently I'm the one who needs a spotter in here...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="26">Gosh! You guys are really good at this game!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png" oneShotId="27">It doesn't seem fair for me to lose so many times in a row. I'm not sure how I could have prevented it!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">That's too bad, but I had to get started sometime.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Well, that's okay. It's not like I'm in any danger of losing right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Oh, I'm not worried. I've been in bigger jams before!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Oh, I knew I shouldn't have gotten too overconfident. It's not over until it's over.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-confused.png">And I was so close too! I was just thinking I might not have to take anything else off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Ha ha, well, it would be a lot more embarrassing if I was the only one that was naked.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Oh well, no reason to get bent out of shape. I just gotta keep up!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-wave.png">Don't count me out yet! I can pull through in a jam if I need to!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">If I can land the Flutter when she's only got one engine working, I could still win this even without my pants. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Uh-oh. I'm starting to think I'm going to be one of the big losers here...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">That's not good. I was hoping I had at least one more round before I had to take this off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Oh, this is so embarrassing. At least I won't be the only one...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Darn, I was hoping to hold out just a little longer before I lost. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Am I missing something? I feel like I should be doing a lot better...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Oh, well, that's okay! I can't let it get me down! Maybe my luck will turn around!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I promise I'm not trying to lose on purpose. I just can't seem to string enough wins together.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh, it's embarrassing enough to be playing so poorly. This isn't going to help either.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh no! Really? I was hoping to avoid being the first one completely out of clothes if possible...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp0_2">I do get that sometimes. It's kind of an old-fashioned notion, but I'm a little old-fashioned myself. I don't know, what do you think about it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp1_2">Yup! My grandpa found him and adopted him, but he let me name him. Maybe it is a little strange, but I was just a kid when I picked it out for him.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp2_2">Well, it's his job to clean the toilet. He's pretty good about getting that done.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp3_2">I asked her quite a few times, but she would always get all cagey and not give a straight answer. She's helped Mega Man before even though we're enemies, so there has to be some reason.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp4_2">G-gosh, it's kinda weird to hear you say that. I always thought people just saw me as a greasy mechanic...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="maria_resp5_2">It has been, and I think I'm the one most surprised by that. I thought I might be too nervous to go through with it, but now that I made it this far...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp0_2">Wait, are you saying you like it? You like my work clothes?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_2">Whoa? Really? I thought magic was supposed to just solve all your problems with the snap of your fingers!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_DASH2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_2">Right, my name is a food too. I've heard that one before, but I don't hold it against bread rolls. Personally, I like bread rolls.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp1_2">Oh, is that why you're asking about the Flutter? Trying to invite yourself over? I don't know how I'd explain you to Gramps or Mega Man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp2_2">Usually nobody bats an eye, but for some reason people around here have trouble accepting it. Not sure why that is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp3_2">They're energy resources. Everything and anything that needs power runs off of refractor shards. We pretty much never have cash, but we can buy things with just refractor shards just as reliably.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp4_2">I'm sure you think that, but it's not like Mega Man hasn't seen me naked. Even if those were accidents...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="kaz_resp5_2">Gosh... you certainly have an active imagination...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_2">I bet that's pretty handy. The ruins we go into have pretty much no information like that. Just an army for reaverbots defending them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_2">Thanks, and I'm sorry if it's difficult to talk about. Even now when I think about Mega Man traveling up to the moon without me, I do feel a little sad.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_2">Building and funding the rocket all by myself wasn't going to be possible. I needed help, but the help I got was... not my first choice. We wasted a lot of time and resources because we couldn't stop arguing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_2">When I first met you, you seemed so cool and in control. I couldn't have possibly imagined something like this might make you nervous...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_2">But it's not taboo here. It's expected. Accepted. Celebrated. It's okay to relax and let go, if only just for now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_HandsDown2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_2">As usual, I don't know what you're talking about, Bobobo. I don't know anyone named Rock.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_Chemistry2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_2">I... wouldn't even know where to begin with doing any of that? Some of those things aren't even tangible? I think? Like, what do you mean "the great taste of bran?"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_WigOutDigOut2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_2">Are you just making up words?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_BoBonne2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_2">The only impossibility was us seeing eye to eye, but we managed to do that long enough to succeed. Despite everything, I am grateful for her help...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_PunAndPunishment2" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_2">Uh... Bobobo...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="15">
                <condition role="other" character="revy" sayingMarker="roll_caskett01" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="revy_resp0_2">Their purpose is to protect against reaverbots, aggressive machines. I mean, we do have to fight off pirates every so often, but even then all we do is disable their vehicle...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="16">
                <condition role="other" character="jura" sayingMarker="roll_caskett01" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="jura_resp0_2">I feel that way sometimes too. I even feel bad about destroying the reaverbots who attack us sometimes. The way they move around sometimes you'd swear they're alive.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="jura_resp0_2">Some of the reaverbots we've seen act and move around as if they were living things, so I get it. Even though they're dangerous and attack us, I still feel a little sad about destroying them sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="17">
                <condition role="other" character="meia" sayingMarker="roll_caskett01" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="meia_resp0_2">I like to think I'm a pretty good mechanic, but nothing holds up forever. Especially stuff that's constantly getting shot at or blown up.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="meia_resp0_2">Machines aren't so different from people, after all. Without constant care, even we would fall to pieces. Even a good mechanic can only do so much sometimes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="18">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll02" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_2">You'd have to be careful you don't take off anything important. It is a weapon, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="19">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll12" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_2">Of course it would, but there's the small prerequisite of having to &lt;i&gt;get rid of&lt;/i&gt; your existing limbs.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="20">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll31" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="nagatoro_resp3_2">What are you imagining? It was just a little plastic casing that I put a small motor inside of so it would vibrate.... </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" id="22">
                <condition role="other" character="dwight" sayingMarker="roll_s0" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="dwight_resp0_2">A generator? I've worked on that kind of thing before! Seen all shapes and kinds, really! There were even a few that powered security doors!</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="dwight_resp0_2">Oh, yeah, I've seen that sort of thing before! Worked on my fair share as well! Even a few that powered security doors.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I don't get out of the Flutter, our ship, all that much. It's my house and my workshop as well as how Gramps, Mega Man, and me all get around. I usually don't have much reason to leave.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Normally I stay at home on our airship, the Flutter, with Gramps and Mega Man. I don't have a ton of opportunities to meet new people, so this is a nice change of pace. </state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It's nice to meet some new people like this. I live on an airship, the Flutter, with Gramps and Mega Man. I love them both, and the Flutter has everything I need, but even I get tired of the same routine after a while.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I don't really have a lot of romantic or sexual experience, to be honest. Not a lot of chances for that sort of thing when you're constantly on the move.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">It will be fun getting to know you all here, but I'm hoping I get to know myself a little better too. When you're stuck on an airship most days, you don't get a lot of romantic or sexual experience.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">There's pretty much no opportunity for me to do anything like this back home. Barely a chance for any sort of romantic or sexual experience. Not a lot of privacy either...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I wasn't even sure I'd have to courage to show my breasts, but now that I have I feel... lighter? Unburdened?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Actually, I'm not as nervous as I was before. I feel sort of relaxed, even. Relieved, maybe?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Since I got this far, going just a little further doesn't seem so hard. It feels right, maybe.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I hope I'm not covered in grease. I think I'd die of embarrassment if have to unzip later and my chest had a huge grease smear on it...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I better not be covered in grease. If I take my hat off later and there's a big grease streak across my forehead, just don't tell me. I'll just see it later and die of embarrassment then...</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I'm pretty sure I'm not covered in grease right now, but then again the more sure I am of that the more likely it is. It better not be on my butt or something...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I just wore my normal clothes when I came here, but was that the right choice? I don't really have that many clothes anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">My clothes aren't weird, are they? Honestly, I don't have the money to spend on a lot of clothes in the first place.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I hope it's okay that I'm just wearing my usual clothes. I don't really have any nice clothes or special underwear to begin with.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Gosh, I feel so self-conscious right now. I feel like my heart is going to beat right out of my chest.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">This is so embarrassing, but it's also so exciting. I wasn't even sure I'd have the courage to make it this far.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Alright, then. Here it goes. Are you guys as nervous as I am about all this?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="4" id="28">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll33" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="nagatoro_resp3_3">Well... it's possible that the motor could possibly maybe burn out...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="ringo_ando" sayingMarker="roll_bodysuit" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="ringo_resp2_s">I-it's not that tight. I fill it out a bit better than I did when I first got it years ago, but it's not uncomfortable or anything.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="maria_resp0_3">Huh? I-ignore them? Do you really think it's that bad? Gosh!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="maria_resp1_3">He's not a dog! He's a very important person to me! Please don't say anything mean about him...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="maria_resp2_3">He's good about doing any chore I ask him to do. I rely on him just as much as he relies on me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="maria_resp3_3">What? No! That's ridiculous! Tron and Mega Man? No way! She better keep her grimy little pirate mitts off my ma--- off Mega Man!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="maria_resp4_3">Oh, w-well, it's not like I don't fantasize about... stuff like that sometimes...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="maria" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_3" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="maria_resp5_3">That's an understatement. I don't think I've ever wanted to masturbate so bad...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="kaz_resp0_3">Is... is that a yes? Oh, well... thanks! I'm glad you like whatever it is you like about it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s0_3" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="yshtola_resp0_3">Gosh, I never thought I'd hear that today! Well, maybe I have soldered together a miracle or two in my career.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="9">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_ThereIsNoDASH3" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="bobobo_resp0_3">No, bad Bobobo. No more name puns for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="kaz_resp1_3">Nice try, but you're not about to find out!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="kaz_resp2_3">But that's clearly different! I don't know why anybody would ever call anyone "Caprese Boy." Do... do people actually call you that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="kaz_resp3_3">Well, I don't think they'd be quite so valuable if they were just laying around where anyone could grab them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="kaz_resp4_3">Pfft, you perv. You're a lot more forward than Mega Man. I don't... think I dislike that either...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_3" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="kaz_resp5_3">And what about what you want? I think you should just come right out and say it, that is, if you want to make me horny...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s1_3" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="yshtola_resp1_3">Knowing what we know now, I can say that is exactly the case. It's not like we know everything now, but we'll keep digging and discovering more for sure!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s2_3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="yshtola_resp2_3">How could both be true? Did he turn into a zombie? If my experience with traveling to the moon is anything to go off of, it's more likely that he got blown up. Maybe even more than once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s3_3" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="yshtola_resp3_3">Yeah, &lt;i&gt;eventually&lt;/i&gt;. We got really close when we first started out, but then a bunch of stuff went wrong and the attempt fizzled out. After years of zero progress, it really felt like we were never going to reach him.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s4_3" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="yshtola_resp4_3">I didn't know I had it in me either. Now I'm just nervous about what that might say about me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <condition role="other" character="yshtola" sayingMarker="Roll_s5_3" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="yshtola_resp5_3">And you've got time. I know I'm in no place to judge right now. Gosh, maybe I won't even look at my cards next round...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="10">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_HandsDown3" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="bobobo_resp1_3">If I did know someone named Rock, I guess we could hang out together and be "Rock and Roll."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" id="11">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_Chemistry3" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="bobobo_resp2_3">Yeah, I'm not sure even you know what you're talking about.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4" id="12">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_WigOutDigOut3" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="bobobo_resp3_3">Is it possible you've got me confused with someone else?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" id="13">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_BoBonne3" />
                <state img="#-upset.png" marker="bobobo_resp4_3">Seriously?! I think your brain needs some concussive maintenance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6" id="14">
                <condition role="other" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_PunAndPunishment3" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="bobobo_resp5_3">Just when I was starting to feel &lt;i&gt;less&lt;/i&gt; embarrassed about losing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="25">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll03_male" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_3">Don't worry, ~player~. I'm sure she's only joking.Still, it might be best to keep any heavy weaponry away from her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" id="26">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll03" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="nagatoro_resp0_3">Expert precision? Uhm, the beam saber really isn't calibrated for that sort of thing!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2" id="27">
                <condition role="other" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="roll13" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="nagatoro_resp1_3">If you want to be stronger or faster, there are plenty of other solutions that let you keep your body as it is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I need some excitement every once and a while. Excitement that doesn't involve almost getting killed by reaverbots...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">But I hope nothing bad happens to the Flutter while I'm gone. Gramps is a good mechanic, but he's not as spry as he used to be. Mega Man on the other hand... well, he's better at breaking than fixing things...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">And who knows? Maybe there are some spare parts around here somewhere. Just think what I could build! It would also give me a less embarrassing excuse for where I went off to.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Once I thought I'd end up with Mega Man, but then he was stuck on the moon for all those years. That kind of distance puts a damper on a relationship that never really blossomed...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I mean, I guess there is Mega Man, but even though we're close it's... complicated. He was trapped on the moon for a really long time, so I'm just not sure where we really stand...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">There is Mega Man, but the closest we've come to doing anything is when he walks in on me changing or bathing. Then he was trapped on the moon for a number of years, so I had a lot of time to consider other options...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I try and keep covered up so I don't get stains all over me, but it gets hot in the engine compartment. I unzip a little, I get sweating, I wipe my hands on myself. It just happens!</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">And I'm &lt;i&gt;sure&lt;/i&gt; I don't have grease on my hands because these gloves do a great job of distributing it evenly across every surface I touch, including me. I can't work with greasy hands, so the gloves stay on.</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">I promise it's fresh grease, really! I bathe regularly, but stuff like motor oil and contact grease don't wash off easy. I have to use special soap so I don't always smell like an engine!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I'm only wondering because I found a dirty magazine under Mega Man's bed one time. All the women in there had really sexy lingerie and make-up on. Meanwhile, I'm just standing here in my work clothes...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I found a dirty magazine in Mega Man's room once, and all the women in it were dressed so provocatively. I just keep thinking I'd be more exciting to~background.time~ if I was dressed more like that.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I mean, Mega Man had a dirty magazine and all the women in there were wearing the most brazen outfits. I don't even know where I'd buy something like them, let alone if I've got the courage to wear it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm not a lot to look at, so I hope you don't mind...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Hoo, okay, maybe I'll calm down if I just pretend I'm at home... in my room... and then Mega Man barges in...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Okay... I'm super embarrassed. Let's keep going before I say something dumb...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm even sort of happy losing one more time means I have to masturbate because all this excitement is making me horny...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I wasn't entirely sure about all of this in the beginning, but now I'm all worked up. Horny enough to touch myself, if you can beat me...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I can feel it. My heart's not pounding because I'm scared, but because I'm aroused...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Sorry, ~target~, but I had to beat you. You understand.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You'll just have to do better next time, ~target~. For now, maybe you can treat us to something nice.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Looks like you're having a little trouble, ~target~. Maybe you need somebody to spot for you.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">It's not wrong to be happy about ~target~ losing, right?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Okay, ~target~. It's your turn!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Gosh, this round turned out better than I hoped.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">This seems perfectly fair to me. </state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Hm, maybe some dreams do come true...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I hope we get more than just a peek at him.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">The less imagination I have to use, the better!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I wouldn't mind ~target~'s company down at my level...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">We're way past being coy. Give us a little show, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Okay, that's more like it!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Too bad! I'm not giving up that easily!</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Don't feel too bad, ~target~. I just think it'll be more fun if we share the bad luck around.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">A guy like you wouldn't chicken out now, would he?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I could do with a bit more of ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Let's see a bit more than just that handsome face, okay?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-2">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">~Target~, are you ready? Seems like it's your turn this time.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Sorry I can't watch your back here, ~target~. I've got my own hands full personally.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Don't worry, ~target~. You're in good company here. We're cheering for you!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Of course I want to see a bit more of ~target~. Well, maybe a lot more. You can't blame me for being curious.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Watch out, ~target~. Looks like you might have a little trouble headed your way.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I'm relieved to see it's ~target~ this time, but not just because that means it's not my turn. Really!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">If you could, please consider that I'd really like to see something exciting from you, ~target~. Doesn't that seem fair?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">It was a good day to disembark from the Flutter!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Wow, I was staring at ~target~ that whole time. Did I make that happen?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You've seen this much of me, I'd like to see just as much of you...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">The further along we get in this game, the more exciting it gets. I didn't feel half this thrilled when we first started out.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't forget to lose with a little enthusiasm! Seeing you're having a good time is kind of a turn on...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3-5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't worry, ~target~. You're not out of this quite yet!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">It's really too bad, ~target~. We do all really want to see you keep going though.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">It's only fair, ~target~. I can't have all the bad luck, now can I?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I'm not so easy to beat. Besides, as a digger I've got a sense for when there's treasure to be found.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Gosh, I'm getting pretty excited about seeing a girl strip, but it's ~target~. Anyone would want to get a better view of that body, right?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I know you're more than just a pretty face, ~target~. Let's see what else you've got going for you!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <state img="#-furious.png">Wait, what? Then what was even the point of that round?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It's a bit disappointing to go on a long dig and only come up with a few small refractors...</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" oneShotId="11">We've never found  ~clothing~ while on a dig. Not even down a hole in the wall.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">~clothing.ifPlural(Some|A)~ ~clothing~? That's kind of interesting. Do you think it would fetch a good price at the junk shop?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It's not the sort of thing we might come across on a dig. You wouldn't believe all the things people have thrown away over the centuries, but I guess they kept ~clothing.ifPlural(all their|every last)~ ~clothing~. Though, maybe they didn't have any.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">So ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ your ~clothing~ valuable or something?  </state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You've got quite the valuable little collection there, don't you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-stern.png">Oh, is that all? You're kind of letting me down, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">It's find to take your time and all, but I know I'm past the point of getting excited over something like that.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Just his ~clothing~? Oh, no big deal then.</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">Right, stop everything. This ought to be a game changer...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Oh, not that I think you should sell your ~clothing~. Not unless you need money for spare parts to repair your often failing airship...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Ah, I didn't mean to imply your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ worthless or anything! I've sold my own clothes to get by once or twice, so I know even stuff like that has a price!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="15">Even little things have some value though and a junk shop will buy just about anything! Even a hand vacuum or a box of active proximity mines.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Maybe just hold on to your ~clothing~, ~target~. Wait to sell ~clothing.ifPlural(them|it)~ until you're in a real financial emergency.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">You didn't bring a bunch of little things just to pad out your losses, did you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Come on, ~target~. Now's the time to be impressing me...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I just want you to be honest with yourself and go a little faster. I mean, I'm already like this...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">If you don't pick up the pace, we might just leave you behind, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Please, don't be shy. I want to see as much of you as you've seen of me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if Mega Man would buy me something like your ~clothing~. What would it even mean for a guy to do that?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Is there some story behind your ~clothing~? Did someone buy it for you?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I don't think your ~clothing~ is my style, exactly. Suits you just fine though. </state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I don't really wear a lot of jewelry of accessories. I wouldn't want to wear something that might get caught in the Flutter's machinery while I'm working on her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Maybe if I had a lot of extraneous stuff, I wouldn't be in this jam.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You're not afraid of losing are you, ~target~? Seems like you might be stalling a bit.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">I think you're doing well enough that you could risk taking some bigger strides right about now.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">It's not a competition to see who has the most stuff, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-8" id="33">
                <condition role="target" character="ms.fortune" stage="3" sayingMarker="Fortune_Strip_2C" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh no! Y-your head! H-hold on! I'll go get my rivet gun!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Sometimes Mega Man just finds little trinkets when he's out and about. He says they remind him of me and lets me keep them. I'm nearly out of space in my room due to his generosity.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Well, Mega Man does have a habit of giving me things he picks up, but it's not uncommon for him to go through trash cans. I just make sure to wash whatever he gives me first...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It's not like I have the money to spend on anything extra for myself. If I have spare zenny, it goes right into the Rainy Day Fund!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Tell me, ~target~, do nice little things like that make you happy? The stuff alone doesn't interest me, but if I get it as a gift from someone I care about it becomes important to me. Is it like that for you too?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Come one now ! Let's really get into the spirit of it!</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I've got a feeling this might not work out like you're hoping it will...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">If my selfish request counts for anything, I'd love for you to show me something far more intimate...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">You can do it, ~target~! The hardest part is taking it all off! It's easy to just be naked once you get that far!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Is this what you usually wear, ~target~? If you were going to go on a dig, you'd need a lot more protection than that.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">If ~target~ were going on a dig dressed how he showed up, he'd be in real trouble.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Your clothing seems pretty comfortable, ~target~, but not very practical. You could use a few upgrades.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't think what you're wearing is very practical for digging. It needs a lot more... well, a lot.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Such a tease, ~target~. Can't you step it up a bit?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">~Target~ is making me feel like I'm not very good at this game, but I can live with that.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Feeling a bit shy still, ~target~? I don't see why you have to be.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Come one, ~target~! I think you need to start pulling a bit more weight around here!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-excited.png">You probably get tired walking and running everywhere. With a good set of wheels and an engine, I can make you some jet shoes to let you zip around faster than a car!</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">You would definitely need a helmet. That's a must. You'll thank me later when a reaverbot drops on top of you from the ceiling.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">First thing is first! You need some armor! Thick, metal, reinforced body armor. Form fitting too! Can't have you getting hurt in a little explosion!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">You definitely need something to defend yourself with! How do you feel about grenades?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I do think it's an improvement, even if it's just a small one. I can think of a few more places that still need work though.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I get the feeling you're building up to something big! I guess I'll just have to wait.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Okay, now you just need to keep losing! Come one, it'll be fun! I promise!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I can respect playing smart, but don't keep us waiting in suspense for too long!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">I don't know a lot about clothing, but I do know a lot about machines. They're kind of similar, wouldn't you say? </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Fashion is not my strong suit. I don't like wearing fancy clothes because I worry too much about getting them dirty. I just get clothes that are durable.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">You've got such an interesting sense of style, ~target~. My style has always been focused on practicality, to be honest.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I don't really keep up with fashion at all, but are your clothes more about form or function, ~target~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">There should be a little more than that you can show us? You should be able to see that clearly.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You're not feeling shy, ~target~, are you? Not after I've cleared the way for you.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I've come all this way and ~target~ is still taking her time. I hope you're not getting cold feet, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">If you're worried about being immodest, I think we're far past that point now.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">If you're looking for something really practical for your wardrobe, how about an arm mounted buster cannon? It fits comfortably over the entire length of your forearm!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">In a way, I'm actually something of a clothes designer myself! I make and upgrade all of Mega Man's digger armor parts! People seem to think he's very cool looking, so maybe I do have some skills in fashion!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It's like I always tell Mega Man: you're never fully dressed without your reinforced custom-fit body armor!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">So I'm not expert, but I'm sure there's no reason you couldn't upgrade your outfit! How about some spring-loaded armored boots? They'll come in real handy if you fall down an elevator shaft and need to escape!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Well, you need to go at your own pace. I don't have any problem respecting that.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I know it seems tough, but it gets easier as you go along. At least, it did for me. I just focused on having a good time!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I don't want to rush you, It's perfectly fine to take the time you need. The anticipation makes things kind of exciting too.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">If you need to just take your time, that's alright with me. Though, I do reserve the right to tease you maybe a tiny bit about it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Seems like you might be in trouble here, ~target~. Do you think you can continue?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Don't worry, ~target~! It's okay! We're cheering you on even if things aren't looking good for you!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Are you really running out of options, ~target~? Seems like you might be in trouble here.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright, ~target~! Don't give up yet! Not when it's about to get exciting!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Got a little something you wanted to show us all, ~target~? </state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">At least we didn't need to break out the drill to get ~clothing.ifPlural(these|that)~ off of ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Say goodbye to your stubborn ~clothing~, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Don't worry! You won't need your ~clothing~ to protect you anymore.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You know, it's times like these you need a good spotter watching your back. If you need someone to do that, I could be your girl...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I do admire a guy who is cool under pressure. Could be fun to see how you do a little later...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't go anywhere yet, ~target~. I don't think I'm done with you by a long shot...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">This is more fun than I was expecting. I think there's a bit more fun to be had with ~target~ as well...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Hm, I wouldn't mind walking in on ~target~ while he's changing...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Oh, we're not done with you yet, ~target~. You know that, right?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Don't turn back now, ~target~. We're finally getting somewhere.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You feel it too, right, ~target~? Maybe you need to lose a little bit more...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Getting down to the nitty-gritty now, huh, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Pretty exciting, isn't it, ~target~? I hope you're still having fun too.</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Go ahead and make yourself comfortable, ~target~. We won't judge.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You might want to stop losing, ~target~. Just something I thought you might want to consider unless you want to lose all your undergarments too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Now it's ~target~'s turn to show us some real excitement.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It's not so bad without your clothes, ~target~. I think it's growing on me a little.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">So? Don't keep us waiting any longer...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Seems like our patience is paying off. Sorry, ~target~. I know you worked hard not to get to this point.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">I sort of wish I had some sexier underwear. No idea how I could budget it though.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">W-wow, ~target~ looks pretty cute like that...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I know Mega Man would like this, if the magazines under his bed are any indicator...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">You've got such a great body, ~target~. There's no way you're nervous about playing a game like this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">I think I prefer ~target~ this way instead...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Any digger worth her salt knows the best treasures are buried as deep as you can go...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Oh, yes. This was well worth the waiting...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Do you promise it'll get even better from here on out?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Not feeling so shy now, are we?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Is it really so bad to lose your ~clothing~, ~target~? Don't guys go around in public without shirts all the time?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">You don't really need your ~clothing~ anyway. I think you'll be a lot more comfortable without it.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">A tragic loss for ~target~, but for the rest of us...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You've been holding out on us, ~target~. </state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Personally, I think this is way overdue.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">It's about time, ~target~. No more teasing us...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Glad we were fortunate enough to get you down this far...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Maybe we can just take an extra moment to appreciate this before the next round?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Gosh, now I feel all embarrassed...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I just want to say I'm glad you decided to join us to~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">So, you must be pretty popular back home, ~target~? I don't see why not.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">See, nothing to be nervous about. Now we appreciate that handsome frame of yours...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">So... nothing but the air between us separating our bodies...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Well, now we're both pretty exposed. I wonder if we have anything else in common...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I hardly even need to imagine anymore...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Sorry, but this just a little awkward...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Oh? If your ~clothing~ is coming off, that means...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I guess this was bound to happen. I kinda thought I had more time to prepare.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">No reason to panic, right? This is exactly what we were all expecting to happen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">I've been dying to see you like this, ~target~. You won't blame me for being curious, right?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Hm, I wanna see what sort of face ~target~'s going to make when it's out...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">C'mon, fair is fair, ~target~. Let's see it.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Sorry, ~target~! I think you're being very brave, and I admire that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Not what I was imagining, but now I'm more curious about it...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Well, I think you're pretty cute, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Oh? It's different than I thought. I sort of... want to see it in action.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">So, this is what you're like? I think it actually suits you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">It only takes a spark to ignite a flame...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">So... are you a gentle lover?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">As an engineer, I'd love for you to demonstrate its functionality...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">You don't need a big gun to impress me, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Confident, aren't we?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I know this is a point of pride for guys, but I gotta say it just looks like any other penis to me.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Sorry, I was staring a bit. My curiosity isn't entirely satisfied...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Is this part fun for guys? What're you thinking, ~target~? It doesn't look like you want to run and hide.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Oh, don't worry, ~target~. I'm a mechanic. I know my way around a gun...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Standing here like this and looking at your penis is... it's making my heart pound...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Well, I could stand to see how you use it...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Gosh, now it's like we're about to... </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Right, so you haven't been nervous at all this whole time, have you?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Men and their obsession with huge guns...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Knowing how guys are, I'm surprised you aren't more confident about this game.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Ah, so we're bringing out the big guns then...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">That is not what I was imagining at all. That's... all I'm going to say about it.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Well, there is a certain satisfaction to holding a weapon with some heft to it...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Oh, boys and their toys...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">From a mechanical standpoint, I should stress the importance of lubrication...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">In all of Mega Man's magazines, the women's breasts are always covered by lingerie or their hands. It's actually sort of disappointing...</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Go for it, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Honestly, I just didn't want to be the first one to have my breasts out. Even now, I'm still totally nervous! I'm sure you'll be fine, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">My luck hasn't been so great, ~target~, so there's a chance you'll have me for company before too long.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Go ahead and join the club!</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">At least you won't be alone...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I already had my turn to show mine, ~target~. C'mon, now its your turn!</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">The more the merrier, at least that's what I hope!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-wave.png">I think you've got a great body, ~target~! I'm almost jealous!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I don't think there's anything wrong with having smaller breasts. I think they're very cute!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Maybe it's self-serving to say, but I think girls with bodies like you are really cute, ~target~! Really!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">With or without your ~clothing~, you look great! Gosh, I might even be a little jealous.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I think we're just the right size to be held, ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Can I compliment ~target~ without sounding too self-aggrandizing? I can't just not tell her she's sexy, right?</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Tell me, ~target~: don't you think having bigger breasts would be a pain? Isn't it nice to just be like this?</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png">Are there really people who don't like bodies like yours, ~target~? I guess there's no accounting for taste...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Gosh, ~target~ is so pretty and has a great body. Just lucky, I guess.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">No secret where some of that confidence is coming from...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Of course I think girls like ~target~ are cute too! Who doesn't?</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Are all the girls where you're from this attractive, or are you just super-popular or something?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I could already tell you might be a bit bigger than me, even through your ~clothing~.  I don't think we both needed to have them out to compare.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">My goodness, you're even sexier like this... not that I'm surprised...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Seeing another girl like this is at lot more exciting than I thought it would be...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">See, now we're together in the same boat. What do you think? Not so bad?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">T-they're even bigger than I thought they were!</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">H-how could they grow &lt;i&gt;that&lt;/i&gt; big?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I mean, I knew they were going to be big... but now that they're out it's like... wow...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">At the end of the day, I'm not sure I would like having a body like ~target~'s. It's pretty cramped down in the Flutter's engine compartment as-is.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">So, a questions suddenly springs to mind: do you have any trouble going up and down ladders?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">This is why I probably couldn't pull off ~target~'s style...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <state img="#-worried.png">And now the difference between us is plain as it could be...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Yeah, I don't think I'd look good with a bust like yours, ~target~. That's clearly more your style...</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">Okay, okay, the difference was obvious beforehand. There's no reason to go comparing now...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">It takes all kinds, I guess. I'm still happy just the way I am.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Well, aside from my own, this is certainly not something I see on a regular basis.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Boy, your luck has &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; not been that good to~background.time~, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You'll be just fine, ~target~. I promise we're not going to say anything mean about you. </state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">What's that look for, ~target~? Are you having second thoughts about going through with it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I hate to say it, but you sort of get used to it after a little while.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Come on, don't be shy! It's not like you're going to be the only one with their butt out at this point.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I hope this part isn't too stressful for you, ~target~. I know it was pretty nerve-racking for me.</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">I know this part is pretty embarrassing, but I'm behind you all the way! It's no big deal if you want to change your mind now!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8" id="4">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh! Oh my! I had no idea. I have... so many questions!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">It's not like you've got anything unusual going on down there. Nothing to be a ashamed of!</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">If I end up where you are, I hope I can be as brave as you are. I'm not used to this sort of thing.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">See, I knew you could do it! I know it's embarrassing, but I hope you're still having fun!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Alright, that's the spirit! You don't have to give up yet if you want to keep going!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Alright then... here we both are. Gosh, why am I getting so embarrassed all of a sudden?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">See, now we're both in big trouble! It's a bit better with you though.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">You know, I don't really see a lot of other women naked. This is all pretty novel for me.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I am going to have one heck of a diary entry to write tonight, that's for sure...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="dorothy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Dorothy_s0_1">Wow, a robot. She's so life-like! I wonder who built her...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Samus_s0_1">She's got battle armor just like Mega Man, but I've never seen a design like this. It looks so... alien?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="9S_s0_1">Is he really a machine? He looks so life-like. He's not one of those androids built for The System, is he?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Caitlin_s0_1">Gosh, I hardly have enough time to brush my own hair in the morning. If I had hair like that I'd never get anything done.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="beatrix" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Beatrix_s0_1">That red eye! And that weapon! T-there's no way she's a reaverbot... right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_1">I've never met anyone like you, Y'shtola. It's a bit much to take in, that you can do magic and you have those ears and that tail...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Bobobo_s0_s1">You're not going to do anything strange, are you Bobobo? It won't be any fun if someone isn't playing by the rules.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Meia_s0_s1">I've never built a large mech before. I've always wanted to, but the parts alone would cost a fortune. And finding a refractor to power it, well, I'd just have to hope I'd be lucky enough to find one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Kaz_s0_1">The way you're dressed, Kaz, makes me feel like I should have worn something nicer. Your clothes don't even have wrinkles!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="fina" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Fina_s0_1">Fina! You live on an airship too, is that right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_s1">I still can't believe you destroyed all your clothes, Bobobo. Even your shoes and socks! How are you going to get home?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_s1">You really backed yourself into a corner, Bobobo. Maybe you need a spotter when you play this game, to warn you before you get yourself in so much trouble.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_s1">I don't think this is very funny, Bobobo. It kind of seems like you're cheating!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_s1">How am I even supposed to prepare for whatever strange thing you're going to do next? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_s1">Was Don Patch here the whole time just waiting for you to lose?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_1">You're out fighting a lot, right, Y'shtola? What sort of equipment do you usually wear for that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_1">I still think you should wear more protective clothing, Y'shtola. It would be much safer that way!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_1">Say, Y'shtola, do your companions every get distracted? Not like in the heat of combat, but in between missions?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_1">How reliable is magic in a fight? Don't you think it would be better to just bring an auto-fire cannon or a rocket launcher?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_1">Gosh, Y'shtola, you're not nervous about losing, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_1">I know it's embarrassing to be seen naked, but at least you're showing us on purpose, right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_1">You know, it might be easier to relax if you weren't working so hard to prevent us from seeing your crotch.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Maria_s0_1">Do you really live next to a river, Maria? That sounds so relaxing to be living out in nature like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Maria_s1_1">Living like you do, you must have some good money-saving tips, Maria.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Maria_s2_1">Can I ask you for advice, Maria? I don't mean to be rude, but you seem a lot more experienced than me with stuff like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="Maria_s3_1">I wonder how Mega Man would react if he saw me working in the kitchen with nothing but an apron on...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Maria_s4_1">I wish I had the sort of confidence you do, Maria. Beyond things even like this, I just get scared when I see a reaverbot on the monitor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Kaz_s1_1">So your butler, Charles, he wears his armor around all the time? That's what makes him a "mecha butler?"</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="Kaz_s2_1">So, do you have a whole arsenal of demon slaying outfits as well? Ever show up to a job late because you couldn't decide which to wear?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Kaz_s3_1">How does a person become a number on bachelor anyway? That sort of seems like it's super subjective.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Kaz_s4_1">Now that you're nearly naked, I think we can start asking the really embarrassing questions. How about you tell us what happened to your last girlfriend?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png" marker="Kaz_s5_1">So, do you think your next girlfriend might be around here? Met anyone &lt;i&gt;special?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="nagatoro" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">So, you and ~player~ are... friends? Is that right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kumatora" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Kumatora_s0_1">All this business about casting magic is so weird to me. Is it really &lt;i&gt;magic&lt;/i&gt; or is there some sort of trick to it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="2" />
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You probably should've been more careful than that since you lost the last round.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Careful, ~target~, you don't want to end up in a rut!</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Okay, so maybe your luck will turn around in the &lt;i&gt;next&lt;/i&gt; next round?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Don't tell me you're losing your nerve, ~target~! You can't let these losses pile up!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Another loss, ~target~? Maybe you should be paying a little closer attention to what's going on.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">It's only two losses, ~target~! Try not to let it get you down!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" consecutiveLosses="3-" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Are you sure you know what you're doing, ~target~? It seems like you'd need more than bad luck to struggle so much...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It sort of seems like you're losing on purpose, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Come on, ~target~, don't let the inertia of your losses drag you all the way down!</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">You're really letting those losses pile up, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I'm convinced there's something more than just bad luck at play here.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">If you want to lose, you're doing a pretty impressive job of it. From a purely statistical standpoint, losing this many times in a row is fairly unlikely.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_caskett_resp0" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Meia_s0_s2">But you do have them, right? Can't you just take them apart, see how they work? That's how I learned how to build vacuum cleaners and grenade launchers.</state>
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Meia_s0_s2">If you have them, how do you not know how to build one? Just take it apart and figure it out. Believe me, it works for car engines, vacuum cleaners, grenade launchers...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" saidMarker="Roll_WheelsOnDa1" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_2">Aren't you worried people will see you? You can't just walk home without any pants!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" saidMarker="Roll_Technology1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_2">You can't possibly mean you planned for this? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" saidMarker="Roll_SpiritoftheLaw1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_2">I guess so... but it seems sort of dishonest to wear two pairs like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" saidMarker="Roll_DonPatchMan1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_2">The only thing I'm expecting at this point is that I'm going to be taken completely by surprise!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" saidMarker="Roll_StrikeOut1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_2">Ah! Don Patch!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_2">Gosh, I don't even know where to begin. I don't think we even have time for every question I have.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_2">Wait, that's it? You don't wear any armor? Y'shtola! That seems incredibly dangerous!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_2">Hmm... well, I guess that's like how Mega Man and I operate. He goes into the ruins to explore and fight while I offer support from back on the Flutter.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-scolding.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_2">Mega Man gets up to the strangest things sometimes. I was worried sick about the upcoming ruins this one time, but then I turned on the TV and there Mega Man was playing in some stupid game show!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_2">But wouldn't it be good to have a backup? You could cast spells with one hand and fire a machine gun with the other! Or maybe a grenade launcher!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp5_1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_2">But you're so beautiful and confident! Gosh, if I looked like you I wouldn't have to worry at all what people thought about me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" saidMarker="roll_resp6_1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_2">What? You too? How did that happen?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" saidMarker="roll_resp7_1" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_2">And now are you going to block your boobs too? You don't think it'd just be easier to put your arms down and just let it all hang out?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Maria_s0_2">Oh? I thought you lived on a farm? Do you just work on the farm but live in an apartment in the city?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="0" saidMarker="roll_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Kaz_s0_2">So your appearance must be really important to you, huh? I bet you've got a whole wardrobe full of fashionable clothes!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-worried.png" marker="Maria_s2_2">It's a little naive, but I'm not sure how to tell if someone is interested in me romantically. I don't get away from the Flutter a whole lot, so I don't have any experience with these things.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Maria_s3_2">I guess I wouldn't &lt;i&gt;hate&lt;/i&gt; that. It'd be nice to turn the tables on him for once.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Maria_s4_2">Ha, maybe I should just stick to my strengths, but thanks! Gosh, you're so nice, Maria!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Maria_s1_2">W-what? You don't use it "personally?" </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp1_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Kaz_s1_2">Wait, who's Sadie?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp2_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Kaz_s2_2">You just go in what you're wearing? Even if it's normal clothes? Don't you need your equipment or protection?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp3_1" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Kaz_s3_2">If you're so popular and everyone knows you're single, why are you still a bachelor? It all sounds a little counter-intuitive.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp4_1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png" marker="Kaz_s4_2">Sounds like you didn't want to break up with her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp5_1" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Kaz_s5_2">So even if you met someone really special, you wouldn't do it? Even if she was some perfect super girl?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="29">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="3" sayingMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wha---what?! S-Sakura? Your head is---</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh! Oh no!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">He left his necklace totally intact though. I wonder if it's special to him somehow...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Uh-oh. I've got a bad feeling about this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh, come on! Don't tell me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">H-hold on! What are you doing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Is that any way to treat your friend, Bobobo?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="samus_aran" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Samus_s0_2">I'd love to get your impression on it and maybe take a look at how it's put together! I'm always in the market for ideas to build better armor! After all, it's a spotter's job to make sure her digger stays safe!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="31">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wah! S-Saki? What the---?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Oh, so you are going to take your ~clothing~ off. I sort of thought you would have done that before you... you know.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">So, did you just forget you were wearing ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ until now?</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Well, if you don't want to lose I guess you have to take ~clothing.ifPlural(those|that)~ off.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">You do have your priorities straight right, ~target~? It seems like you might be just a little mixed up...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="armor" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Good armor is hard to come by, huh? I try to keep Mega Man in armor that won't get him killed when he's out on digs.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Who makes your armor, ~target~? Does it work well for you? Are you able to move around comfortably? Do you have a coolant system in there?</state>
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Diggers need sturdy armor to do their jobs. Something that will stand up to the weapons reaverbots use. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" saidMarker="Roll_WheelsOnDa2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s1_3">What's obvious about that?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" saidMarker="Roll_Technology2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Bobobo_s2_3">What kind of half-baked plan is this?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" saidMarker="Roll_SpiritoftheLaw2" />
                <state img="#-furious.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_3">Having &lt;i&gt;three&lt;/i&gt; doesn't make it any better!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" saidMarker="Roll_DonPatchMan2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s4_3">Okay, now this has to be actually cheating, Bobobo.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" saidMarker="Roll_StrikeOut2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Bobobo_s5_3">I thought Don Patch was your friend! Why would you do that to him?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Yshtola_s0_3">I mean, it definitely seems like the ears are attached to your head. I'm sure at some point I'll get to see where your tail attaches too.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-stern.png" marker="Yshtola_s1_3">It seems wrong to me. Without armor, even a grazing blow could really hurt you! And that dress! Don't you ever step on it while trying to move quickly?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Yshtola_s2_3">But I do! I'm inside the Flutter! It's far safer than just standing around in the open, even if I'm not actually down in the ruins myself!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Yshtola_s3_3">One time Mega Man helped a bunch of Servbots open up a burger restaurant. He just can't turn down anyone who asks him for help...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Yshtola_s4_3">There's all kinds of options out there! Maybe a giant drill bit or some proximity mines or a laser cannon or a beam sword...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="6" saidMarker="roll_resp5_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Yshtola_s5_3">Kinda seems like you're even more nervous than me! I knew you must be brave, but I guess I underestimated just how much!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="7" saidMarker="roll_resp6_2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png" marker="Yshtola_s6_3">That's funny. I was never in any danger, but it's happened to me twice as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="yshtola" stage="8" saidMarker="roll_resp7_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Yshtola_s7_3">You don't exactly &lt;i&gt;look&lt;/i&gt; relaxed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Kaz_s0_3">Hm, other than my pajamas and my winter clothes, I just own a bunch of this outfit.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-excited.png" marker="Maria_s1_3">That sounds lovely! I guess it would be a little hard for an entire society to work like that, but I'm glad your community is so supportive and hardworking!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Maria_s2_3">S-so you're an advocate of the direct approach? I mean, I guess that sort of seems obvious now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="Maria_s3_3">I kind of like the way you're thinking right now, Maria.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Maria_s4_3">Or maybe I should say you're &lt;i&gt;mostly&lt;/i&gt; nice.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="maria" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_resp0_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Maria_s0_3">That sort of sounds like it would go against some kind of zoning law?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="2" saidMarker="roll_resp1_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Kaz_s1_3">Are you saying you didn't know she was in there?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="3" saidMarker="roll_resp2_2" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png" marker="Kaz_s2_3">Aren't demons dangerous? Shouldn't you take the necessary precautions?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="4" saidMarker="roll_resp3_2" />
                <state img="#-smirking.png" marker="Kaz_s3_3">Okay, so you're a bit of a romantic? That's not "complicated," Kaz. I think that's pretty normal.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="5" saidMarker="roll_resp4_2" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png" marker="Kaz_s4_3">Okay, that wasn't embarrassing. That was just... depressing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="6" saidMarker="roll_resp5_2" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png" marker="Kaz_s5_3">You're not quite as smooth as you think you are since you've got your underwear off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition role="target" character="meia" stage="1" saidMarker="roll_caskett_resp01" />
                <state img="#-smiling.png" marker="Meia_s0_3">If they're not useful, that's even more reason to take them apart! You can never have too many spare parts, especially if you've got other machines to take care of.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="Meia_s0_3">Taking them apart still makes sense even if they're not useful to you. I'm sure the parts and the scrap metal could still be useful. It'll be extra material for your other vessels.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="30">
                <condition role="target" character="sakura" stage="4" saidMarker="headless" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Does that happen a lot? Do... do you need me to bolt your head to your neck?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">His nosehairs really just went everywhere! It was incredible! And... and terrifying? And a little gross?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-confused.png">Oh, well, I guess not? He doesn't really seem like the sentimental type.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Wait! Was this your plan all along? Why? Why do it like this?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-upset.png">Exactly how long is this going to go on for? !</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-furious.png">At least you were &lt;i&gt;wearing&lt;/i&gt; all that underwear! Th-this has to be cheating!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" stage="6" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">With everything that was going on... I hardly noticed how rugged his body is. ..</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8" id="32">
                <condition role="target" character="saki_zls" stage="7" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Does that happen a lot? It must be rough being undead. Maybe you need a collar riveted to your neck to keep your head on...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_GetEquipped3" />
                <state img="#-furious.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_1a">Who are you talking to?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition role="target" character="bobobo" sayingMarker="Roll_GetEquipped3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="Bobobo_s3_1b">W-what? You're copying me?!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="exhibitionist" status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I guess I shouldn't be surprised. ~Target~ does seem like ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ wants to be seen...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">~Target~ doesn't seem to mind being naked though, so I guess I should have seen this coming.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition status="exposed" role="target" />
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="extra" />
                </alternative>
                <alternative>
                    <test expr="~clothing.type~" value="minor" />
                </alternative>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Well, whatever floats your boat! No reason you can't keep stripping until you're all out of clothes!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">I can respect that you're not ready to lose. I guess the point is to win after all!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Seems like maybe you're just showing off, ~target~!</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Whatever the case is, you shouldn't be so certain it's going to save you here!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="armor" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Maybe your armor could use some modifications? Stabilizers to keep you from falling over during combat? A data chip to keep you from lighting on fire?</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">Junk shops always have the best stuff laying around for armor parts. It can be a little pricey, but it's hard to put a price on staying alive.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Say, what kind of threat are you up against that you need armor for? Seems like it's pretty safe around here. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I guess when they built you, they had this sort of thing in mind. Does... does it work?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I've never considering building a robot with a working... I mean, surely you weren't built just for this purpose, right?</state>
                <state img="#-surprise.png">I guess you would want to build an android as close to a human as possible, but to go this far? It just seems like your creator had ulterior motives.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-8">
                <condition filter="robot" role="target" />
                <state img="#-nervous.png">It actually wouldn't be very hard to build a robot with functioning genitalia, but there aren't a whole lot of reasons to do so aside from the... let's say "obvious" ones...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Whoever made you decided you should be this attractive and have working genitalia, so... yeah... there's really only one conclusion I can draw from that.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="no_genitals" role="target" />
                <state img="#-curious.png">What the...</state>
                <state img="#-upset.png">Is this seriously happening?</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">I can't believe we're watching this...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="tandem" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm embarrassed just watching them, but they don't seem bothered at all to be seen like this.</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Must be nice to have someone you feel so comfortable with...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" oneShotId="4">I knew people would be masturbating, but this is more than I was anticipating!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Even watching them is almost too stimulating...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <condition filter="tandem" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Seeing them... I feel a little lonely...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I wish I had someone to help me out too...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="10">Watching them makes me fee like I could do something like that too... but no? Right? No way!</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">They're both so... ah, I wish that I could...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-8">
                <condition filter="joke_forfeit" role="target" />
                <state img="#-stern.png">I just... I have no idea how I'm supposed to feel about what just happened.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">If you wanted to back out now, ~target~, I wouldn't blame you...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Looks like this is the end of the line for you, ~target~. Nice try though!</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Boy, am I glad I'm not in your shoes. I've had run-ins with reaverbots less thrilling than all this.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I don't know who came up with these rules, but it is a pretty exciting way to end this off...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-excited.png">Okay, ~target~, I'll try not to stare too much, but only when you're not looking...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">For all your stubbornness, you still lost it all. At least you tried.</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I might be a little too excited to see this play out...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Now you've really got to show us something big, if you wouldn't mind.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, do I, uh, watch or look away or what? I don't want to be rude...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I probably shouldn't watch too much, should I?</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Hm, feels pretty good to win! I just hope ~target~ ends up feeling good too.</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">You know, I wonder if Mega Man has ever done this while I was on the Flutter with him? I never really thought about it...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Did I already say I was curious to see how you used it? I'm so giddy I can't really remember.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">If you want to peek at me at all, I wouldn't mind too much...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">We'll be here still, but you're on your own, ~target~. Maybe pretend we're not here.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">What else can I say? Do your best, ~target~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">~Target~ seems like he's really making an effort...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I can barely focus for two seconds before I look over at ~target~ again...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Now it really feels like I'm seeing something I was not meant to see...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">... Am I staring too much? It doesn't seem to be bothering you... I think...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I probably shouldn't ask what ~target~ has on his mind...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Am I imagining ~target~ looking over here, or... </state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">~Target~ is... he really is... gosh...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I this how all guys do it? Does Mega Man also...?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I might end up thinking about this later...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6 8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I can't help but look over at where ~target~ is... </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">So, exactly how long do you plan on going for?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Seeing ~target~ turned on is... stimulating...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">This is a lot more than I could have hoped for from  ~target~...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Is that how you like it, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">My heart is pounding about a mile a minute right now...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">This is so strange, but I don't think it's so bad...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">~Target~ doesn't seem bothered at all that he's not alone.</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Is it always so exciting?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Is ~target~ going to... look this way?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Each stroke... would be a thrust in...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I've been watching ~target~ so closely... I think I synced up...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">So much more exciting than just being alone... imagining...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Seeing you aroused, arouses me. Do I do the same for you, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">If I gave him the chance... would ~target~ feel me instead?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">G-gosh... w-wow... he really... he really came in front of us...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Does anybody else feel a sort of... tingling?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Obviously, ~target~ had a lot of fun here... obviously.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">And just like that, the excitement is over, huh?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You held out as long as you could, huh? I admire that, really...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Hm, he's cute when he's satisfied...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">It seems like you enjoyed yourself, but not as much as I am...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Ha ha... so cute...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-giggling.png">~Target~ got unlucky just one too many times. Good news for the rest of us.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Maybe it's just bad luck, ~target~, but it might be that poker just isn't your game.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Gosh, that's too bad for you, ~target~. I hope you don't feel too bad about losing.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">That's okay, ~target~. No hard feelings, right? You played a good game!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-curious.png">So, ~target~ lost? That means she'll...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">~Target~'s luck ran out, huh? I sort of feel bad for her.</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">If ~target~ lost now, then I guess that means she's completely out of the game...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">That's too bad, ~target~. I was sort of rooting for you a little...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-flattered.png">This is... unusual for you, right? If I was in your shoes, I'd normally double check to make sure the door is locked...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, I don't want to stare too much, b-but I'm really curious...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I don't usually think too much about other girls masturbating. This whole game is a bit of a novel experience for me.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm a bit more excited about this than I thought I would be. ~Target~'s so beautiful though... so...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Just when I thought it couldn't get more exciting...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Wow, I never really... I just... sorry, I got a chill down my spine just now.</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">Okay... I'd love to see... just a bit of this...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Sorry if I stare a bit, ~target~. It's just that I want to see how you treat yourself...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="5-6 8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">~Target~ is so beautiful and seeing her like this is... really hot...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Don't stop now, ~target~. I'd like to see a little more...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">~Target~ really isn't holding back, is she? Must feel nice...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I never imagined I'd see ~target~ make a face like that...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Why don't you show us how you like it, ~target~?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Gosh, I'm shaking so much from excitement it's embarrassing...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I never thought watching ~target~ would be so thrilling...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">~Target~ is able to lose herself, even in front of us...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">I knew this would be exciting, but this is a lot more than I thought.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Are you watching me at all, ~target~? </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Look at us, ~target~. Did you ever imagine?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">If I touch myself like ~target~ touches herself... it's almost like...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">With another girl here... it's so much more stimulating...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I'm enjoying watching you, ~target~. Does watching me... do anything for you?</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">It might be better... if I let ~target~ do it for me...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Am I like that when I touch myself? </state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">Whenever ~target~ makes a noise, I can't help but picture myself... ahem, where were we again?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">~Target~ is showing us something really special. That's quite the treasure...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Even like this... she's beautiful...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">You know, looking at ~target~... I'm starting to feel like maybe losing wouldn't be so bad?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Did ~target~ just look at me or did I imagine that? </state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">Just the look on ~target~'s face is... is so... wow...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">If I don't lose... I might have to hurry home and just... take care of myself anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I'm going to see this in my head later, aren't I?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-5">
                <state img="#-curious.png">That looked like... it felt really good...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Do I make a face like that when I climax? That was so... sexy...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Do you need a minute, ~target~? You look like you might still be riding the wave.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">Take your time and enjoy it, ~target~. You might not feel so euphoric when you come back down.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-8">
                <state img="#-nervous.png">The excited pit in my stomach just got a whole lot heavier.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">That might be worthy of applause...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">When I met  ~target~, I did not imagine I'd be seeing her make that face.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">You're really sexy, ~target~, but I feel like you have to know that by now...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Oh, oh no! Oh, I was hoping I wouldn't have to go first. Oh well, g-guess that's just my luck.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-surprise.png">Oh no! I lost? Guess I should have been more careful, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-stern.png">Fine, I can see that I'm beat. I tried my best, but luck just wasn't on my side to~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-scolding.png">Oh, alright. You won fair and square. No reason to make a big fuss about it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-lost.png">Well, I may as well make the best of it, right? I am feeling like I could...</state>
                <state img="#-lost.png">I can do this. It's embarrassing, but it's not like it will be unpleasant, right? </state>
                <state img="#-lost.png">This is all so unusual. Hopefully I can just relax and enjoy myself...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-curious.png">Ooh... okay, that's... that's it...</state>
                <state img="#-excited.png">I just need... a little extra...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">G-gosh... everybody is looking...</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">All this excitement does have me feeling pretty horny...</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">There's not a lot of privacy on the Flutter. I make sure the bath faucet is running when I do this at home.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Well, this makes for good stress release at least...</state>
                <state img="#-lusty.png">This is nice... but will it be enough?</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">This is... so... b-but still it feels...</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Hm... c'mon...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Mmf, oh, I've got it now...</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Hah... oh, right there...</state>
                <state img="#-worried.png">Hope I'm not... making too much noise...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-heavyc.png">Ha... ha... almost... I'm almost...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png">I'm so close... I can't stand it...</state>
                <state img="#-heavya.png">Mm, I'm going to... to...</state>
                <state img="#-heavya.png">Ah, I'm... haa... almost...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png">Feels like it's going to be a big one...</state>
                <state img="#-heavyc.png">Oh, faster... come on now...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-climax.png">Mm... that's it...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">Wow... that was amazing. I think... I think I needed that...</state>
                <state img="#-afterglow.png">H-hang on... I'm still... I just need a second...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-confused.png">I hope this doesn't go on for too much longer. I've got to get back to the Flutter to help cook dinner.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">Just because I'm done doesn't mean I'm still not just the tiniest bit in the mood...</state>
                <state img="#-curious.png">I wonder if I'd still be in the game if I took off my socks and gloves separately...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Hm, I'm going to need a bath after this...</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">Mmm... hmm...</state>
                <state img="#-nervous.png">I hope nobody back home hears about any of this...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I feel so relaxed now. It's probably not a good idea to take a nap here on the floor though, huh?</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">It is fun to just watch without having to worry about whether I'm going to win or lose.</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Should I... be putting my clothes back on now?</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Just keep doing your best!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-4">
                <state img="#-curious.png">So that's it then? I won? That went better than I could've hoped for.</state>
                <state img="#-wave.png">Not too shabby, huh? I've got a trick or two up my sleeve, so don't you forget it?</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">I feel kind of bad that I won without really getting naked. No hard feelings, right?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Another close call! Well, thanks for playing! I had a lot of fun!</state>
                <state img="#-stretch.png">That's that. It's too bad since I was starting to get used to standing around like this.</state>
                <state img="#-smirking.png">You came close, but it wasn't good enough. I hope you still had fun!</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-smiling.png">Well, congratulations, ~target~! Luck really was on your side to~background.time~.</state>
                <state img="#-giggling.png">I guess you could say ~target~ won, but ~target.ifMale(he|she)~ is the only one here who didn't cum...</state>
                <state img="#-flattered.png">Gosh, that was embarrassing. Well, ~target~, I hope you had a good time too.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
