<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<metadata>
    <owner>magical_sempai</owner>
    <height />
    <age />
    <pronunciation />
    <othernotes>Main personality points:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Very aggressive about wanting to do magic tricks. This means being very stubborn to do them, wanting others to see or participate in her magic.&lt;br&gt;Even though she sucks at magic, she pretends that everything is going alright, or puts others down in order to make herself look good.&lt;br&gt;Casually suggests or does things that are inappropriate or immoral.&lt;br&gt;Cute and excited personality. Can be very childish or annoying.&lt;br&gt;Overreacts to everything&lt;br&gt;Unintelligent and socially inept when it comes to anything that isn't magic</othernotes>
    <noteworthy>
        <case name="Hat drop good" id="2" priority="Noteworthy" min="3" max="3">
            <description>Sempai gets a good hand, but suddenly her hat falls from the sky and hits her head.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Hat drop okay" id="18" priority="Noteworthy" min="3" max="3">
            <description>Sempai gets an okay hand, but suddenly her hat falls from the sky and hits her head.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Hat drop bad" id="19" priority="Noteworthy" min="3" max="3">
            <description>Sempai gets a bad hand, but suddenly her hat falls from the sky and hits her head.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Socks-through-shoes trick" id="1" priority="Noteworthy" min="1" max="1">
            <description>Sempai performs a magic trick that involves tearing her socks off without taking off her shoes.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Flying-cape-and-hat trick" id="20" priority="Noteworthy" min="3" max="3">
            <description>Sempai performs a magic trick that involves making her cape and hat fly into the air.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Quick-change trick" id="3" priority="Noteworthy" min="3" max="3">
            <description>Semapi performs a magic trick that involves quickly removing her blazer. However, she accidentally reveals her bra.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Cards fall out of skirt" id="4" priority="Noteworthy" min="4" max="4">
            <description>Sempai is revealed to be cheating by keeping extra cards hidden under her skirt.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Hiding cards under shirt" id="21" priority="Noteworthy" min="5" max="5">
            <description>Sempai takes off her shirt, while carefully stowing away other hidden cards she had underneath.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Hidden tapes under bra trick" id="6" priority="Noteworthy" min="6" max="6">
            <description>Sempai tears off her bra revealing that her nipples are covered in tapes... except they're not.</description>
        </case>
        <case name="Disappearing panties trick" id="14" priority="Noteworthy" min="7" max="7">
            <description>Sempai implies shoving her panties inside herself. Instead, she performs a magic trick that involves putting her panties  in her hands and making them vanish.</description>
        </case>
    </noteworthy>
    <responses>
        <response id="9" opponent="mari_setogaya" opponentId="55" />
        <response id="10" opponent="mari_setogaya" opponentId="56" />
        <response id="11" opponent="twisted_fate" opponentId="254" />
        <response id="13" opponent="twisted_fate" opponentId="174" />
        <response id="17" opponent="tharja" opponentId="11" />
        <response id="23" opponent="nagatoro" opponentId="223" />
        <response id="24" opponent="nagatoro" opponentId="2" />
        <response id="25" opponent="nagatoro" opponentId="10" />
        <response id="26" opponent="kumatora" opponentId="170" />
        <response id="27" opponent="kumatora" opponentId="208" />
        <response id="28" opponent="kumatora" opponentId="191" />
        <response id="35" opponent="bobobo" opponentId="93" />
        <response id="37" opponent="barbara" opponentId="10" />
        <response id="38" opponent="senko" opponentId="15" />
        <response id="39" opponent="senko" opponentId="168" />
    </responses>
    <notes>
        <note id="1">Sempai will remove her socks first using magic. However, she realizes how uncomfortable wearing shoes without socks is

Sempai will try hypnosis for one round, but avoids the effects by keeping her eyes shut. This will end up making her lose a hand easily

Possibly have dove fly off with the hat, and have it fail somehow

Masturbation may involve being tied up and toyed, and escaping before she reaches an orgasm.</note>
        <note id="2">She will be in a thinking pose. have her hat drop on her head It will be animated. have her tilt her head down and put her hand on her head</note>
        <note id="3">Sempai using pullstrings to quickly tear off her blazer. However, in the process of doing that, she accidentally pulls the upper part of her shirt, revealing her bra and cleavage</note>
        <note id="4">When Sempai takes off her skirt, she will accidentally reveal playing cards under her skirt suspected on her panties</note>
        <note id="5">Tricks to do
Have cards in both hands, shuffles them, and glances over them left and right with her eyes
Uses one hand to make a coin disappear, or turn into something else
Rolling a ball in her hand to practice hand muscles</note>
        <note id="6">Sempai will rip off her bra, but the pasties to ver herself will fall out from the bra</note>
        <note id="7">Sempai thinks that the player is horny for magic</note>
        <note id="8">Sempai think the player is doing it for presentation like magic</note>
        <note id="14">Magical sempai says she will make her panties disappear by shoving it... into her hands</note>
        <note id="32">Sempai think the player is doing it for presentation like magic</note>
    </notes>
    <nextId>39</nextId>
    <markers>
        <marker scope="Public" name="chuuni_strip_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="HatFall" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="kumatora_hand_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="kumatora_hand_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="lonely_strip_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="lonely_strip_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="magicalgirl_strip_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="magicalgirl_strip_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="mediumhair_strip_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="moe_strip_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="moe_strip_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="moe_strip_3" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="nagatoro_hand_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="nagatoro_hand_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="nagatoro_hand_3" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="nagatoro_hand_4" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="nami_hand_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="nami_hand_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="pervert_strip_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="pervert_strip_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="sheena_hand_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="superhero_strip_1" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="superhero_strip_2" />
        <marker scope="Public" name="whitehair_strip_1" />
    </markers>
</metadata>
