<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>

<!--This file was machine generated using the Character Editor v6.7.9.1 at 2:25:55 PM on January 05, 2023. Do not edit this file directly unless you know what you're doing.-->
<opponent>
    <version>v6.7.9.1</version>
    <first>Binah</first>
    <last />
    <label>Binah</label>
    <gender>female</gender>
    <size>medium</size>
    <timer>30</timer>
    <intelligence>average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="1">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="2">good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="3">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="4">average</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="5">good</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="6">best</intelligence>

    <intelligence stage="7">best</intelligence>

    <nicknames>
        <nickname for="critical_darling">Ibuki</nickname>
    </nicknames>


    <wardrobe>
        <clothing name="panties" generic="underwear" position="lower" type="important" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="bra" generic="bra" position="upper" type="important" />
        <clothing name="leggings" generic="leggings" position="lower" type="major" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="shirt" generic="shirt" position="upper" type="major" />
        <clothing name="shoes" generic="shoes" position="feet" type="minor" plural="true" />
        <clothing name="coat" generic="jacket" position="upper" type="minor" />
        <clothing name="cloak" generic="cape" position="upper" type="minor" />
    </wardrobe>


    <behaviour>
        <trigger id="selected">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Countless stars light the sky again today.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="TheWingQuote">“Every day I am fated to die. When I awake from the sleep I have been sleeping - how long ago did I begin this sleep that I sleep?" The Wing, by Yi Sang.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="FaustQuote">“Imagination, however high it flies, falls short, however hard it tries. But spirits fit to see deeply invest in what is boundless a boundless trust." That was Faust part Two by van Goethe.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="DonQuixoteQuote">"The most perceptive character in a play is the fool, because the man who wishes to seem simple cannot possibly be a simpleton." That one is from Don Quixote by Cervantes.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="HellScreenQuote">“He was said to have survived starvation by eating human flesh, after which he had the strength to tear out the antlers of a living stag with his bare hands.” Hell Screen by Akutagawa.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="TheStrangerQuote">“I may not have been sure about what really did interest me, but I was absolutely sure about what didn't.” The Stranger, by Albert Camus.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="DoRCQuote">“Truth becomes fiction when the fiction's true; real becomes un-real where the unreal's real."  That was The Dream of Red Chamber by Cao Xueqin.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="WutheringHeightsQuote">“If all else perished, and he remained, I should still continue to be; and if all else remained, and he were annihilated, the universe would turn to a mighty stranger.” Wuthering Heights by Emily Bronte.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="MobyDickQuote">“Talk not to me of blasphemy, man; I'd strike the sun if it insulted me.” That was Moby Dick by Herman Melville, a personal favorite of mine. </state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="CrimeAndPunishmentQuote">“Pain and suffering are always inevitable for a large intelligence and a deep heart. The really great men must, I think, have great sadness on earth.” Crime and Punishment, Dostoevsky,</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="DivineComedyQuote">“All hope abandon, ye who enter here.” The Divine Comedy by Dante Alighieri. Many only know Inferno, but it is actually three stories.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="DemianQuote">“If you hate a person, you hate something in him that is part of yourself. What isn't part of ourselves doesn't disturb us.”  Herman Hesse's Demian.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="TheOdysseyQuote">“Of all creatures that breathe and move upon the earth, nothing is bred that is weaker than man.” That was Homer's The Odyssey.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="MetamorphosisQuote">“I cannot make you understand. I cannot make anyone understand what is happening inside me. I cannot even explain it to myself.” Metamorphosis by Franz Kafka.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="OrlandoFuriosoQuote">“Ah, how I rue that what I could have done I did not do!” That is Orlando Furioso, by Ariosto.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="ClockworkOrangeQuote">“The important thing is moral choice. Evil has to exist along with good, in order that moral choice may operate. Life is sustained by the grinding opposition of moral entities.” Clockwork Orange, by Burgess.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="DODOESQuote">“You will be required to do wrong no matter where you go. It is the basic condition of life, to be required to violate your own identity.” That one is from Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_start">
            <case stage="0" priority="300">
                <condition role="self" notSaidMarker="MetamorphosisQuote" />
                <condition role="opp" character="anatoly" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="AnatolyBait">Hmm, does anyone at the table do much reading? I am looking to pick up some new titles.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="AnatolyBait">Are there any other avid readers here, I'd like to find some new titles to pick up.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="AnatolyBait">I'm in need of some new books to read, my current collection is looking quite bare.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="300">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuri" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="YuriNovelRec">You appear well read, my child. I have taken to literature recently due to my new domain and career. Care to share any book recommendations?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="YuriNovelRec">You look like one with a good head for literature. I am looking for new novels to read, have you any ones to recommend?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="DokiDokiBinah">I believe I heard mention of a "literature club", are you looking for new members? I am currently looking for others to share in my taste of literature that aren't my co-workers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="300">
                <condition role="opp" character="tomoko" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="TomoJudge">You look a bit maladjusted, my child. Are you quite alright?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="TomoJudge">You almost remind me of Netzach, only not an alcoholic. I smell a strong odor on you, but not alcohol.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="TomoJudge">Were you by any chance held in a dumpster for some extended time, my child? You do not look... right.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="300">
                <condition role="opp" character="komi-san" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="KomiMute">If you don't mind my asking, are you unable to speak, Komi-san?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="KomiMute">You seem quite quiet, my child. Are you incapable of speech, or perhaps prefer not to?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="KomiMute">Are you unable to speak, my child? If so, it's not a problem, I am simply curious.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" priority="300">
                <condition role="opp" character="dwight" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="DwightRunning">I sense you are a man who is used to running, Dwight. But what from?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="DwightRunning">You look to be a man who spent a long time running away, Dwight. From what? I am curious.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="DwightRunning">Dwight, I am curious. You look to spend a lot of time running away, but what could you be running from?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="aloy" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_aloy_tailor">Such rudimentary clothing, Aloy. It does not appear to be made from a Tailor, how do you expect to survive any encounters?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_aloy_tailor">What a strange manner of dress, Aloy, how do you expect to survive? You should consult a Tailor, I will even give you the contact to the ones A-Corp utilized.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_aloy_tailor">What are you wearing, Aloy? Did you make it yourself? That will not do at all, you should consult a Tailor. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="blake_belladonna" />
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="binah_blake_gothromance">“I care for myself. The more solitary, the more friendless, the more unsustained I am, the more I will respect myself.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="binah_blake_gothromance">“If all the world hated you and believed you wicked, while your own conscience approved of you and absolved you from guilt, you would not be without friends.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="binah_blake_gothromance" font-size="smaller">“I can live alone, if self-respect, and circumstances require me so to do. I need not sell my soul to buy bliss. I have an inward treasure born with me, which can keep me alive if all extraneous delights should be withheld, or offered only at a price I cannot afford to give.”</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="caitlin" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_caitlin_intrigue">Now &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; are interesting. Caitlin, was it? I will be keeping my eye on you, I have not felt an aura from anyone that piqued my interest like you...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_caitlin_intrigue">I wonder what this feeling emanating from you is. At first I thought you just some sickly girl, but now? Is it Distortion, or something else? Only time will tell.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_caitlin_intrigue">How... interesting. I will have my eye close on you, Caitlin, you intrigue me. I want to see just what this aura around you means.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="cheryl" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_cheryl_distortion">You have been touched by the Distortion, Cheryl. Am I correct? No, not the Distortion, but something similar. What sort of world did you flee?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_cheryl_distortion">The Distortion... no, something similar. More malicious. Just what life did you lead, dear Cheryl?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_cheryl_distortion">Cheryl, what sort of life have you lived? I have not seen someone so marked as you, by something evil. I thought it was the Distortion, but no, the Distortion is not evil. Whatever haunts you, is.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="darkness" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_darkness_fixerknight">So, you are one of those newer Fixers that dress up all fancy for work, yes? It is adorable, Darkness, I love Fixers like you.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_darkness_fixerknight">Goodness, all that armor. Ohohoh, you must not have enough to afford a Tailor yet. It's cute, seeing Fixers play at being knights.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_darkness_fixerknight">Are you some Grade 9 Fixer, roleplaying a knight? Adorable, I do enjoy seeing what gimmicks new offices make nowadays.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="hilbert" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_hilbert_pokeballs">Say, I notice some strange readings coming from that bag of yours, Hilbert. What did you bring to this game, dear?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_hilbert_pokeballs">You have something in that bag, Hilbert, what are you smuggling? It gives off the same energy as U-Corp products, but I am not sure...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_hilbert_pokeballs">I would like to know what you have in your bag, Hilbert, I can't ignore the strange energy coming from them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="mitama" />
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="binah_mitama_haiku">"The Arbiter stalks &lt;br&gt;Cloaked in shadow's grim embrace. &lt;br&gt; Another star falls." &lt;br&gt;I believe that is how those poems go, right Mitama? Haiku, correct?</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="binah_mitama_haiku">Perhaps I may try my hand at a Haiku, Mitama. &lt;br&gt;"The stars light the sky&lt;br&gt;the watcher keeps them in check. &lt;br&gt;Why can't she join them?" &lt;br&gt;I pray I am not as good as you are.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="binah_mitama_haiku">If I may try, Mitama. &lt;i&gt;Ahem&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;br&gt;"Stars of the City &lt;br&gt;The Obsidian Warden&lt;br&gt;Massacre, at dawn."&lt;br&gt;Was that any good?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="okino" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_okino_friends">You were thinking of recommending this place to others, too? I have a few co-workers who could use the stress relief.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_okino_friends">I, too, was planning on inviting a few colleagues. I do think they will enjoy the time here.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_okino_friends">Perhaps I, too, will invite some friends here. I have many colleagues who could take a load off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="shamir" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_shamir_bow">Bow and arrows? How adorable, I have not seen something quite so &lt;i&gt;amusing&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_shamir_bow">Oh, Shamir, you sweet thing. You really carry around a bow? Oh, I have not seen such a thing outside of a museum.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_shamir_bow">Oh, thank you, Shamir. I needed the laugh, at seeing that adorable little bow of yours. Would you mind firing one at me, I want to feel it bounce off my cloak.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="steve" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_steve_upsidedown">You are an odd looking man, Steve. Now, why do you give off such an ominous aura?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_steve_upsidedown">I cannot decide what is stranger. Your hair, or the fact you give off such an otherworldly aura. What life have you lived?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_steve_upsidedown">You are weird, Steve, but in a sort of charming way. I cannot shake that strange aura of yours though, you must tell me what you have went through, where you have been.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kyoko_kirigiri" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_kirigiri_analytical">You seem to keep looking around, Kyoko. Are you looking for something, or just drinking in the environment? I am curious what causes you to be so vigilant.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_kirigiri_analytical">The way you carry yourself is not  how your average woman would, Kyoko. Tell me, why do you feel the need to be so vigilant? It almost appears you are analyzing the participants here.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_kirigiri_analytical">You can relax, Kyoko. There isn't anything to analyze yet. I am curious what life you had to make you so cautious of your surroundings, though.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="chie" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_chie_sadist">Such a hopeful, energetic girl. My old tendencies rear their head, and I am urged to crush you. Forgive me, Chie, old habits are hard to shake.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_chie_sadist">Your optimism is adorable, Chie. My natural instinct is to destroy it, and break you. I ask you forgive me, it is simply what I was made for.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_chie_sadist">I must resist the urge. You awaken some feelings I have tried to purge in myself, but of course they never leave. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="dunban" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_dunban_accent">Dunban, forgive me if this is too forward, but I find your accent to be incredibly attractive.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_dunban_accent">I must say, Dunban, I do find your voice very attractive. The accent you speak in is nearly making me blush.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_dunban_accent">I always was infatuated with your sort of accent, Dunban. It is not too common where I am from, so I have taken quite the liking to it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="aaravi" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_aaravi_past">Aaravi, you look like quite a seasoned fighter. Are you something like a Fixer? Perhaps a member of a Syndicate?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_aaravi_past">You look like one who knows combat, someone who has fought and killed many. Are you a Fixer? A member of a Syndicate? You look like you could even be a Color Fixer.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_aaravi_past">I wonder what you are, Aaravi. A Fixer? A syndicate member? Just another run of the mill murderer?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="dorothy" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_dorothy_aiethics">You are lucky I no longer serve The Head. If I had, I'd have killed you on the spot, for breaching the AI Ethics Amendment. So, Dorothy, it is your lucky day.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_dorothy_aiethics">Where I am from, sapient robots must be killed immediately upon encountering them. Luckily, we are not where I am from.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_dorothy_aiethics">The AI Ethics Amendment would call for your death, Dorothy. Be grateful, because I would have disposed of you immediately.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_kaz_wings">I always hated the pampered rich of the Nests. So boring, so pampered. Maybe someday your Nest will collapse, and you will learn pain.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_kaz_wings">You really get on my nerves, Kaz. You and those rich, pampered feathers of the Wings.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png" marker="binah_kaz_wings">Bloody feathers, you rich snobs in the Nests. I always delighted in my work, but I could not stand those in the Nests who lived so easily. When was the last time you struggled, Kaz?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="lucy" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_lucy_exposed">So much exposed skin is a great way to die, Lucy.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_lucy_exposed">Bearing so much of your flesh is dangerous. Are you confident, or arrogant? </state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_lucy_exposed">Exposing so much skin, do you comprehend the dangers that poses, Lucy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="lyralei" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_lyralei_bow">A bow and arrow? Oh, that is adorable, Lyralei.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_lyralei_bow">Such an archaic weapon, have you even spilled blood with such a ridiculous instrument?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_lyralei_bow">Seeing someone with such a foolish weapon is quite refreshing, sensibility has grown tiresome. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="neptune" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_neptune_fakegod">A God is only a coping mechanism made by those who seek reason in the unreasonable. Anyone who claims to be one simply wants power.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_neptune_fakegod">You call yourself a God, Neptune? Tch, you are no better than the Index. I bet you do so to prey on their desperation, too.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_neptune_fakegod">Ugh, another power-hungry fool that wishes to call herself a God. I grow tired of the same ridiculous farce, day after day.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="toph" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_toph_blind">Are you truly blind, Toph? I can not imagine going through life lacking such a vital sense.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_toph_blind">To think, you lived so long deprived of sight. You must be an impressive woman, Toph.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_toph_blind">I have heard of people replacing their eyes, it is not uncommon to lose body parts. But to willingly continue life without sight is unheard of. How have you lived so long?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="trixie" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_trixie_distortion">Just... what are you, Trixie? I would assume you are a result of the Distortion, but you do not give off that energy.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_trixie_distortion">My first instinct is to assume you are a result of the Distortion, but I have seen that effect with my own eyes. I know the aura of the Distortion, and you do not hold it, Trixie.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_trixie_distortion">I have never seen something like you, Trixie. Are you the Distortion, or are you something else?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="adora" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_adora_corpfixer">A sword that expensive-looking makes me assume you are some sort of corporate Fixer, Adora. Perhaps an affiliate of T-Corp or W-Corp?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_adora_corpfixer">That sword looks pricey, did your employers cover it? I imagine a Fixer affiliated with T-Corp or W-Corp would have their kit paid for.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_adora_corpfixer">Ah, another corporate Fixer with a fancy workshop weapon. Did your employers at W-Corp buy you that? Maybe you work for T-Corp instead?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="sannytess" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_sannytess_duo1">Are you two playing as a duo? Is that allowed within the rules?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I had not considered playing with a partner; is there even any benefit to such?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="aella" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_aella_big">Aella, you are quite large. I can only imagine that gives quite the benefit to melee combat.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_aella_big">Your size must make fighting easier, Aella. Sure, you may be less agile, but you surely can dish out punishment to those foolish enough to take you head to head.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_aella_big">You are indeed very large, Aella. I mean no offense, physical bulk is quite useful in combat.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="akko" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_akko_magic">A witch? Surely you must be joking. Magic is not accessible by any regular person, even if it was real.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="amalia" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_amalia_plantclothing">Are you wearing plants? Well, you really do meet all sorts of people...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="amy" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_amy_literature">You are part of a literature group, correct? Do you think we could discuss some literature then, Amy? I am not very good with socializing, but I am well-versed in books.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_amy_literature">Amy, you appear to be an avid reader. Do you want to discuss some of our favorite works, perhaps?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_amy_literature">I am looking for more people to discuss literature with. What sort of books do you enjoy most, Amy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="amy_rose" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_amyrose_petting">Those ears are adorable, Amy. How much was the body modification procedure? I know they can be quite expensive. Would it be alright if I touched them?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_amyrose_petting">What adorable little ears, Amy. I always wanted to see how sensitive the body modification procedure makes them. May I touch them?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="aqua_grunt" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_ag_syndicate0">Team Aqua? I've not heard of this Syndicate.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_ag_syndicate0">Another day, another new Syndicate. Team Aqua sounds about as interesting as the rest of them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="arueshalae" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_arueshalae_threatening1">Well, I wasn't expecting to run into someone like you, Arueshalae.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_arueshalae_threatening1">Arueshalae, even just your name sounds threatening. I was not expecting to run into someone like you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="asuna_yuuki" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_asuna_fixer">Asuna, you look quite capable. I may not be with Hana Association, but if I was I'd place you at Grade 1 in terms of Fixers.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="ayano" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_ayano_searching">Are you looking for someone, Ayano?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_ayano_searching">Do you need help with finding someone, Ayano?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_ayano_searching">Who are you searching for, Ayano? Perhaps I can offer some assistance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="barbara" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_barbara_favonius0">"Church of Favonius"? Color me skeptical.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_barbara_favonius0">Color me skeptical of this "Church of Favonius".</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kyouko_toshinou" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_kyouko_hyper">Kyouko appears to just be some hyperactive student. Or perhaps that is a ploy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="beatrix" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_beatrix_hubris">Another victim of their own hubris, and the technology of the City. I pity you, Beatrix.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_beatrix_hubris">To give up your own humanity in the pursuit of hubris and science. I pity you, Beatrix.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_bernie_seminar0">This is meant to be some sort of seminar? I was not aware. Still, I suppose I will stick around. Thank you for informing me, Bernadetta.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="brock" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_brock_rocket0">Brock, is that a real rocket launcher? Does it actually fire an explosive payload? &lt;i&gt;Did you really bring it to this game of strip poker?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="cagliostro" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_cag_flirting">What an adorable girl you are, Cagliostro. I cannot wait to see you lose.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_cag_flirting">I pray this is not too forward, but I would like to see you lose this game, Cagliostro.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_cag_flirting">We all know why we are here. I, for one, am here to see Cagliostro lose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="cammy_white" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_cammy_fixer0">What a very professional woman. I'm sure you must be a successful Fixer; maybe even a Colour.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="adrien" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_catnoir_colorfixer">Now that is a way to turn heads, Cat Noir. It's funny, your name almost fits the naming conventions of Color Fixers. A shame that black is an active Color Fixer.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_catnoir_colorfixer">Had it not been for the existence of a black Color Fixer, I'd have assumed you were one. Cat Noir, it has a ring to it.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_catnoir_colorfixer">Cat Noir certainly has a ring to it. A shame black is already taken - that could have been your title as a Color Fixer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="catria" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_catria_simplefixer">Quite simplistic gear. Catria is your average new Fixer, it seems.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_catria_simplefixer">Just a run-of-the-mill Fixer, Catria is nothing too special, it seems.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="caulifla" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_caulifla_hair">Your hair is quite unruly; is that on purpose?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_caulifla_hair">Did you choose that hairstyle consciously, Caulifla? It is quite unruly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="chara_dreemurr" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_chara_evil">Chara... you have an aura of pure evil...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_chara_evil">Chara, what are you? I have not felt such palpable evil before.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_chara_evil">Such malice and evil inside such a person. I have not felt this before...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="chazz" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_chazz_dueldisk0">What is that on your arm, Chazz? I've not seen a device like that.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_chazz_dueldisk0">What a strange device, Chazz. What is it?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="chiaki" />
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="readyplayeronequote">“You'd be amazed how much research you can get done when you have no life whatsoever.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="readyplayeronequote" font-size="smaller">“Whenever I saw the sun, I reminded myself that I was looking at a star. One of over a hundred billion in our galaxy. A galaxy that was just one of billions of other galaxies in the observable universe. This helped me keep things in perspective.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="readyplayeronequote">"No one in the world gets what they want and that is beautiful."</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="chihiro" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_fujisaki_wing">A programmer? Which Wing do you work for?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_fujisaki_wing">A few Wings use programmers. Which are you with?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_fujisaki_wing">I know many Wings are in need of programmers. Which are you with?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="chun-li" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png" marker="binah_chunli_legs">Forgive me, Chun-Li. Those legs of yours inspired some... thoughts in me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="coco" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_coco_bullets">So many bullets. You must be quite well off, Coco. Not even The Thumb has that much of an excess on bullets.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="critical_darling" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_cdarling_musician0">A musician? I only hope you're a normal one, Ibuki.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="croix" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_croix_tech0">Such strange technology. I sure hope Croix didn't bring anything dangerous to our game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="cynthia" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_cynthia_flirt">Such a powerful presence. I like that in a woman, Cynthia.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="dark_magician_girl" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dmg_magicalgirl">Dark Magician Girl? Now who do &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; remind me of?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="dust" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_dust_distortion0">To think that the Distortion Effect even reaches out here. I'll keep my eye on Dust.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_dust_distortion0">What an interesting sight. A result of the Distortion Effect, standing before me. I'll need to keep my eye on Dust.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I hope you are ready to begin, everyone. I pray you do not go too easy on me.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Your willingness to challenge me is admirable, but try not to overwork yourselves.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Tis an ordeal to overcome, for you and for me.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I pray I learn not only the shape of your bodies, but the contents of your minds and hearts. Do hold nothing back.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Have any of you read any good books lately? I hope you do not mind me quoting some of them.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I am excited we all get to be here together, I only hope you did not come in hopes of winning.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="swap_cards">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" cmp="&gt;" value="1" />
                <test expr="~cards~" cmp="&lt;" value="5" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Please allow me ~cards.text~, dealer.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Give me ~cards.text~, sir.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">~Cards.text~, if you would be so kind.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I will trade away ~cards.text~. Let us see if I can rewrite fate.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Fate is fickle; I'll need ~cards.text~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I have need of ~cards.text~ more, Dealer.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I shall rid myself of  ~cards.text~ and replace them if it is alright.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I would like to swap ~cards.text~, dealer, thank you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I need only one, dealer.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Ohoho, nearly perfect. Let me swap one.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I only need one card, are you afraid ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Just one please, dealer.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">One will do, thank you.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">If you would be so kind, I only need one.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">How quaint, I only need one.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">One, now, if you will.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">How pleasing, my hand is perfect as is.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">As an Arbiter always must, I began with the tools I need.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Would you look at that? I need not exchange any cards.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Are you worried, ~player~? I will not be exchanging my cards this round.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Ohoho, how lovely. I was dealt a hand not needing of change.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">No cards, dealer. I am satisfied.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~cards~" value="5" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Just give me a new hand.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Worthless, give me another one.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I suppose I must start from the beginning.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Nothing of value in this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Are you quite serious? A new hand, please.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">These cards are no good, not even one worth keeping.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I've gotten out of tougher. I'll start from the top.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">You shouldn't see this.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="good_hand">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="self" hasHand="Royal Flush" />
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="FaustQuote">“As soon as you trust yourself, you will know how to live.”</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">The Royal Flush, only the best for one like me of course.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I can get used to the royal treatment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I do not believe I will be losing this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">There will be no obstacle I cannot overcome.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">One's outlook is what decides many things.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Stars truly do shine brightly, yes?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="StarOfTheCity">I am curious, what does a star mean to you?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">My apologies, but I will be taking this victory.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I doubt you'll surpass this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I suppose it will keep me in the game a bit longer.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">A little late, but whatever. As long as I am still in the game.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I appreciate it, even if I'm already in a corner.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good, this will stave off my defeat a bit longer.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I just need to get this lucky for awhile longer.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Good, I am not fully defeated yet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Excellent, this will surely keep me going.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I have little to worry about, this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You will not expose me any further.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Good, I won't need to take much more off.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">This will keep me going - the call of the void is silenced.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Good, I won't be out too soon then.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="okay_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It could go either way.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Mediocrity at times is more offensive than that which is objectively worse.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">So dull, truly this draws my ire.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I do dislike the common mediocrities in life. These cards are amongst the worst offenders.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Nothing remarkable here, I fear.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="195" marker="PrayerForLovingSorrow" font-size="small">"O my sorrow, you are better than a well-beloved: because I know that on the day of my final agony, you will be there, lying in my sheets, O sorrow, so that you might once again attempt to enter my heart."</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="196" marker="TheStrangerQuote">“I opened myself to the gentle indifference of the world.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="197" marker="MetamorphosisQuote">“Calm (indeed the calmest) reflection might be better than the most confused decisions.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="198" marker="DemianQuote">“I have been and still am a seeker, but I have ceased to question stars and books; I have begun to listen to the teaching my blood whispers to me.”</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-bored.png">I don't have a great feeling about a hand this... mediocre.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">This hand does not inspire hope. It hardly inspires &lt;i&gt;anything&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is not the time to be receiving such base hands.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Great, this is just what I need. A bland, boring hand while I'm already exposing myself.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Really? It isn't the worst, but really?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Such mediocrity, I just need to hope someone else has a worse hand.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">The median is not what I was wanting, but I suppose it can be worse.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">This should be enough, for this round.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I pray this is enough to keep me decent.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Will this be enough? I have lost so many times already.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">As long as at least one person has a worse hand, this is doable.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Bitter, just as tea is meant to be.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Is this the best I can get at this point?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Such mediocrity does not bode well when I am standing in my underwear...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="bad_hand">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">This bodes worrisome for me.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">How very troublesome indeed.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">This is not looking to favour me at all.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Well, get on with it. Either I lose or I don't, I have accepted such.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">To wish to never lose is a foolish dream.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">A star can only truly be seen in the darkness...</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Even if a burden that cannot be avoided comes my way, I shan't collapse.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I suppose it was foolish to believe I could avoid it.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">A rubbish hand, wonderful.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is quite an awful hand...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well, it appears I will be losing this round.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Great, just what I needed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-anger.png">Damn you, dealer. You cannot be serious with a hand like this.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">This is not a time for piss-poor hands. </state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">A hand like this is not going to suffice.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Such a useless hand. I'm not in a position where I can handle losses.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">...</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Oh dear, this might be it for me...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">This is hardly what I need at this time.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I need better than this.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I really needed better, dealer.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I am already near nude, and this is the hand I must receive?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Goodness, I might have to strip again this round.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">I am far from pleased with this hand.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Hardly worth my time when my last cards were better.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I do not think I will avoid stripping this round.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">A star can only truly be seen in the darkness...</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Dealer, do you &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; wish to get on my bad side?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well, I suppose I'll be stripping again.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Tsk.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">What a rubbish hand.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="hand">
            <case stage="0-7" oneShotId="22" priority="999">
                <condition role="opp" character="amalia" saidMarker="grow1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_amalia_flowers2">To think you'd resort to cheating. Pathetic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="opp" character="dunban" sayingMarker="dunban_binah_teatimeQ1" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_dunban_teatimeA1">I only drink black tea, free of any sugar or milk. Nothing except for the tea itself, anything else would ruin the purity of the flavour. Care for a cup, Dunban?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="5" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Angela" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png">~player~, you share a name with someone dear to me. I almost wish I could invite her to join us. I did always find her quite attractive.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="6" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Roland" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png">~player~, hm? "That's that, this is this". That's what he would say. I wonder if he would join if I requested.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="7" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Yesod" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I do not think Yesod would ever come here. I doubt he's gotten used to his own flesh. My apologies, ~player~, a co-worker of mine shares your name.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="8" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Malkuth" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png">What an uncommon name, ~player~. Frankly, Malkuth could do with a vacation. Such a busy bee, and I would hardly dislike the opportunity of playing with her.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="9" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Hod" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Ah, ~player~, you share a name with one of my co-workers. Hod... she was always quite cute. She was my eyes, I never did... reward her for such good behaviour that day.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="10" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Gebura" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">You really share a name with &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt;, ~player~? Maybe I'll need to make you my toy, at least until that woman shows up herself...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="11" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Netzach" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png">~player~, you share a name with one of my co-workers. He's a drunk, but I would be too had I been living his life. I think he would enjoy this game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="12" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Chesed" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I wonder, ~player~, do you like tea? Or are you like that blue-haired noble you share a name with, and drink only coffee? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="13" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Hokma" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png">What an interesting name, ~player~. I doubt we'd ever see the Hokma I knew here, he was only ever interested in one man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="14" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~player~" value="Binah" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What an odd coincidence, ~player~, that we both have the name Binah.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="15" totalRounds="0">
                <test expr="~background.category~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">So we'll be playing in a library, hm? I wonder what wondrous books this one holds.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">A library? I came to escape from work, though I suppose I cannot complain too much. I did always love a good book.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-1" oneShotId="23">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_lcorp_collapse">Many of you might have heard I work with a company called Lobotomy Corporation. Unfortunately, that Corporation has since collapsed. </state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_lcorp_collapse">You likely have heard I work for a group known as L Corp. That Wing no longer exists. It is not anyone's fault; that Wing was doomed to be clipped.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3" oneShotId="24">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_jcorp">I wonder if the nests of J Corp hold these sorts of games. It is the gambling center in The City.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" oneShotId="25">
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_myo">As a certain little rabbit would say: Time to graze the grass.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_myo">As a certain mercenary would say: Time to graze the grass.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_myo">As a particular R Corp captain would say: Time to graze the grass.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="26">
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_blacksilence">I'm sure Gebura would like this game, but I wonder about the other colors. Black Silence, perhaps... well, he wasn't ever really the Black Silence.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_purpletear">I'm sure Gebura would like this game, but I wonder about the other colors. The Purple Tear might be a bit too old for this.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_bluereverberation">I'm sure Gebura would like this game, but I wonder about the other colors. I would hope not to run into the Blue Reverberation.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5" oneShotId="29">
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_23">A tip for all of you: If you ever find yourself in District 23, don't order any food with meat in it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip">
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="20">
                <condition role="opp" character="okino" saidMarker="binah_friends1" sayingMarker="binah_work1a" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_okino_friends" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_okino_work1a">It is, luckily, much less stressful now. These days we are much more capable of living our own lives, though it is still good to unwind from the lingering stress.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="21">
                <condition role="opp" character="okino" saidMarker="binah_friends1" sayingMarker="binah_work1b" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_okino_friends" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_okino_work1b" font-size="small">Things have calmed much down, luckily. I work with a few other librarians, and I think nearly all of them could benefit from a release like this game. Many things can be gained from this game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuno_uno" sayingMarker="yuno_binah_books1" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_yuno_books1">Hmm, do not worry, my child. If you are studying history, perhaps we can compare facts of the worlds we come from?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_yuno_books1">Worry not, child, I am quite curious in the worlds people come from. How about we discuss history instead?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1" oneShotId="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuno_uno" sayingMarker="yuno_binah_tea1" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_yuno_tea1" font-size="small">It is neither, I simply am using a U-Corp Stasis Container to store a cup of tea, and a W-Corp Short-Distance Transportation Device, or an STD, to transport the cup into my hand when I wish. Both are common household products.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="ringo_ando" sayingMarker="binah_paleskin" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="re_binah_paleskin">Pale? I suppose I do not get much sun, I oft spend my time indoors. The only time I left was as an Arbiter, but I was often in this full uniform. Hardly time to tan.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="dunban" sayingMarker="dunban_binah_literature1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dunban_literature1">Yes, I consider myself an avid reader, though I only started thanks to a career change. Currently, I work at a Library, accumulating knowledge and philosophy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="dunban" sayingMarker="dunban_binah_intentions1" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_dunban_intentions1">You wound me, Dunban. I know I seem the type to exclusively observe, but I am a woman with needs. I am here for pleasure, the carnal desire of sexuality all humans carry deep within.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagatoro" sayingMarker="binah01" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_nagatoro_illiterate">Worry not, I did not expect you to understand. I had been working on the assumption that you did not know how to read to begin with, Nagatoro.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="jura" sayingMarker="binah0" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_jura_creepy1">I offer my apologies, Jura, I had not intended to cause discomfort. The life I lead has made socialization quite difficult. </state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_jura_creepy1">I apologize if I had given you those concerns, Jura. I do not intend to treat you like anything besides what you are, I can assure you. I understand if my disposition can cause discomfort.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="meia" sayingMarker="binah0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_meia_lcorp1">It depends on which employer. I have changed careers many times. Lobotomy Corporation was the source of all energy in The City, so it held much sway. </state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_meia_lcorp1">In terms of employers, I have had a few. Lobotomy Corporation was an energy company, the only one that was reliable. So, you can imagine it was considered quite important.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="revy" sayingMarker="binah0" />
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="binah_revy_communism1">Ah, Karl Marx. Since my most recent career had me as a librarian in charge of philosophy I am well versed. Though I suppose literature isn't your thing, Revy?</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="binah_revy_communism1">Karl Marx, the father of Marxism which would later inspire the  ideology of Communism. Thinkers like that are who I archived the works of, though I suppose books are not your thing?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="gloria" sayingMarker="gloria_binah_thesaurus1" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_gloria_thesaurus1">I assure you, it is not in any attempt of vanity. I am simply hoping to connect with others through literature.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_gloria_thesaurus1">I simply wish to connect to others through literature, as it is one of the few things I know. My apologies if my manner of speech bothers you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" sayingMarker="Binah_s0_1" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_kaz_fear1">As much as I enjoy people fearing me, no. You don't need to worry about me harming you. I am simply here to unwind, and have some fun.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="mitama" sayingMarker="Binah_librarian" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_mitama_librarian1">It is wonderful, Mitama. To be surrounded with so many books - it is a dream come true. I started with philosophy, as that was my floor.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="mitama" sayingMarker="Binah_haikuflirt" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_mitama_haikuflirt1">Why thank you, Mitama. Perhaps, when this game concludes, we can make our own art together?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_mitama_haikuflirt1">I love the feeling I get with your eyes upon me, Mitama. Maybe we should abscond together when this game ends? I would love to make love and art with you, my dear.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_mitama_haikuflirtdommy1">Darling, to say such things takes a level of boldness. I like girls who do not fear me. It makes it so much more fun to &lt;i&gt;make&lt;/i&gt; them fear me, Mitama.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="okino" sayingMarker="binah_strippoker1a" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_okino_strippoker1">I assume looking at me would cause one to think I am a more prim and proper woman, no? Okino, my child, I simply wish to enjoy the pleasures I have been denied. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon01" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_leon_reading1">Indeed, I consider myself one at least.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_leon_reading1">I would consider myself one. Working at a library has its perks.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_leon_reading1">Indeed, both philosophy and classical literature.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon11" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_leon_tea1">Simply put, you can truly taste the palpable agony of the tea leaf infused in each cup. If you can taste the full flavor of the tea, then you are enjoying a good cup.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="asuna_yuuki" sayingMarker="binah_stage0" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_asuna_hana1" font-size="small">Fixers are sort of general mercenaries. Hana Association is the absolute top of Fixer hierarchy. They decide the grade of Fixers, and act as the final authority of all offices and associations.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="eichi" sayingMarker="binah_interest1" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_eichi_mommydom1" font-size="small">My child, I am full of the same carnal desires that anyone else here is. As for my name, you can just call me Binah. However, mistress works just as well, and if you feel particularly bold: mother.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon21" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_leon_freetime1">I suppose my current employment situation is best described as laid off? It is complicated, but let us simply say I have a lot of free time now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon31" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_leon_attention1">I wish I could say it was my intention, Leon. Alas, this is simply my uniform.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="dwight" sayingMarker="binah_ms0" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png">It comes with the territory. My old job had me often being a symbol of fear for others. I suppose it is hard to break that intimidating aura.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="dwight" sayingMarker="binah_ms1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dwight_twilight1">I cannot say I am familiar with those books. My apologies, Dwight.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="mitama" sayingMarker="Binah_become_librarian" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_mitama_becomelibrarian">I simply awoke there, once again a living and breathing human being. I was unable to leave - not until the work was done - so I did my part.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="aaravi" sayingMarker="BinahWeirdVibes" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_aaravi_weirdvibes1" font-size="small">I suppose you could say that. I have quite a number of past lives, but I suppose I will start with my first. That of Garion the Arbiter, a weapon capable of destroying full Districts alone.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="3" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Goodness, three losses in a row?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="4-6" />
                <state img="#-anger.png">Again? How am I failing so absolutely?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-6">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="7-7" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Goodness this was a free fall. How did I fail so absolutely?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_winning">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Simply losing my cloak is of little consequence when I have such a lead.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">This is fine, I needn't keep my cloak on at this time.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This is hardly an issue, I will simply remove my cloak.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I am still &lt;i&gt;much&lt;/i&gt; better off than you all, my children. I can afford to  shed my cloak.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I am still well off, and besides this cloak can get heavy anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">With a lead I am more than willing to take another loss. After all, it is only my shoes next.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Sure, I suppose I will take another loss. My shoes can be the next sacrifice.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">So I must strip again? I suppose, next will be my shoes then.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Do not get too excited, I will only be removing my shoes. </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I suppose there are those who will get aroused from me removing my shoes. So be it, a price I am willing to pay.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hardly an issue. I lost once more, so now I must remove my jacket.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It is only my jacket next, I suppose it will make more of my form visible though. But hardly an issue.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">A second loss, I cannot expect to be exempt after all. No problem, I shall take off my jacket next.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I often take my jacket off when I am relaxing anyway, so this is no different than returning from a day of work.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Most would remove their jacket in company anyways, so this is hardly a large loss.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It seems it was unavoidable. Even with my dominance, I must reveal &lt;i&gt;something.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">A shame, even though I am winning I still must show some skin. Lucky you.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I will not kick up fuss, I signed up for this knowing I may have to show some skin.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not a worry, I am still winning after all. Why not give you all some &lt;i&gt;motivation&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-calm.png">My fifth loss, I would be upset but you are all much worse off.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I'm already showing my underwear, so what's one more piece of underwear shown? Besides, I am still winning.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Not a problem, I don't like being those close to the edge, but at least you've begun falling off the side.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-smug.png">I can at least live with the fact I am not the first to bare flesh.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">At least I am not the first - that is what matters to me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Despite the fact it required you to strip down as well, you  did succeed in stripping me down this much. Shall I show you your prize?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I might as well join those of you already nude.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I suppose I could not complete this game without baring my body more for you all.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_normal">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I have lost, so I suppose I shall remove my cloak for you all.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Congratulations on defeating me, but you are yet to get a reward. I am only removing the cloak.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Good work. As per the rules of the game, I shall shed my cloak now.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I doubt this will be all that tantalizing for you, my children. It will only be my cloak.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hmm, I am starting to run out of items I can take off without exposing too much...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This is troubling, but I am far from the worst off. I can come back from this.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I am far from out, but still, I was hoping to be winning this. I will remove my shoes, next.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I am performing worse than I originally predicted. I will need to focus more.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I do not mind taking my jacket off; I have yet to reveal anything major.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Next will be my jacket, not the most attractive I assure you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">If any of you are particularly fond of a woman's arms, then I suppose this is for you?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">A second loss, but I am far from bad off. Let me remove my jacket.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">My fourth loss, and I hope my last. Very well, you shall see beneath my shirt.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">It looks like I lost again. Next I shall remove my shirt for you all.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">My shirt next. Not a great sign but I am, luckily, not the worst off.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I see. Well, I can live without my shirt.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Losing my leggings next; you have bent my back more than I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">You pushed me a lot further than I expected. My fifth loss.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Well, I suppose you did earn this. Watch closely.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, you did it. Now I must bare my body further.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Watch closely. You did earn this, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Congratulations, ~player~, you have pushed me to the brink.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I suppose I did sign up for this. I owe it to you now, ~player~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_strip_losing">
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Not a fantastic start for me, but it is only the first article of my clothing.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">My, I am not off to a fantastic start.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Tsk, behind already? I suppose nothing can be done.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Goodness I am under-performing. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I lost again? That is my third loss, and I am the worst one off. I am performing poorly...</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Again? I am performing poorly. It is only my shoes, but still, I need to do better if I am to win.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Fine, celebrate your win for now. I will not lose further.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I must rethink my strategy, if I am losing by this wide a margin...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I would prefer to be doing better, but this is fine. It is only my jacket after all.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You are all so overdressed... So be it, I shall remove my jacket.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">At least it is only my jacket...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Another loss, next is my shirt. I was hoping to avoid showing so much school this early.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Damn, I am not doing well at all. So be it, enjoy viewing my body without my shirt.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">It is more skin than I wanted to show this early. So be it, you did earn it.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Another loss? I swore I would be better than this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I cannot believe I am losing this much.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Tch, fine. You earned this, so you better witness it.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">To think I am losing so easily.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5-6">
                <state img="#-anger.png">Tch, to be left so utterly defenseless against you all. I truly have degraded.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I came here with the expectation of domination, not this.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Damn, I suppose I lost. Though I am not happy about it.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I bet you only come here to see this sort of thing, right ~player~? You do not seem capable of finding a partner outside of these games.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripping">
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="ringo_ando" saidMarker="binah_paleskin" sayingMarker="binah_arbiter" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="re_binah_paleskin" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="re_binah_arbiter" font-size="small">I was one of the Arbiters of The City. My masters would send me to snuff out rebellion or destroy non-compliant Wings. So, I suppose I was an Arbiter over death itself. I chose who lived or died.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="nagatoro" saidMarker="binah01" sayingMarker="binah02" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_nagatoro_illiterate" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_nagatoro_illiterate2">Only a B+? I'm sorry, my child. Perhaps you would like to read `The Very Hungry Caterpillar'? That may be more your style, Nagatoro.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" saidMarker="leon01" sayingMarker="leon02" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_reading1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_leon_mobydick">The books I enjoy are rather dense. I'll avoid the texts on philosophy, at least for now. How about `Moby Dick' by Herman Melville?</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_leon_thestand" font-size="small">Well, I suppose dense philosophical texts may be a bad start. How about `The Stand' by Stephen King? Frankly, I think you would like King's works in general, but that is a good place to start.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_leon_daskapital">Dense philosophical texts might be a bad suggestion. Actually, maybe you could enjoy some philosophy. How about `Das Kapital' by Karl Marx? I found that easily digestible.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuno_uno" saidMarker="yuno_binah_books1" sayingMarker="binah_yuno_books2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_yuno_books1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_yuno_books2" font-size="smaller">“If you know the enemy and know yourself, you need not fear the result of a hundred battles. If you know yourself but not the enemy, for every victory gained you will also suffer a defeat. If you know neither the enemy nor yourself, you will succumb in every battle.”</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_yuno_books2" font-size="smaller">“All warfare is based on deception. Hence, when we are able to attack, we must seem unable; when using our forces, we must appear inactive; when we are near, we must make the enemy believe we are far away; when far away, we must make him believe we are near.”</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_yuno_books2">“Treat your men as you would your own beloved sons. And they will follow you into the deepest valley.”</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="jura" saidMarker="binah0" sayingMarker="binah01" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_jura_creepy1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_jura_creepy2">It comes down to the lives I've lead. The first life was spent as a weapon, the second a prisoner, and the third I spent much in a deep sleep. I only recently became truly free.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="revy" saidMarker="binah0" sayingMarker="binah01" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_revy_communism1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_revy_communism2">Perhaps you can expand your taste, then? Sometimes knowledge is just as good a weapon as any firearm.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_revy_communism2">Knowledge is as good a weapon as any firearm. Perhaps you could expand your knowledge.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="okino" saidMarker="binah_strippoker1a" sayingMarker="binah_strippoker2a" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_okino_strippoker1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_okino_strippoker2">Worry not, it is only natural to judge off of appearances. When I first joined this game, I had thought you a girl, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="okino" saidMarker="binah_work1a" sayingMarker="binah_okino_work2a" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_okino_work1a" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_okino_work2a">At least I get this time to meet new people, and perhaps form some long-lasting bonds.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="okino" saidMarker="binah_work1b" sayingMarker="binah_okino_work2b" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_okino_work1b" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_okino_work2b">We archive all of the texts of the City. My section was the philosophical texts. It allowed me to truly fall in love with literature.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" saidMarker="leon21" sayingMarker="leon22" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_freetime1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png">A proper relationship would be nice, but I am also not against a temporary arrangement. Though, I do not think one disqualifies the other. Were you hoping to check one of those boxes, Leon?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" saidMarker="leon31" sayingMarker="leon32" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_attention1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_leon_attention2">I may as well be out with it. Yes, I did dress up for this. It is a matching set. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="gloria" saidMarker="gloria_binah_thesaurus1" sayingMarker="gloria_binah_thesaurus2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_gloria_thesaurus1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_gloria_thesaurus2">I suppose I simply do not have many ways to connect to others. It is hard to talk about my life without causing others discomfort.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="asuna_yuuki" saidMarker="binah_stage0" sayingMarker="binah_stage0a" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_asuna_hana1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_asuna_hana2">They work alongside the leaders of The City. It is all quite simple really, a well-oiled machine that keeps itself in check. The real power lies in the Corporations.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" saidMarker="Binah_s0_1" sayingMarker="Binah_s0_2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_kaz_fear1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_kaz_fear2">A large amount of stress over many, many years of jobs. What do you do for work?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="dwight" saidMarker="binah_ms1" sayingMarker="binah_s1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_dwight_twilight1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_dwight_twilight2">Intelligence cannot be measured by such limited testing. I don't wish for you to think less of yourself because of me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="mitama" saidMarker="Binah_librarian" sayingMarker="binah_philosophy" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_mitama_librarian1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_mitama_librarian2">How is it possible for anything to be void of meaning. The fact it exists means there is meaning. Questioning the world around you is simply what it means to be human.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="mitama" saidMarker="Binah_haikuflirt" sayingMarker="binah_haikuflirt_cont" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_mitama_haikuflirt1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_mitama_haikuflirt2">I am glad this is not too forward. I cannot help but find you quite attractive. I want to not only explore that beautiful mind of yours, but also your equally beautiful body.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="mitama" saidMarker="Binah_haikuflirt" sayingMarker="binah_haikuflirt_subby" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_mitama_haikuflirtdommy1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_mitama_haikuflirtdommy2">What a good girl you are, Mitama. Keep behaving, and I will ensure you feel pleasure beyond pleasure.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuno_uno" sayingMarker="yuno_binah_tea1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_yuno_tea1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_yuno_tea2">I did not come up with the name, but I am curious as to what the acronym means to you.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_yuno_tea2">Oh, how come? I cannot think of any issues with STD.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_yuno_tea2">I don't quite understand, is there an issue with STD?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" saidMarker="leon12" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_tea1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_leon_tea2">Apologies, Leon, I was waxing poetic again. I have been told the ways I speak at times can cause discontent in others.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <condition role="opp" character="meia" sayingMarker="binah01" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_meia_lcorp1" />
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_meia_lcorp2">Indeed, so you can imagine the fallout when L-Corp collapsed.</state>
                <state img="#-stripping.png" marker="binah_meia_lcorp2">Yes, so imagine the fallout when that corporation collapsed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Next are my shoes. I hear some are into this sort of thing, yes? I do not judge.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Next is my jacket, another indicator of the Arbiter. This jacket may not look it, but it can stop any bullet, and almost any blade.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">My cloak, the shroud of darkness in which the Arbiter comes. If one is sent after you, it will be a painful end.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Congratulations, now you may gaze upon much more of my flesh. I will not go down easily, however.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Down to my underwear. If one wished me dead, this would likely be the only chance they'd have with a probability above 10%. None of you are actually assassins, are you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">I try not to even bare an inch of skin that I cannot defend. To think now I am exposing my entire chest before a perfect stranger.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-stripping.png">Well, there is no way around it. With this, I lay bared before you. Rejoice.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="stripped">
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_daskapital" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" marker="binah_leon_daskapital2">Seizing your throat for such a bold claim is one idea. Though, I believe I'd rather grasp your heart.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" stage="7-9" sayingMarker="leon03*" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_daskapital" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png" marker="binah_leon_daskapitalALT">At first I had thought of grasping your throat for such a bold statement, however I see something else I'd rather hold in my hands currently.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" stage="0-6" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_mobydick" />
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_leon_mobydick2">Comparison to a whale is certainly one way to raise my expectations, Leon.  However, you have certainly caught my attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" stage="7-9" sayingMarker="leon03*" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_mobydick" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png" marker="binah_leon_mobydickALT">Whale may be slightly generous, Leon. But I have found something worth pursuing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="ringo_ando" saidMarker="binah_arbiter" sayingMarker="binah_arbiter2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="re_binah_arbiter" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="re_binah_arbiter2">You need not be afraid of me, my child. That was in my past, nowadays I am little more than a librarian.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" saidMarker="leon12" sayingMarker="leon13" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_tea2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_leon_tea3">Hmm, no. There is such a thing as too much agony. I wish to bring out the flavor of the tea, not torture it. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" saidMarker="leon32" sayingMarker="leon33" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_attention2" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_leon_attention3">Make me pant? Darling, I am no common dog. If anything, you will be the one in a collar.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="jura" saidMarker="binah01" sayingMarker="binah1s" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_jura_creepy2" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_jura_creepy3">Simply put, I am a librarian. I collect and archive books - philosophical texts mostly.  It helped me learn a lot about myself, and my coming here was also part of that journey of learning myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="meia" saidMarker="binah01" sayingMarker="binah1s" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_meia_lcorp2" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_meia_lcorp3">Many other Wings fell afterward. R Corp, W Corp, T Corp...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="revy" saidMarker="binah01" sayingMarker="binah1s" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_revy_communism2" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_revy_communism3">I suppose that is fair. &lt;i&gt;(How is she worse than Gebura?)&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon03" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_leon_thestand" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_leon_thestand2">Yes, I suppose it can be a little bleak. Perhaps you'd be more open to romance? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <condition role="opp" character="ringo_ando" saidMarker="binah_coatstrip" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="re_binah_coatstrip" font-size="small">Indeed, my child, it would be heavy if it were made with metal. However, the Tailors strange forms allow them to create incredibly powerful silk out of the victims they consume. Would you like me to bring you some fine silk?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <condition role="opp" character="leon" sayingMarker="leon43" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_leon_tease3">Enough to tease you, but not enough to satisfy. Yes, I do like working you up. Work hard enough, and you will earn your prize.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Excellent, you have done well. What memories will we all yield soon?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-haughty.png">My arms do not inspire anything like lust, do they? I have yet to find one who finds arousal in arms.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Ah, it feels good to be able to relax...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I look much less intimidating now, yes?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">My cloak alone inspires fear. I hope I inspire more comfort, now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Do you like what you see, my dear? Go ahead, look. I want you to enjoy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Yes, I did dress up specially for this occasion. If I am to be brought down to my underwear, I may as well wear something attractive.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Feeling your gaze upon me is awakening long-suppressed emotions.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_strip">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_jin_fixer1">You described yourself as an Agent, are you by chance a Fixer? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Now now, be a good boy for me, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I hope you don't wish for me to avert my gaze. I want to see you in your totality.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">My delicious tea, and a show. Make it good for me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What will you be taking off for us this time, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">~name~ was the weakest among us, or at least their hand was.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Don't be ashamed, it was only a matter of time for you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You knew you would need to do this, ~name~, didn't you?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">So now it is ~name~'s turn, hmm? Go on, then.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I'm already so exposed, so surely this isn't a problem for you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I've managed to get this far. So can you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Well, at least I'm still in the game.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It would appear I'm still in the game for a while. Thank you, ~name~, for losing this round.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You are up it seems, ~name~. Go on, do not delay.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Much better you than me, ~name~. Now do put on a good show, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Excellent, I am glad you were the one who lost.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Hah, that is quite good. I was worried I would need to strip again.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Delicious, what a wonderful cup of tea. ~name~ putting on a show for me will be even sweeter.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Were you hoping it would be me, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now for ~name~ to strip for me, how delightful.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Put on a show for me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Please make it good, ~name~, I do not wish to- &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt; -lose my composure.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, bring yourself- &lt;i&gt;ngh&lt;/i&gt; -even closer to where I sit.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Good, I was hoping to see you strip more, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good boy, ~name~. Take it off for me. Take it- &lt;i&gt;ngh&lt;/i&gt; -off.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I would love to break you down, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Boys like you are meant to be subservient.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Good boy - good boy. Keep this up, and I might keep you as a pet.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Surprised you are still in the game, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Surely you cannot be getting flustered now, can you?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Go ahead, it is your time to shine.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Be a good boy, ~name~. Strip for me.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I want to make you mine, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_strip">
            <case stage="0" oneShotId="19">
                <condition role="target" character="aella" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_aella_tailor1">Aella, I am curious of something. Does your armor not feel overly bulky? I suppose your world does not have Tailors.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_aella_tailor1">Such bulky armor is quite unsightly, and inefficient. Though, I suppose not everyone has access to Tailors.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_aella_tailor1">Plate armor, how rustic. It has a nice aesthetic, but I feel clothing made from a Tailor would be much better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_amy_genres1">What genre do you like most, Amy? You strike me as a horror fan, though I can also see you enjoying Gothic romance.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_amy_genres1">Are you into horror novels, Amy? Gothic romance, perhaps?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_amy_genres1">I don't know if I have a favorite genre. How about you, Amy? You strike me as a woman who enjoys horror or Gothic romance.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Well, ~name~? Do not keep us waiting.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It appears ~name~ is to strip; I will have my eyes on you, my dearest.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">A hot cup of tea, and a beautiful woman. What more is needed in life?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Go on, do not be shy, my dear.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It is alright; I do not bite. I mark my property in much more elegant ways.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am glad it was you and not me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">It seems the loser for this round was ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Too bad, ~name~. You must strip next.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I am sure you wished it was me, but you are the one who failed, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Oh, you lost, did you? Then get on with stripping, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Fantastic, I don't need to strip, &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; I get to watch ~name~ strip. Two wins.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Good girl. Go on and take it off for me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">~name~, you have quite a lovely throat. I'd love to put a collar around it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I am already so exposed, so come join me. Don't you wish to experience bliss together, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I already got this far, surely you needn't kick up a fuss, child.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Come, do not disappoint me. I am stripped nude already, standing before you like this.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Don't pussyfoot around, ~name~, we needn't pretend you do not want to join me.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">At least I can enjoy your body as much as you are enjoying mine, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Be a good girl. Come here, and let me strip you instead.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I'm certainly exposed, so why waste time feeling shy?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">You can feast your eyes on me, and become a feast for my eyes. A fair trade, no?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Put on a lovely show for me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I will be using you for my inspiration, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~, you're so beautiful. Such a beautiful girl.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Good girl, &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt;, good girl. Be a good girl for me.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I would love to make a mewling mess of you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">To keep you as a pet would be the ultimate prize.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Go ahead, ~name~, please don't be shy, darling. I mean, just take a look at me.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Even if I already finished, I can't help but enjoy this.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, dearest? What will you be removing for us?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">So beautiful, ~name~. The things I would do to you given the chance...</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">What an adorable pet you'd make, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="tie">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A tie, is it? How very quaint. </state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition status="naked" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I suppose you have no choice but to sacrifice sight for one more chance.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I can see why you saved your glasses; I can only imagine you must be impaired now without them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition status="naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Why did you wait this long before removing your ~clothing.generic~? ~clothing.ifPlural(Do|Does)~ ~clothing.ifPlural(they|it)~ hold some special sentimentality?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">It's interesting that you saved your ~clothing.generic~ for so late in the game.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You've already bared it all. Why take your ~clothing.generic~ off now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Glasses, hm? I hope you did not need those, my child.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I do hope those were not a necessity for you...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Let us hope those do not hinder your ability to play such a game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="weapon" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" oneShotId="119">So you came armed then? Interesting. I suppose I did as well, considering I am a weapon.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="118">And just what did &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; bring a weapon for, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="123">A weapon, ~name~? Just what were you so afraid of, my child?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="gloves" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png">It would seem the gloves are coming off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">The game is still warming up, after all, small items are to be expected.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Yes, I suppose starting with miniscule items is a surefire strategy to employ.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Perhaps I should  have brought some smaller items myself...</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">It is still early, I am not going to kick up fuss about someone preserving their decency a little longer.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I don't mind you delaying the inevitable, the hunt is my favorite part.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">So you are removing your ~clothing~  now?  No fuss, you are still not going to escape me.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">It is hardly a concern to me. Go ahead, take off your ~clothing~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-anger.png">Are you serious? I'm like this and you're only taking off your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Dammit, you still had your ~clothing~ remaining? Lucky bastard.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Fine then, I'll just need to beat you again, and again after that.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Bloody hell, fine. Go ahead, ~name~. Take off your ~clothing~ that you still somehow had left.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'm this undressed, yet you still have your ~clothing~ to take off?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Really? You were still wearing your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh, to think you would go for your ~clothing~ when I'm here in my underwear.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Was I doing that poorly?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I know it is a competition, but can you consider something better than your ~clothing~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Dammit, ~name~, I need more than just your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">I cannot believe you still had your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Such a damned tease, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">You have a woman before you, desperately trying to get off. Yet you remain a coward.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Is that all you can offer me? Pathetic.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-haughty.png">You still &lt;i&gt;had&lt;/i&gt; your ~clothing~ on? Amazing.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">I cannot believe you still had that.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Well, let us continue then.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Shall we begin the next round, then?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now that is out of the way, let us resume.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Do any of you drink tea?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" oneShotId="1" marker="BlackTeaOnly">Black tea is perhaps the only beverage I have imbibed for the last millennium. I see not reason to expand my horizons.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Good, you are now closer to your defeat. I await it with great anticipation, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This is but the first note in the symphony of your defeat.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Dealer, please hand out the next cards.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You will not last for long, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I suppose its smart to bring many small items, but I'm still annoyed.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I apologize for losing my temper, you must understand how frustrating it is to be in my position right now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Whatever, this is fine. I'll just need to beat you again.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Fine, go ahead and play safe for now. You will be backed into a corner soon enough.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Whatever, next round.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Bring on the next round. You won't stay so safe for long.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-anger.png">Just- dammit, just move on already.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Just move on, I need better inspiration.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Well, I suppose you beat me even worse than I thought.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I can hardly blame you for playing well, now, can I?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I may need to study this game more before I return.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_accessory">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition status="naked" role="target" />
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I suppose you have no choice but to sacrifice sight for one more chance.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I can see why you saved your glasses; I can only imagine you must be impaired now without them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition status="naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Why did you wait this long before removing your ~clothing.generic~? ~clothing.ifPlural(Do|Does)~ ~clothing.ifPlural(they|it)~ hold some special sentimentality?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">It's interesting that you saved your ~clothing.generic~ for so late in the game.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You've already bared it all. Why take your ~clothing.generic~ off now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="weapon" />
                <state img="#-smug.png">So you came armed then? Interesting. I suppose I did as well though, considering I am a weapon.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">And just what did &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; bring a weapon for, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="glasses" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Glasses, hm? I hope you did not need those, my child.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I do hope those were not a necessity for you...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Let us hope those do not hinder your ability to play such a game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~clothing.generic~" value="gloves" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png">It would seem the gloves are coming off.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am a patient woman; I will wait eons for you if I must.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I can wait, ~name~, but do not make me wait too long.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">It only makes sense to start off small, no?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">...Hm? My apologies, I was lost in thoughts.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Delicious...</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">What sort of tea do you prefer, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Maybe I should have dressed up more...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What will you take off next, I wonder?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Ugh, I didn't realize you even still had your ~clothing~, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Well, it is a smart idea to remove your ~clothing~ at this time, but it still frustrates me.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Sure sure, go ahead and take off your ~clothing~. I'll punish you later.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">She still had that left? Bloody hell...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It is alright, ~name~. I'll forgive you for taking off such a small item this time.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I'm in my underwear, and yet you are only removing your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Well, I don't blame you for removing your ~clothing~, but I wish it was more exciting.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">You were still wearing your ~clothing~ while I was already down to my underwear?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I suppose I cannot be mad at you, ~name~. Removing your ~clothing~ is most optimal in this game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">~name~, darling, can you please choose something more exciting?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Something so small... I cannot fault you, but I can be unhappy.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I was hoping you'd help me cross the threshold, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I was hoping to see more, is all.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Well, I suppose you did beat me...</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">You must be proud of yourself, ~name~. I know &lt;i&gt;I&lt;/i&gt; am proud of you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_accessory">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="FaustQuote">“A man sees in the world what he carries in his heart.”</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">With the loss of your ~clothing~, you must resort to something more exciting next round.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good, let us get going to the next round then.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I do not like my tea sweetened at all. I do, however, like my women sweet. Do keep such in mind, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" oneShotId="7" marker="TeaFFDom">I like my women the way I like my tea, held tight in my grasp and under my full control.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder what will be taken off next...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">At least it's out of the way now. Please remove something better next time, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Goodness, I am not doing well. Okay, next round. I got this.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Alright, well, I can last a few more rounds.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">So be it, complaining will not change the outcome.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, let us not delay the next game.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I forgive you, ~name~, even if I expect you to bare more of yourself later. Okay?</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I hope you lose more...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I guess we shouldn't fret about it. Let us begin the next round.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">That is fine, just keep going.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I do hope you lose more, following this.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Still, I do hope to witness your fall.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I see, so you chose your ~clothing~ next, then?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, take it off. Take another step towards oblivion.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good boy, take your ~clothing~ off for me, okay? </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How does it feel to be made to remove your ~clothing~ now?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">My tea tastes all the sweeter due to the loss of your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Good, good, keep up the good work ~name~. You are making me quite happy, dear.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="WutheringHeightsQuote">“If he loved with all the powers of his puny being, he couldn't love as much in eighty years as I could in a day.”</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Alright, not me this round. It's ~name~'s turn, so I'm safe a round.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Okay, take off your ~clothing~. This is buying me time.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I can outlast them, I'm sure...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Alright, I don't mind you stripping your ~clothing~ this round, ~name~. I just don't want to lose myself.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not too bad, one step closer to nudity.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, at least your ~clothing~ will no longer remain active in the game, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">So you're choosing to remove your ~clothing~ then? Not a problem. Next will be more, yes?</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Eh, I can't complain much. It makes sense to take off your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">First your ~clothing~, next your dignity.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Get on with it, take off your ~clothing~ already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Your ~clothing~ inspires very little lust in me, my dear.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">It's something, at the least. Not great when I am attempting to get off.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, I suppose that isn't an issue. I wish it was something more than just your ~clothing~, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">So next will be your ~clothing~, correct?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Next comes your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="50" marker="TailorFleshSuit">This may be odd to divulge here, but did you know that, well. Your ~clothing~ would have been made by Tailors, likely out of human flesh. Goes to show how different our worlds are.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now that you are without you ~clothing~, we can continue.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good, now we can begin the next act in this play.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">And the curtains close for your ~clothing~, exit stage right.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I like you more without your ~clothing~ anyways, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good, how does it feel to be without your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What comes next in our tale, I wonder?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Have you begun to regret playing against me now? I will hold no ire if you have, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="MobyDickQuote">“I know not all that may be coming, but be it what it will, I'll go to it laughing.”</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Okay, it's out of the way. Next round, I can't lose here.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm not ready to lose, so let's get going to the next round.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Come, let's get moving. I'm tired of being this close to defeat, so I will have to demolish you all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Now with ~name~'s ~clothing~ discarded, we can continue the game.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">I hope you lose again, both to protect myself and so you can take off something more interesting.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">At least it's out of the way. Next time you won't be able to hide behind your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Well, let us begin the next round. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Out of the way now, let's keep- &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt; -going.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">Whatever, next round. &lt;i&gt;Hah&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">That's not a problem, this is alright. Let's go to the next round.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I wonder who will lose next.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This game is much more fun to watch from the outside, frankly.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png">Hmm, hmm, hmm.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_minor">
            <case stage="0-7 9" id="2">
                <condition role="target" character="cammy_white" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_cammy_view2">Good girl, giving me quite the nice view there. Are you even aware of the view you are giving?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good, rid yourself of your ~clothing~ this round, and next we move to something better.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good girl, take off your  ~clothing~ for me.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="StepOnMeFemDom">Oh, how lovely you will look squirming beneath my shoe... </state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Your defeat this round brings me a smile. I wonder what your defeat in this game will bring me?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Oh, you did look good in your ~clothing~, however I find you being rid of such will be even more beautiful.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">~name~, I do love how you look removing your clothing before me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good, continue to show you are inferior to me. I enjoy such reminders.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Excellent, I do enjoy the view as you take off your ~clothing~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I don't mind, I'm still in the game at least.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Go ahead, strip your ~clothing~. At least I'm still in the game.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">At least you're cute, and I'm still in the game. That's fine.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Really? Whatever, just take off your ~clothing~ already.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't worry, I am sure nobody will take your adorable ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, ~name~, get on with it.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">It is time for ~name~ to strip. How thankful I am for this.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Do not be shy, ~name~. I want to see you undress posthaste.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Sure,  this round you can remove your ~clothing~. But next round? We shall see.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">This is alright, it gets me a step closer to seeing your beauty, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You are so beautiful, ~name~, please take it off for me.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">To think I was so far behind you, ~name~. I thought I'd have done much better.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I am always quite happy to watch you strip, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Thank goodness, I was hoping it'd be you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Now it is your turn, shed your ~clothing~ at once.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_minor">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Excellent, now we can progress to the next round.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">I only hope you continue to lose, ~name~. I do not mean that out of cruelty, but of desire.</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" marker="CrimeAndPunishmentQuote">“To go wrong in one's own way is better than to go right in someone else's.”</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I think I quite enjoy this game. I know I quite enjoy the sight of your slowly more exposed state, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I do not mean to be cruel, but I simply enjoy it when you lose.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Do I intimidate you, ~name~? I hope I do.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">A cup of black tea to warm my damned soul, and perhaps ~name~ can return with me to warm my bed?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Okay, let's keep going. </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I just need to avoid losing, more than anything.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Alright, it's out of the way. Let's move on, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Well, here comes the next round. I hope I can stay in.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">A shame, your ~clothing~ looked quite cute on you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good girl, doesn't it feel better now without your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I still think you look adorable, ~name~, even without your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I am drinking in what is now exposed to me, like a fine cup of tea.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Not too bad, is it ~name~? Do you feel freer than you did earlier?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I am thankful that is out of the way now, shall we continue?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good, I'm glad it is out of the way.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Shall we- &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt; -continue?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">There, don't you feel much better without your ~clothing~?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I mean no offense, but I am cheering for your downfall. I wish to watch you strip more, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I must admit, your ~clothing.ifPlural(are|is)~ quite cute.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">~name~, I am excited to see what you show off my dear.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Go ahead, take off your ~clothing~ for me. I am quite excited.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Put on a good show, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I think a few marks on that body will do you some good.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good boy, take it off for me now, okay? Nice and slow.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">~name~, I must confess something. You look good, all pathetic and stripping down.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, I guess I can still enjoy this...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Even in my position, I'll still be enjoying this, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, seeing ~name~ take off his ~clothing~ is enjoyable, regardless of my own state.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Thank you, ~name~. For both losing this round instead of me, and for putting on a show.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Excellent, now you must come down to my level.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Haha, it seems ~name~ is coming down to my level now.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good, you cannot remain dressed for much longer.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good boy, now take your ~clothing~ off for me, and join me in near nudity.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">No delays, ~name~, rid yourself of your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Fantastic, &lt;i&gt;gah&lt;/i&gt;, this will help a lot.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You're excited, aren't you? &lt;i&gt;Damn&lt;/i&gt;, I am sure you want me to look, yes? Don't worry, I will.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">It seems you are far from safe, now, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">How lovely, your ~clothing.ifPlural(are|s)~ leaving your body.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How nice to watch you fall another round, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good boy, ~name~. You made me very happy just now.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Seeing so much of you become exposed adds unexpected sweetness to my tea.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How does it feel to be so exposed, while I stand here basically fully clothed?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Good, continue stripping down before me.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I hope you are worried, ~name~. I hope you realize your position.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Sitting in the same room as a wolf, and slowly covering yourself in scraps of meat, is never a smart idea. That is what you are doing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good, some eye candy and another chance.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Excellent, I'm still in and I get a good view.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Brilliant, I stay in another round and I get something nice to look at.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, this makes me feel &lt;i&gt; much&lt;/i&gt; better, thank you ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">With your ~clothing~ out of the way, little is left to the imagination.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hah, now you are closer to being out before me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Excellent, now I am less likely to be naked early.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">This is good for me, in more ways than one. I stay decent longer, and I get to eye your form.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Good, I am sure everyone here is much happier now that you are free of your ~clothing~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Gods above, ~name~, I love what I am seeing.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Next round, please, I want even more of your body exposed to me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Fantastic, I am very happy to see you without your ~clothing~. What will you take off next round, I wonder.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Seeing you lose your ~clothing~ ~clothing.ifPlural(add|adds)~ some sweetness to my tea.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removing_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Good, my dearest  ~name~. Shed your ~clothing~ for me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How wonderful, my darling. Be a good girl and take it all off for me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You are so very beautiful, ~name~. I wish to learn every inch of your body and mind.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Pushed so far, ~name~. How truly pathetic.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">A girl like you certainly deserves to be made into a pet.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Good work, my dearest. Behave and you shall be rewarded.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I may be in a bad state, but I'd still like to get a look at you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I may be in dire straits, but a good look at ~name~'s body will still sweeten my mood.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You taking off your ~clothing~ certainly makes me feel better about my state, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Might as well take my mind off my impending defeat by watching ~name~ remove her ~clothing~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good, I can't wait for you to expose your underwear for me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, dearest ~name~. Take off your ~clothing~ for me, now.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm rather excited to see what you have under that ~clothing~, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Well, this buys me another round. It also allows me a chance to see more of ~name~. I fail to see a downside.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Ah, so it is you now my adorable little ~name~. Go on, do not be shy. Please, show me your all.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">You are up next, ~name~? Well, don't delay. Give us all a good show, my sweet.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Be a good girl, ~name~. Put on a good show for me, and keep your eyes on me as you do. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I only wish this was happening earlier.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A shame you couldn't be removing your ~clothing~ a few minutes earlier.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">A shame, ~name~, I wanted to use you removing your ~clothing~ as inspiration.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_removed_major">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">How does it feel to be so close to nudity, yet I am standing here decent enough to go out to the shops. Is it humiliating, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Oh, how I want to feel you in my lap.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">What a beautiful woman you are, ~name~. I wish to see so much more, but I suppose I must be patient.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Perhaps I should play this game with the other librarians.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">A collar and a leash would really complete this look, ~name~. Don't you agree?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Truly wonderful, truly beautiful. Oh how I missed the pleasure of the flesh.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I can almost forget the fact I'm a moment away from total humiliation.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You look amazing, ~name~. Perhaps you can lose the next round too, for me?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good girl, such a wonderful sight for me. Can you lose the next for me, as well?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Maybe I can still make this all work.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I must say, I am enjoying this view so far.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now this is what I came here for. I cannot wait for you to lose further.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I hope you lose again soon, my dearest ~name~. I yearn to see more of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-flirty.png">That is wonderful, ~name~. Good girl, now lose the next round for me.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah&lt;/i&gt;, goodness. That is very good, ~name~. So very, very good.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">This will surely help, thank you. I hope you don't mind how closely I am watching you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">What I see still brings a smile to my face.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Well, I can still enjoy the view.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Still, you are far too beautiful to be mad at, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">A man taking off his ~clothing~ is such a mundane thing, yet still feels like such a thrill.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, ~name~, reveal to me your flesh. Expose to me your bare chest.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Exposing your chest to someone where I'm from is a major risk. I could take your heart, and I am not waxing poetic when I say that.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">How tantalizing. Do not keep me waiting, I am so very excited to see this.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good boy, ~name~, take your ~clothing~ off for me.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">The thoughts entering my mind at this time. I hunger for you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, now another joins me on the brink.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">So, ~name~, now you must bare your chest to the world.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Best not delay, ~name~, let us see your body.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm already topless, so you may as well join us, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="24">It is odd, is it not? Your chest is considered to be less provocative than mine. It is curious, because both the male and female body can bring about lustful thoughts.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">At least you will be showing more skin than I, and I am excited to see said skin.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Despite me being in my underwear, you are still going to be stripping more. I am more than happy with this.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Go ahead, ~name~, take off your ~clothing~ and show us all what you are hiding. I wish to gaze upon your body.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Do not delay, ~name~, please. I wish to see what you've been hiding from me.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah, hah, nngh!&lt;/i&gt; Pleasure beyond pleasure, please show me more.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hardly fair of you to be shy &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;. Take off your ~clothing~, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">So now you will be baring your chest, ~name~. I can't wait to see what you have to offer.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Now&lt;/i&gt; you take off your ~clothing~? Where were you when I was masturbating?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Would you complain if I offered to pepper your body in bite marks, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="athletic" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now that is a good sight. The things I'd do to you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">May I run my hands up and down your body, ~name~? I want to treat all of my senses to this display.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">My, I might just fall for a sight like that.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="muscular" role="target" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh those arms, to be wrapped up in them and lay my head against your chest. Oh I feel like a girl again.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Even with a body as crafted as that, you do know I will be on top.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="chubby" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do not be ashamed of your physique, I will still gladly keep you as my pet.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Still incredibly handsome, ~name~. Do not worry.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good boy, I would love to mark you up enough so any others know you belong to me.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">So lovely, this game was an incredibly good idea.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">How does it feel, ~name~? You are topless, and I'm decent enough to go into my workplace.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not a bad look at all, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You look rather good, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm hardly about to complain about this, ~name~, my current predicament aside.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">How does it feel, ~name~, joining me in baring our chests.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now that is not bad at all...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am quite pleased with what I am seeing now.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good, ~name~ is shirtless now. I am pleased by this.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good boy, taking your top off for me so obediently. I know it was due to the games rules, but I know you'd do it if I ordered anyway.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Perfect, this is what I needed. You are such a handsome boy, ~name~. Such a good, handsome boy.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">So good, &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt;, this will do more than suffice. You're getting closer to me now, my dear.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Do you not feel freer, my dear ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">The amount of marks I could leave on you. Bites, scratches, bruises. Would you enjoy that, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Dammit, how am I to resist taking you here and now?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-smug.png">Now that is quite the sight to take in...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I suppose late is better than never.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, I wonder what will come next.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">The anticipation is killing me, I wonder if ~name~ is hard already.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Do not be shy now. Be sure to show off for me, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Please do not disappoint me, ~name~. I want to see you in your totality.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I cannot wait to see it, I suppose I've grown quite excited...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Alright, not only am I still in it, but you're showing me something delightful soon too~</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Well, I may be on the brink, but now you are too.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">This is a good distraction from my own position. I can't wait to see you reveal yourself to me.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I wonder if you're already aroused by the sight of me like this.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">At least ~name~ will have to pull his cock out next. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, ~name~, remove your ~clothing~. At least I'm only in my underwear.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">At least I can be thankful for ~name~ getting his most intimate parts exposed before myself.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Are you to be a good boy, showing me just how hard you have gotten thus far?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Now this is sure to be great for me.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I wonder if you are hard already, ~name~. I am sitting here, touching myself right before you.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">We mustn't break the rules of this place, so you must resist coming and taking me here and now. Can you resist such, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">It may be a little late, but I am not about to complain.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_small_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Not a lot to work with, ~name~. It's okay, I will be penetrating you if we were to ever sleep together.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">That's all you have for me, hmm? I can still make it work.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">I had high expectations, ~name~. I thought you could at least perform.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Don't worry ~name~, it's quite alright. I'll just be the one penetrating you, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-bored.png">Not a worry, you won't be the one penetrating me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You hardly need a large member when I'm the one penetrating you.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You won't need to use that with me, I'll be on top, and inside of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't worry, ~name~. If we are to bed, I will not be the one being penetrated.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I don't much care how endowed a man is, I am rarely the one being penetrated.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Don't worry, ~name~, the apparatus I like to use on my partners is twice the size of you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">It is okay, size matters not when you become my toy.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Not a lot to offer, I think my fingers will suffice.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">You're still adorable, dear, just not a lot to please me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_medium_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-smug.png">You are exposing your member now, meanwhile I have barely shown any skin. How shameful, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Seeing you so vulnerable awakens the predator inside of me. The hunger for a hunt, and a thirst for you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am certainly not about to complain.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">So exposed, I do hope you are not too shy. I don't want you to cover up after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not bad, I'm feeling quite excited by all of this.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm exposed, you're exposed. Do you have any plans later, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I suppose I'm not that fussed, knowing you'll be thinking of me when you have to masturbate.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">So this is your cock, ~name~? Soon you will be stroking it for me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="26">It is interesting. There are so many words to describe a penis. Cock, dick, knob, rod, member. I don't quite like the sound of any of them, though.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now you've revealed yourself to me. Are you afraid? Aroused? A little nervous? Maybe you wanted an excuse to get naked for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Oh how I wish you could come here and sit upon my pillar. I would love to- &lt;i&gt;ngh&lt;/i&gt; -to ride you, until you break.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Well hello there, it appears your little friend is quite happy to see me.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I indeed hope I'll get to see you jerk yourself to completion.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_large_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Goodness, is that natural or did you undergo some body modifications?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">That is quite large, I wonder how it would feel...</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Goodness, you must struggle to find sexual partners who can handle that. I believe I would be able to, ~name~. If you are in the market for one.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Goodness that thing is gargantuan. </state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I feel bad for any woman you have managed to bed. </state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">That could be a weapon in the right hands.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Goodness, that is quite sizable.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do you struggle to find partners who can take that?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">That is just about the largest dick I have ever seen.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Goodness, that is massive. I can only- &lt;i&gt;haaah&lt;/i&gt; -imagine how that would feel inside of me.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Gods... I want to feel that.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I do not think I could fit that inside of me, but I have more ways to please a man than with my slit.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I must say, I am excited to see what you can offer, dear.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Are you alright with exposing yourself to me? I may take your heart, and I do not mean in the metaphorical sense.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Do not be shy, ~name~. It isn't the first time someone has stripped down for me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Please do put on a show for me, my dear. I can get bored easily.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How does it feel, ~name~? You'll be exposing your chest to me, yet I am still nearly fully clothed.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">~name~, this surely makes it all worth it. Join me, dear.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, dear, don't be shy. I've already bared so much, so surely you can bare yourself just the same.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm already standing here, exposed as I am, so you can hardly act shy now, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It appears ~name~ will be exposing her breasts, next. I can't wait to see them, darling.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, ~name~? You aren't going to delay it too much, will you?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, give us a good show ~name~. I've been waiting to see this all game.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Good, please expose to me your beautiful body. I wish for nothing more than to see every inch of your body, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Hah, you will be so much closer to joining me. Maybe you can come sit in my lap as we play.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I am so thankful it is your turn, ~name~. I truly wish to gaze upon your wonderful frame.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Go ahead,  please, I need to see what you can offer me. Gods, I want you. I really, really want you.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_small_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't worry ~name~, I find small chests quite attractive. </state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Much smaller than myself, not that you can tell due to the fact I've hardly had to strip.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I hear smaller chests are more sensitive. Would you like to put this theory into practice, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">The size of your breasts matter not, I can make you melt no matter their size. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">What an adorable chest you have, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do not worry, ~name~, you look wonderful.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if it is true that smaller chests are more sensitive. May I test this theory, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">How wonderfully adorable, don't feel jealous. All breasts are wonderful, no matter the size.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't feel the need to compare our sizes, you're beautiful regardless, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do not feel less adequate compared to me, I personally like your chest more, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Goodness, your chest is so cute, ~name~. I always preferred a smaller partner.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">What an adorable pet you would make, ~name~. What an adorable girl you are.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I always loved smaller breasts, so sensitive and adorable. </state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;Fuck&lt;/i&gt;, that throat of yours was made to bear a collar.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_medium_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I am not the type to act foolish at the sight of breasts, but I do enjoy them greatly.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">A good, full pair of breasts. I can imagine they would feel good to grasp, and perhaps bite too?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">You have a lovely pair of breasts, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Do you feel embarrassed, ~name~? The open air on your chest, the many eyes on your body. Are you feeling shame, or are you feeling arousal?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm relieved you had to show your chest before I did.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I must say, you look wonderful with your breasts on display.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Goodness, I won't forget the look of your chest for awhile, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="28">There are so many names for a woman's chest. Breasts, boobs, tits, bosoms, melons. Not a big fan of most of them, though breasts suffice I suppose.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Between ~name~ and I, who's chest do you prefer, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, darling, both of us have our chest exposed. How is it making you feel?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Thankfully you are not alone in baring your chest, ~name~, for I too am at this state.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Oh dear, I would absolutely love to explore your body, ~name~. What a wonderful chest you have.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Not dissimilar to mine own, though I personally always wished for it to be a bit smaller.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I feel so wet, my darling. The things you do to me, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_large_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="boob_envy" role="other" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="349">Be careful not to show off too much, ~name~. Someone might get jealous.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="350">I am sure &lt;i&gt;someone&lt;/i&gt; is feeling jealous now.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It seems you are quite well endowed, ~name~. I personally prefer smaller, but I can still appreciate yours my dear.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">That must hurt your back. Would you like a massage? I know someone who's very good at them.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Most men seek out large breasts in a partner as it shows a mature, motherly figure. As I am not looking for children, I am not swayed by this. Though I like you for my own reasons, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Reminds me of Angela, it was odd just how top heavy she was. But then again, I guess he would make Angela to fit his own preferences...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Goodness, your chest is quite large. Does it cause any back pain?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Dear, it may be a cliche line... But do you need someone to help hold those for you?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">So large, I wonder if those cause more positive or more negative attention.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Goodness, I feel a little inadequate next to you, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">Hmm, I suppose I don't look as attractive next to you, depending on if ~player~ prefers larger breasts.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I can only imagine that causes more trouble than not, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-thinking.png">So large, I wonder if there is any benefit to breasts of that size. Barring the aesthetic ones, of course- &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt; -damn. So good.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="48">I can think of many &lt;i&gt;vulgar&lt;/i&gt; things to say about you, ~name~. Cow comes to mind, but that I only know from books. Apparently cows were kept for their milk, and since women lactate, then perhaps you are only kept around for your breasts? Apologies, that was a vulgar tangent. I am so lost in my own thoughts.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I would rather a smaller chest. A much cuter look, and less back pain.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_chest_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="huge_breasts" role="target" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Surely those cannot be real...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Those are simply too much...</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_will_be_visible">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">I wonder just how wet you are, with so many eyes on you. Are you shy, or are you aroused beyond description, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'm starting to suspect ~name~ might be getting a rush out of stripping for us all.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You look good, stripping down your ~clothing~. Thankfully I won't be reduced to such a state anytime soon.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Revealing your most intimate parts in front of us all. Are you embarrassed, ~name~? Aroused, perhaps? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You are moments from showing off your most intimate spot. Do not be too intimidated, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, ~name~, expose yourself to me. I promise I'll appreciate the view.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Excellent, expose yourself to me. I wish to see your all.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">At least I'm not revealing my pussy right now, not like ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now you shall bare your forbidden fruit, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, at least I have something to enjoy for my misfortune.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Goodness, I wonder how wet you must be at this point.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Good girl, bare yourself to me. Bare yourself in your all to me, my darling.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Are you as wet as I am? Is this scenario breeding many pleasurable thoughts in that adorable little head of yours?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I was waiting for this, I must confess. I need you, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_crotch_is_visible">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="shaved" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">I must confess, I do not often see women who bother to shave so much outside of the Wings.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">To have the time to shave yourself there fully generally implies having a life of luxury, at least where I come from.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">The only people I know who shave so often are wealthy enough to have free time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition filter="hairy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">Many people I know do not shave at all, due to having little time for themselves. I prefer to trim a little to stay neat, myself.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Generally people at home do not shave their body much, hard to worry about appearance when you are more focused on simple survival.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9" oneShotId="27">
                <condition filter="heart_pubes" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Aww, so adorable, ~name~. Did you style them that way just for us?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Ah, there it is. Your most intimate area on full display for us now. Fantastic.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I must say, I can feel myself growing aroused at this sight. Even one as myself still yearns for intimate touch after all.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">How unfortunate for you, ~name~, to be reduced so far. I can't help but condescend in this situation, so my apologies.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Many delightful thoughts just rushed through my mind. Pinning you down, placing a vibrating apparatus between your legs... I would love to leave you there for hours, until you are in tears for me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Oh that is very lovely. I wonder just how wet you are already.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good, now you're exposed. Soon, your fingers will be digging into your wet cunt for us all to enjoy.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I wonder, darling, maybe I can taste you? I wouldn't mind eating you out ~name~, if you'd let me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" oneShotId="36">There are many names for a woman's genitalia. Vagina, pussy, cunt, twat, slit, box... Not a fan of them, honestly.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">If you are enjoying my own body, than allow me to enjoy yours in turn.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I know your eyes have been on me, so now mine are on you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Are you enjoying the sight of my body? Because I am very much enjoying yours.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">So beautiful, you really are excited looking at me, aren't you?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">My dearest, I want you to join me. I &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; you to join me.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Goodness, I feel my mind going blank. I've never felt so out of control before.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah&lt;/i&gt;, ~name~, I want you. I need you. I will make you mine, do you hear? &lt;i&gt;Mine&lt;/i&gt;, do you hear?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_lost">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="0" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_kaz_wings" />
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_kaz_apology1">Kaz, I do wish to apologize. I spoke quite rudely at the start of the game, making assumptions about your character based on other people I have met.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="dwight" stage="0" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="DwightRunning" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dwight_pursuit1">Why do you find yourself pursued by murderers so often, Dwight?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dwight_pursuit1">Interesting. I must ask: how do you find yourself the would-be victim of murderers so often?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="dunban" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dunban_injury1">Dunban, you've been holding your cards with only one hand. Are you perhaps injured?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dunban_injury1">Is your arm alright, Dunban? You've been handling your cards one-handed.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dunban_injury1">You've been handling your cards with your non-dominant hand, and without the assistance of the other. These observations tell me you must be injured, Dunban.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="anatoly" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_anatoly_pbird1">That companion of yours is quite adorable, Anatoly. I have a little companion as well, though I could not bring it here with me.  It is a little bird who pecks people when they are stressed.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_anatoly_pbird1">I have a small companion as well, back at the library. A small little bird who likes to peck people when they are too stressed out.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_ag_syndicate1">Wait, you do not have a name? Are you so devoted to your Syndicate that you changed your name to simply be a grunt for that organization?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_ag_syndicate1">I have never met someone who would change their name to their Syndicate. You must be quite devoted.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_ag_syndicate1">Perhaps I misjudged your Syndicate. It appears you are willing to go so far as to change your name in its support.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="arueshalae" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_arueshalae_bloodfiend1">Forgive me if it is prying, but are you a Bloodfiend? You share some traits with them.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_arueshalae_bloodfiend1">Arueshalae, I need to ask. Are you a Bloodfiend? The wings certainly bring such to mind.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_arueshalae_bloodfiend1">Are you a Bloodfiend by any chance, Arueshalae? The horns and wings remind me of one of the Bloodfiends we had back in the Library.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="ayano" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_ayano_leave1">If you did not intend to play, you can leave. I am sure nobody will fault you, Ayano.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_ayano_leave1">You do not need to feel obligated to remain here, Ayano. If you wish to go, I will take the fall for you.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_ayano_leave1">It appears you did not intend to join our game, Ayano. If you wish to leave, I am sure everyone will understand.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="barbara" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_barbara_favonius1">I mean no offense. However, most religious groups I have encountered have been manipulative cults. How do you expect me not to be skeptical of your own church?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_bernie_seminar1">If you do not mind my asking, Bernadetta. What exactly is this seminar for?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_bernie_seminar1">I was not informed upon arrival. What exactly is this seminar for, Bernadetta?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_bernie_seminar1">Bernadetta, may I ask what this seminar is for? You seem to know, and I was not informed when I arrived.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_blake_stories1">You strike me as a woman with many stories, Blake. I can see it in your eyes; a deep sorrow, and a deadly determination.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_blake_stories1">Your eyes carry a lot of untold stories, Blake. A deep sorrow, a deadly determination, and much more. I am curious as to what you hold in your heart.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_brock_rocket1">I need to ask, it has been eating at me for awhile. Why are you using such a destructive and unpredictable weapon? Are you not worried about harming yourself in a fight?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="cagliostro" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_cag_singularity1">You keep talking of alchemy and other fantastic things. Do you have a Singularity, Cagliostro? </state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_cag_singularity1">All this talking of fantastic, magical things. Are you in possession of a Singularity? </state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_cag_singularity1">Do you posses a Singularity, Cagliostro? That is the only explanation for your fantastic ramblings.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_caitlin_experiments1">Not only do you appear wealthy, but you have strange powers. Were you perhaps experimented on by a Wing? It isn't so odd, I was also an experiment.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_caitlin_experiments1">Wings experimenting on people is far from odd. I, myself, am a result of that. Is that why you are so wealthy? Compensation for the experiments?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_caitlin_experiments1">Vast wealth and strange powers. Did you gain those from a Wings experiments? It isn't too uncommon, it happened to me as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_catnoir_kitten1">I am curious, though. What sort of things do you do for work, &lt;i&gt;my kitten&lt;/i&gt;?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_catnoir_kitten1">Well, &lt;i&gt;my kitten&lt;/i&gt;, what do you do for work?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_catnoir_kitten1">I am wondering what you do for work, &lt;i&gt;my kitten&lt;/i&gt;.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="catria" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_catria_pegasus1">Wait, Catria, you mentioned Pegasus. What is that?</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_catria_pegasus1">You mentioned Pegasus earlier, Catria. What are those?</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_catria_pegasus1">Catria, I am curious. You mentioned something that caught my ear. What is a Pegasus.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_caulifla_minimalclothing1">One who wears minimal protection is either incredibly confident or incredibly foolish. Which are you, Caulifla?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_caulifla_minimalclothing1">You are either a prolific fighter or a bumbling fool - dressing in such minimal protection. Which is it, Caulifla?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_caulifla_minimalclothing1">To wear so little indicates either a skillful fighter or an utter fool. I am curious as to which you are, Caulifla.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="chara_dreemurr" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_chara_human1">Chara, I need to ask: Are you... human?</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_chara_human1">Are you truly human, Chara? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="cheryl" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_cheryl_comfort1">I suppose I just want to ask: Are you okay, Cheryl?</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_cheryl_comfort1">Are you okay, Cheryl? I suppose I just wanted to ask. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="chiaki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_chiaki_videogames1">I've not ever really played a video game, Chiaki. What is the draw?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_chiaki_videogames1">What is so enjoyable about video games, Chiaki? I've not ever played them.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="yuelia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_yuelia_transformation1">Is this some sort of strange joke? A talking butterfly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_caulifla_supersaiyan1">Well, are you going to get to stripping? It is in poor taste to stall.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_caulifla_supersaiyan1">Don't stall now, Caulifla. You lost, accept it with grace.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="chihiro" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_fujisaki_araara1">So what is someone as adorable as you doing in a game like this, Chihiro?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_fujisaki_araara1">So, Chihiro, what is someone as adorable as you doing here?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_fujisaki_araara1">What is a girl as adorable as you doing in a game such as this, Chihiro?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="asuna_yuuki" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_asuna_association1">Is that an earpiece? Maybe you &lt;i&gt;are&lt;/i&gt; an association Fixer. Who are you with? Hana, maybe? Whatever your worlds equivalent of Hana Association is?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" marker="binah_asuna_association1">An interesting earpiece. Do you work for a Fixer Association by chance? Does your world even have the Associations?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="critical_darling" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_cdarling_musician1">You seem normal enough Ibuki, but I need to ask. You aren't a Musician of Bremen, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_cdarling_musician1">You don't look like it, but I should ask anyway. You aren't a Musician of Bremen, are you?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_cdarling_musician1">I may as well ask, Ibuki. You aren't a Musician of Bremen, are you? You seem normal enough.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="croix" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_croix_tech1">Tell me, Croix. What exactly is the purpose of those strange cubes? You mentioned tracking mental states?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_croix_tech1">Those cubes monitor mental states? What is the purpose of such, Croix?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_croix_tech1">What is the purpose of monitoring our mental states, Croix? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="cynthia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_cynthia_arbiter1">You have quite the oppressive aura, Cynthia. Perhaps you could even become an Arbiter.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_cynthia_arbiter1">You have many traits that would make for a good Arbiter, Cynthia.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="dark_magician_girl" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_dmg_qoh1">Tell me, Dark Magician Girl, does the name Queen of Hatred mean anything to you?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_dmg_kod1">Tell me, Dark Magician Girl, does the name Knight of Despair mean anything to you?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_dmg_kog1">Tell me, Dark Magician Girl, does the name King of Greed mean anything to you?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_dmg_sow1">Tell me, Dark Magician Girl, does the name Servant of Wrath mean anything to you?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_dmg_nihil1">Tell me, Dark Magician Girl, does the name Jester of Nihil mean anything to you?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="dorothy" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_dorothy_antirobot1">To think that someone created an abomination like yourself for the sole purpose of sexual pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png" marker="binah_dorothy_antirobot1">So you exist to fulfil sexual desires? What was the point of creating a mockery of humanity like yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_dorothy_antirobot1">Mocking humanity, all for an automated prostitute. Ridiculous.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="dust" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_dust_bladelineage1">Dust, were you a member of Blade Lineage at any point? Your hat reminds me of a member I met once.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_dust_bladelineage1">That hat reminds me of Kim. Were you associated with Blade Lineage?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_dust_bladelineage1">Huh, never thought I'd see a hat like that again. Do you have any association with Blade Lineage?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="aella" sayingMarker="AellaStalling" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" marker="binah_aella_stalling">Don't stall, Aella. Just get on with it. You know what you signed up for.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_aella_stalling">To try such a shameful ploy. You know what you signed up for - stop stalling.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_aella_stalling">Stalling, really? I expected more honor from you. Get on with it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9" oneShotId="28">
                <condition filter="maid_uniform" status="not_lost_some" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="355">A shame the uniform must come off. Frankly, I've always wanted a servant. Are you in the market for a master?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="239">Maybe now you'd consider calming down a little.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="240">Seeing people like you learn their place always brings a smile to my face.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="241">Maybe now you'll be a good ~target.ifMale(boy|girl)~, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="exhibitionist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" oneShotId="249">Someone seems a little eager.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="250">Ohohoh! It seems ~name~ was waiting for any chance to strip down for us.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" oneShotId="251">Amusing, I thought the goal was to avoid stripping - yet ~name~ couldn't be happier to undress.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="fancy" role="target" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" oneShotId="269">Take care, ~name~. Wouldn't want to get your expensive clothing dirty now.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" oneShotId="270">Soon you will learn that once your expensive silks fall, you are left with the same flesh as the rest of us.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" oneShotId="271">It appears money cannot buy you luck.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="indifferent" role="target" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" oneShotId="305">You seem rather unfazed, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" oneShotId="306">Not one to worry too much, ~name~? I can admire that.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="307">You may not be reacting much now, ~name~, but just you wait. I'll find how to make you squirm.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="lonely" role="target" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="314">Perhaps you and I are here for the same reasons, ~name~. After this game, would you like to have some tea?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="315">Do you want to enjoy some tea together, ~name~? After this game. I think we both are searching for new friends.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="316">I am glad to not be the only one in need of friends. Shall we talk after this game, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="moe" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="330">Aren't you just adorable, ~name~. I could just eat you up.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="329">I was in the market for a new toy. Are you up for the job, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="magical_girl" role="target" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" oneShotId="340">I swear they multiply every time I am not looking at them...</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" oneShotId="339">I thought there were only four of them? Now there's another?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="opp" character="cammy_white" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_cammy_fixer1">I'm curious, have you done any Fixer work, Cammy?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="opp" character="chazz" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_chazz_dueldisk1">So, is that duel disk some sort of weapon? I am curious as to what purpose it serves to you.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_chazz_dueldisk1">So what sort of purpose does that duel disk serve? Is it  a weapon?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_chazz_dueldisk1">Is your duel disk some sort of weapon? What purpose does it serve?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripping">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="0" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_kaz_apology1" />
                <condition role="opp" character="kaz" saidMarker="binah_resp0_1" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_kaz_apology2">No, so far in this game you appear, at the least, more charming. Regardless, I shouldn't make judgements until I know who you are as a person.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="4" />
                <condition role="opp" character="pyrrha" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_brock_pyrrha_rocketsave">The rocket came back? Watch out--- what? How did it... stop?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="0" saidMarker="AG_Binah_A1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_ag_syndicate1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_ag_syndicate2">I suppose I can understand the logic in that. You represent your organization. I wonder, is this Team Aqua by chance a Thumb subsidiary?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_ag_syndicate2">Yes, I can appreciate that. You wish to only be representing your Syndicate, and as such will keep your personal identity separate. May I ask, are you a subsidiary of The Thumb?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="asuna_yuuki" stage="0" saidMarker="binah_association0" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_asuna_association1" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_asuna_association2">I understand, yes. I suppose I have only really seen such prevalent with the Associations. But money does open many doors. May I ask what an Augma does?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="cheryl" stage="0" saidMarker="binah01" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_cheryl_comfort1" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_cheryl_comfort2">If you are certain. If you would like some tea to calm your nerves, feel free to ask.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="0" saidMarker="blake_binah_stories1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_blake_stories1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_blake_stories2">I am more a keeper of stories than an author. I have already had my own story end thrice. Perhaps you can help me pen my fourth?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="blake_belladonna" stage="0" saidMarker="blake_binah_stories1b" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_blake_stories1" />
                <state img="#-calm.png" marker="binah_blake_stories2">I am more a keeper of stories, than an author. I have already had my own story end thrice. Perhaps you can help me pen my fourth?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="caitlin" stage="0" saidMarker="binah_caitlin_experiments1R" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_caitlin_experiments1" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_caitlin_experiments2">Hmm, I see. So your abilities are natural then? How interesting...</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_caitlin_experiments2">So your abilities formed completely naturally? How intriguing...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jin" stage="0" saidMarker="jin_binah_fixer1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_jin_fixer2">Truly? That is rather intriguing. So perhaps yourself and I have something in common, no? We both were meant to protect our homes.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png" marker="binah_sannytess_futa1">Huh. So that is what you were hiding beneath your skirt. I must admit, I am certainly surprised.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="yuelia" stage="0" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_yuelia_transformation2">So, you simply were using the facade of a butterfly... What are you?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_yuelia_transformation2">How strange - just what are you, Yuelia? Using the facade of a butterfly...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_caulifla_supersaiyan2">What the hell!?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_caulifla_supersaiyan2">Gah! What is happening!?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_caulifla_supersaiyan2">What is this dominating force!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-anger.png" marker="binah_brock_loaded2">You idiot, why was it loaded!?</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png" marker="binah_brock_loaded2">It was &lt;i&gt;loaded&lt;/i&gt;!? Why did you bring it here &lt;i&gt;loaded&lt;/i&gt;!?</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png" marker="binah_brock_loaded2">What in the world were you thinking, bringing that here loaded!?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="brock" stage="4" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_brock_rocketkill">The rocket came back!? Is... is Brock dead?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="adrien" stage="1" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_adrien_ego2">Were you wearing E.G.O? I had no idea - I suppose I still have much to learn about it.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="cammy_white" stage="3" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_cammy_extralife2">Well... that is one way to buy yourself another round.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_cammy_extralife2">Ohohoh! I suppose you did buy yourself another round.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png" marker="binah_cammy_extralife2">Ohohoh! At least you get another round out of it.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_stripped">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="aqua_grunt" stage="1" saidMarker="AG_Binah_B1" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_ag_syndicate2" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" marker="binah_ag_syndicate3">Important? No. They control a fifth of all organized crime where I'm from. One of the five Fingers of The City. Part of the hand grasping the very throat of The City.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="asuna_yuuki" stage="1" saidMarker="binah_association0a" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_asuna_association2" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_asuna_association3">I see, I suppose that must be more common where you are from then. I only really wore mine when I worked for A Corp.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="kaz" stage="1" saidMarker="binah_resp0_2" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_kaz_apology2" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png" marker="binah_kaz_apology3">I suppose we shall see, Kaz. I hope I can make up for my kneejerk hostile reaction earlier, as well.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="target" character="jin" stage="1" saidMarker="jin_binah_fixer2" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" marker="binah_jin_fixer3">I am afraid I am far from heroic, my child. I have done many misdeeds, and many would label me villain. My repentance will take a lifetime.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="sannytess" stage="3" />
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="binah_sannytess_futa1" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png" marker="binah_sannytess_futa2">The procedure to get a member is available for women, but I have not seen anyone go for both sets. I suppose it would prove adaptable? I could see sex workers benefiting from such...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amy" stage="8" sayingMarker="planar_form" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_apocalypse">This power... Apocalypse...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="amalia" stage="5" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" marker="binah_amalia_flowers1">Well, my dear, it appears you have been reduced to nothing.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="caulifla" stage="2" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_caulifla_supersaiyan3">Such overwhelming power! What... are you? You are no human.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_caulifla_supersaiyan3">I've not felt this power before, what is it!?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png" marker="binah_caulifla_supersaiyan3">What is this power? What are &lt;i&gt;you!?&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="enf" status="naked" role="target" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="233">I do not understand why you were so scared to strip down, ~name~. You look wonderful, my darling.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="229">To think you were afraid to undress, ~name~. You are gorgeous.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="230">I quite enjoy seeing you strip down like this, ~name~. No need to be afraid.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="231">Be not afraid of exposing your flesh for us all, ~name~. Everyone will enjoy this memory, including you.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="232">Don't be so scared, ~name~. I haven't given you something to be afraid of, yet.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="bernadetta" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_bernie_carryaway">Worry not, my child. Wrap yourself up tight and enjoy yourself. Oh how I could just carry you off, Bernadetta.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png" marker="binah_bernie_carryaway">You look so adorable, all bundled up. I could just carry you off, Bernadetta.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="aggressive" role="target" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="245">Maybe this will help you calm down, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="246">Perhaps now you'll calm down a little, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition filter="exhibitionist" role="target" />
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="255">It seems both of us were waiting for this, ~name~. Go on, the floor is yours.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png" oneShotId="256">I always liked an overachiever, ~name~. Good ~target.ifMale(boy|girl)~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="opponent_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <condition role="target" character="9s" />
                <state img="#-bored.png" marker="binah_9S_nocum">Tsk, you couldn't even muster up some cum for me? Pathetic.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Are you ready to begin, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Set the stage for ~name~'s soliloquy of lust, everyone.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Be sure to put on a good performance for me, okay? You can do that, right?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">A shame I have hardly lost, I cannot offer much in terms of visual stimuli.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I cannot offer visual stimuli, but I can more than offer verbal stimuli.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">It would seem you are eliminated, ~name~. Now, go ahead and put a show on for us.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Looks like ~name~ has to pleasure himself, and we all get to watch. I can't wait.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Go ahead, ~name~, stroke yourself off for us all. I'm sure I can provide more than enough visual stimuli.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I won't blame you for watching me, I know I am quite attractive.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I wonder if I'll be pushed to the point of needing to do that. I hope not.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Well, it looks like you have been eliminated. Are you ready to begin your forfeit, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Do not be shy now. We are both so close to oblivion, after all. Why not let slip our inhibitions.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Well, at least I get a show for recompense. Do make it good, ~target~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Keep your eyes on me while you do this, okay? </state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Well, go ahead. Try and impress me, if you can.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Are you ready to join me? We can help each other - stimulate each other visually.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Now we can watch eachother, and help eachother reach the peak.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You and I, we can both enjoy the noises and gestures we both make.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Well, my darling. Don't let us keep you. Stroke it up and down, slowly for me.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Be a good boy and take your time, do not rush it too quickly. Let your orgasm slowly build, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do be a good boy and avoid pointing it at me, okay ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">How adorable. I am sure you know what makes you feel good, ~name~.  So just stick to that, okay?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Are you going to use me as inspiration, ~name~? I would like if you did.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Don't hold back any moans as you start, I want to hear you.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Good, now make sure to enjoy yourself ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I'll be sure to beat the others, and give you even more to use as inspiration.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Good, good. Stroke it nice and slow for me.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Hmm, it's been quite a long time since I was able to enjoy something like this. Please, do make it good for me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Hah, my goodness. I can't wait to see you experience ecstasy. I will be experiencing it with you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Let us both help eachother, my darling.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">So hard, is that because of me, by chance?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Are you enjoying yourself, ~name~? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">That's it, keep it up ~name~. Up,  down, up, down. Keep a good pace, okay? Good boy.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Let me hear that voice. Don't keep it from me, okay? Let it &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; out.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">The look on your face is so very delightful, ~name~. The way it twists in pleasure, I wish to never forget it.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Goodness, you really are giving it your all. Do you enjoy being watched this much?</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I wonder, it is a bit of a vulgar though but... No, I wouldn't want to mix anything into my tea. Even if the idea is erotic.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">What are you imagining, ~name~? Are you fantasizing of a lover? Someone back home? Perhaps someone here? Are you even, by chance, thinking erotic thoughts of me?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Is this how you usually do it? Or do you usually employ a different technique? Simply do what you find most natural, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You truly are enjoying this, aren't you? Pathetic. Shameful. Do be reduced to a mewling mess, stroking your cock for strangers.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Good boy, continue desperately stroking yourself off. Are you hoping for relief in front of a group of strangers?</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Just look at how he &lt;i&gt;throbs&lt;/i&gt;. Fantastic.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Make sure to give the head some attention.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I wonder how it tastes...</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Just a touch wouldn't hurt, right? </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Keep stroking, keep your eyes on me.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">So handsome, the way your cock &lt;i&gt;throbs&lt;/i&gt; for me.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I wish you and I could forgo hands, and use our bodies to please one another.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah, hah, nngh- hah!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Amazing, my darling. So, &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt;, amazing.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Don't turn your gaze, I want to be the reason you cum.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">You don't need to do anything but this, I can keep you as a pet. I can keep you for myself.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;Please, please, please, please, please, please.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You're enjoying this, aren't you? Don't you wish you could fuck me right now, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">So sweet, such a pathetic little thing. You want me, you &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">What are you thinking of doing to me, ~name~? Go on, let spill your fantasies.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="male_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Hahaha, look at how much it shot out all over the place.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">You really let a lot out, didn't you? Did it feel &lt;i&gt;that &lt;/i&gt;good?</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">Did you enjoy yourself, ~name~? Ohoho, I suppose I did as well.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">So much, you really did enjoy showing off. What a good boy you are.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-laughing.png">My underwear was enough to inspire all that, hmm? I am flattered, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Goodness, I feel a little wetter just witnessing that...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">My dearest ~name~, I am glad to see you enjoyed yourself. Such a good boy.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Well, how did it feel my darling? Did you get what you needed out of it?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">That look on your face, ~name~. The things I would do to see it again.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I am glad you enjoyed yourself, and I am glad to have been part of the reason you did.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Were you pent up, ~name~? Perhaps you need me to help you again?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Did I inspire this? I am glad I was of service, then.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Such a big load, a shame it went to waste. I would have taken it happily.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Good boy, you made me very happy today.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_must_masturbate">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">So now it is time for ~name~'s forfeit, hmm? I am intrigued, I must admit.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go on, ~name~, do not be shy. I want to see it all, after all.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Be good, and I might just adopt you as my pet. You could come and stay with me, does that sound fun?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I will be watching with bated breath, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I must say, I am curious to see just how long it takes you to finish.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Go ahead, ~name~, put on a show for me- or well, for us. </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Alright darling, you may use me as inspiration. Think of the things you and I could do together later.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Have a good time, darling. Make sure you enjoy yourself, and to keep your eyes on me.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Put on a good show dear. I might just take you home with me if you're good. Okay, ~name~?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">My darling, I hope you are not feeling too shy. Just keep your eyes on me if it helps, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">~name~, my sweet, I wish to watch. You can keep your eyes on me in turn.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I was waiting to see you reach this point all game, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I would be lying if I said I didn't want this to happen all game.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">You know what you signed up for, my dear. I see no reason to hold back.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Be a good girl, won't you? Put a good show on for me, and I will reward you.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Wonderful, this is what I was waiting for. Now come join me, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I have waited all night for this, ~name~. Do not disappoint me.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_start_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Are you comfortable, ~name~? Ready to begin? </state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I cannot provide visual stimuli, so just keep my words and promises of action.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Now keep yourself comfortable, my dear. I cannot wait to see how much you enjoy yourself.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Please try and think of me as you do this, of all the things I have said and promised to do if we were to spend a night together.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">What a wonderful sight, I'll struggle to focus on the game with the cute mewling noises I'm sure you'll hear.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make sure to not stifle your adorable noises, the auditory part of sex is just as good as the visual.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Worry not, ~name~, I will provide more visual stimuli. Not by myself, by beating the others.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Make sure to keep me in your thoughts as you please yourself, my darling ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7 9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Go on, my sweet. Do well, and I will perhaps show you my techniques in person. Would you like that, ~name~?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">You look so wet, ~name~. Look how your arousal drips down your thighs. Is that my fault?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I do not wish to be too forward, ~name~, but I want to keep you like one would keep a pet. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Beautiful, I am glad to see you joining me. Wish to follow my technique, or are you skilled in the area?</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Use my form as visual stimulation, and my- &lt;i&gt;nngh&lt;/i&gt; -voice as audio stimulation.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I wish we could help eachother get off, ~name~, but maybe we can do such another time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <condition role="target" character="amalia" />
                <state img="#-shocked.png">So odd...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">With a giant... plant?</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">I suppose that's one way to do it...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I've not ever thought of it like that.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I suppose if it works...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Interesting...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Intriguing...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Strange...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">How odd...</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">How interesting...</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">How strange...</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">How odd...</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Fantastic...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7 9">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Keep it up, ~name~, I can hear how wet you are from here.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I can tell you are enjoying yourself. Make sure to apply some focus to your clit.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do not hold back on our account. Please yourself how you would at home, all that matters is your physical pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I wonder if I am a help to that pleasure you are feeling. Maybe you can experience an orgasm caused by me firsthand, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" oneShotId="9" marker="TeaBodyshot">I have heard of bodyshots before, and I once thought about that with tea but... Now I realize that would be painful. Ignore this, that was a silly idea...</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Do you touch yourself often, ~name~? You seem quite experienced.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Have you perhaps awakened to the idea of being watched? Do you even think you may struggle to climax without an audience from here on?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">The way ~name~ is going all out, crying out for us as she pleases herself. Oh, it is hard to focus on the game, almost, with her lovely voice leaking out.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Your moans bring me the greatest pleasure, ~name~. I always loved the noises people made involuntarily. I much prefer to be the reason they make them, though.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Do not hold back, ~name~. I want to know how you are feeling.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Are you thinking of me? You should be.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Delicious, and I don't just mean my tea.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">A treat for all of my senses.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Hah, we're going at the same pace. It is almost romantic, ~name~. </state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">The way your face contorts, and the noises that escapes your throat. Both are so adorable, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">~name~, please, let me hear your voice. Please call my name, darling.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I want to own you. I want to inflict both pain and pleasure upon you in equal measure. I apologize, but I cannot contain my true feelings.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I will take care of you, ~name~. I will tie you up, keep you fed and happy. You will be in my service.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Oh, the things I would do to you given the chance.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I want you, I &lt;i&gt;need&lt;/i&gt; you. Please be mine, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">What an adorable little pet you'd make, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">So beautiful, you are such a beautiful woman, ~name~.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Am I making you happy, ~name~? Do you like the sounds I make in your presence?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Goodness, she is really going at it.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Giving it your all, ~name~? I appreciate it.</state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Are you almost at the brink? </state>
                <state img="#-flirty.png">Go on, let it all out.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Give me your all, ~name~. Go on, cry out my name.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="female_finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="0-3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You really enjoyed yourself, ~name~. It makes me happy that I contributed to it.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">That was a delight to watch, ~name~. Maybe next time, you can call out my name.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Those noises you made, it will be hard not to remember them tonight.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">What a good girl, you put on such a wonderful show for us, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4-5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You had a cute look on your face as you climaxed, ~name~, I would love to see it again.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do you need help cleaning up? If you come back with me afterwards, I'll happily lick you clean.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Maybe next time, I can be the one who made you cum.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Such a wonderful sight. What a good girl you turned out to be, ~name~.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6-7">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Goodness, you looked fantastic as you reached climax.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Goodness, the way your body &lt;i&gt;quaked&lt;/i&gt; as you found release. I felt my own body shake as well.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">The things you inspire in me. I feel like a mighty beast, gazing down at a hapless deer. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">So beautiful, what a wonderful sound you made my darling.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">So wonderful, I can only imagine I had a large part to play in your &lt;i&gt;explosive&lt;/i&gt; finale.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Did you enjoy, my sweet ~name~? Now watch, I am not far behind.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I wonder if I sounded similar when I reached my own climax...</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Some call an orgasm &lt;i&gt;"la petite mort"&lt;/i&gt;, an ancient barbaric languages term for &lt;i&gt;"the little death"&lt;/i&gt;.  So tell me, ~name~, how did your little death feel?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I almost wish to go again, this time we can more directly please one another.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate_first">
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-anger.png">I was truly the first out? Damn it all, fine. I will accept my defeat, I suppose.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I cannot truly believe I lost first.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I lost first? Did I truly play so poorly? </state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I will have my revenge, mark my words.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="must_masturbate">
            <case stage="7">
                <condition role="self" consecutiveLosses="8" />
                <state img="#-anger.png">This is... Fucking bullshit!</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-calm.png">You've proven yourself, now witness me with your own eyes.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Then I shall draw from the well once more, congratulations.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Have you ever witnessed a star with your own eyes, ~player~?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="start_masturbating">
            <case stage="7" oneShotId="3">
                <condition role="opp" character="yuno_uno" sayingMarker="yuno_binah_pillar_reactionA" />
                <state img="#-pillar.png" marker="binah_yuno_pillarA">Worry not, this pillar is not a weapon today. It is a part of the powers forced upon me. Today, it is simply a stage in which my performance begins.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7" id="1">
                <state img="#-pillar.png">Ah, this brings me back to my senses.</state>
                <state img="#-pillar.png">You've proven yourself. Now witness me with your eyes.</state>
                <state img="#-pillar.png">Rise. Collapse. Resonate.</state>
                <state img="#-pillar.png">The waves will rock the shore again.</state>
                <state img="#-pillar.png">I'll open the door if I must.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="masturbating">
            <case stage="8" oneShotId="17">
                <condition role="self" timeInStage="0" />
                <test expr="~background.category~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-thinking.png">To be doing this in a library is, frankly, quite natural. I only really had this sort of free time whilst in one, after all.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-aroused.png">So good, I rarely get a moment alone.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Please, &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt;, witness me, ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Don't stop watching - I feel it building.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="218">Why am I thinking of &lt;i&gt;her&lt;/i&gt; at a time like this?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">Oh goodness, I--- &lt;i&gt;guh&lt;/i&gt; ---I cannot get enough of this.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Pleasure and pain exist together, which do you prefer?</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Don't you &lt;i&gt;dare&lt;/i&gt; take your eyes off me.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I never got a chance to just be a woman, ~player~. Please watch me, please.</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">I always wanted to do something like this, I never realized just how much.</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah, hah, guh- nngh- hah!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-pleased.png">Are you watching, ~player~? Do you like what you see?</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png">I wish one of you could come assist me; I am sure we could both bring each other to the brink.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">Goodness, I had no idea it felt so good with an audience.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png" oneShotId="217">Have you ever seen a woman in this state, ~player~? I have my doubts.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Hah, I needed this. I really, really needed this.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Dammit, I needed this.</state>
                <state img="#-anger.png">Oh, how I needed this. I needed to blow off some steam.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Guh&lt;/i&gt;! It still feels so odd to have a crowd.</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Fuck!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Shit!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-annoyed.png">&lt;i&gt;Dammit!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Are you watching me? So good - keep your eyes on me, ~player~.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Don't you dare look away. I yearn for your gaze.</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">Keep watching - keep watching!</state>
                <state img="#-bored.png">&lt;i&gt;Mmmpf&lt;/i&gt;- this is so new. I love this experience.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Are you enjoying the show?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Do you like what you see, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">Am I what you look for in a partner, ~player~? Perhaps, I can become what you need?</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">Sorry, I still am new to this experience...</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">This is still so new to me, I do feel &lt;i&gt;some&lt;/i&gt; shyness.</state>
                <state img="#-haughty.png">I am still a woman. Even I can feel bashful...</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah- nngh- haaah!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">So incredible- so incredible!</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I can feel my reservations slipping away.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">What is going through your mind, ~player~?</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png" oneShotId="228">I wonder what Gebura would think - seeing me like this.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I wonder if I could - &lt;i&gt;hah&lt;/i&gt; - surprise that nobleman this way.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">&lt;i&gt;Ooh!&lt;/i&gt; Such a sudden spark of pleasure.</state>
                <state img="#-shocked.png">&lt;i&gt;Hah!&lt;/i&gt; Oh that felt very good.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">Don't you wish you could be the one making me mewl?</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">I am certain you wish you were allowed to have your way with me.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">That hunger in your gaze, ~player~ - it is adorable.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Such carnal pleasure; this risks addictions.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I  wonder how much better it would feel with a partner.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Would a partner increase this pleasure? Twofold? More?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="heavy_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-heavya.png" oneShotId="221">&lt;i&gt;I'm so close, I can feel it building up!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavya.png" oneShotId="222">&lt;i&gt;Please, witness me. Witness me!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png" oneShotId="223">&lt;i&gt;Guh, hah- hah! Nngh- fffffuck!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyb.png" oneShotId="224">&lt;i&gt;My mind is going blank, how have I not experienced this before!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyc.png" oneShotId="225">&lt;i&gt;It's coming, I'm near - witness me please!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-heavyc.png" oneShotId="226">&lt;i&gt;Hah- gyah! Ngh, mmpf! So close. So close!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="227">&lt;i&gt;Every great story comes with a climax, here comes mine.&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finishing_masturbating">
            <case stage="8">
                <state img="#-climax.png">&lt;i&gt;FUCK- HAAAAH!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png" marker="ClimaxAngela">&lt;i&gt;HAH- HAH- ANGELA!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png" marker="ClimaxGebura">&lt;i&gt;Please, PLEASE, GEBURA!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png" marker="ClimaxGebura">&lt;i&gt;S-so goood- hah- HAH! KALI!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png" marker="ClimaxAyin">&lt;i&gt;Manager, manager, mmpf- AYIN!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png" marker="ClimaxRoland">&lt;i&gt; Harder, don't hold back. Come- ROLAND!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png" marker="ClimaxPlayer">&lt;i&gt; It's so close- please- ~PLAYER~!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png" marker="ClimaxZena">&lt;i&gt; Punish me, make me yours- ZENA!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
                <state img="#-climax.png" marker="ClimaxBaral">&lt;i&gt; I'm so close, I- BARAL!&lt;/i&gt;</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="finished_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-finished.png">Goodness... I did make quite the mess, didn't I?</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="after_masturbating">
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ClimaxAngela" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" oneShotId="57">Well, I can't help but feel Angela knows I called her name out during my climax. </state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ClimaxAyin" />
                <state img="#-haughty.png" oneShotId="59">I cannot believe that bastard entered my thoughts. I suppose he wasn't... The worst looking.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ClimaxBaral" />
                <state img="#-pleased.png" oneShotId="61">A shame he wasn't one of my Claws. He was always such a charming man.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ClimaxGebura" />
                <state img="#-annoyed.png" oneShotId="63">Please, do me a favor. Never let that woman know I cried her name out. It would go straight to her head.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ClimaxPlayer" />
                <state img="#-flirty.png" oneShotId="66">My apologies, ~player~. I could not get you out of my head. I feel a strong attraction towards you, as of this moment.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ClimaxRoland" />
                <state img="#-pensive.png" oneShotId="69">A shame, I do not think he is open to a relationship with me. I think I scared the poor man...</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="ClimaxZena" />
                <state img="#-smug.png" oneShotId="72">Despite what Zena would say, I will always be her better. I trained her, after all. She wishes to be on the level of an Arbiter that I was. What a cute little raven.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <condition role="self" saidMarker="IndependentReadingTime" />
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="136" marker="TheWingQuote">“I regretted that I had gone out. I wanted a long, sound sleep, forgetting all this fatigue. I wanted a good, long sleep.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="137" marker="TheWingQuote">“Every day I am fated to die. When I awake from the sleep I have been sleeping - how long ago did I begin this sleep that I sleep - a bone-painful life resumes and even though I lie down and cover myself with blankets, I witness the squandering of my youth.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="138" marker="FaustQuote">“Oh my, but art is long and our life is fleeting."</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="139" marker="FaustQuote">“Men’s wretchedness in soothe I so deplore, not even I would plague the sorry creatures more.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="140" marker="FaustQuote">“All theory is gray, my friend. But forever green is the tree of life.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="141" marker="FaustQuote">“If I wasn't a devil myself I'd give Me up to the Devil this very minute.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="142" marker="DonQuixoteQuote">“The truth may be stretched thin, but it never breaks, and it always surfaces above lies, as oil floats on water.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="143" marker="DonQuixoteQuote">“When life itself seems lunatic, who knows where madness lies? Perhaps to be too practical is madness. To surrender dreams — this may be madness. Too much sanity may be madness — and maddest of all: to see life as it is, and not as it should be!”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="144" marker="DonQuixoteQuote">“For neither good nor evil can last for ever; and so it follows that as evil has lasted a long time, good must now be close at hand.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="145" marker="DonQuixoteQuote">“It is one thing to write as poet and another to write as a historian: the poet can recount or sing about things not as they were, but as they should have been, and the historian must write about them not as they should have been, but as they were, without adding or subtracting anything from the truth.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="146" marker="HellScreenQuote">“I could have sworn that the man's eyes were no longer watching his daughter dying in agony, that instead the gorgeous colors of flames and the sight of a woman suffering in them were giving him joy beyond measure.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="147" marker="HellScreenQuote">“He felt so lost, he said later, that the familiar studio felt like a haunted valley deep in the mountains, with the smell of rotting leaves, the spray of a waterfall, the sour fumes of fruit stashed away by a monkey; even the dim glow of the master's oil lamp on its tripod looked to him like misty moonlight in the hills.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="148" marker="HellScreenQuote">“Still more horrible was the color of the flames that licked the latticed cabin vents before shooting skyward, as though - might I say? - the sun itself had crashed to earth, spewing its heavenly fire in all directions.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="149" marker="HellScreenQuote">“People used to say that on moonless nights Her Ladyship's broad-skirted scarlet trousers would glide eerily along the outdoor corridor, never touching the floor.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="150" marker="TheStrangerQuote">“I looked up at the mass of signs and stars in the night sky and laid myself open for the first time to the benign indifference of the world.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="151" marker="TheStrangerQuote">“Since we're all going to die, it's obvious that when and how don't matter.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="152" marker="TheStrangerQuote">“I realized then that a man who had lived only one day could easily live for a hundred years in prison. He would have enough memories to keep him from being bored”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="153" marker="TheStrangerQuote">“Mother died today. Or maybe yesterday; I can't be sure.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="154" marker="DoRCQuote">“The cunning waste their pains;&lt;br&gt; The wise men vex their brains; &lt;br&gt; But the simpleton, who seeks no gains, &lt;br&gt; With belly full, he wanders free &lt;br&gt;As drifting boat upon the sea.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="155" marker="DoRCQuote">“When grief for fiction’s idle words &lt;br&gt;More real than human life appears, &lt;br&gt;Reflect that life itself’s a dream &lt;br&gt;And do not mock the reader’s tears.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="156" marker="DoRCQuote">“No remedy but love&lt;br&gt; Can make the lovesick well; &lt;br&gt;Only the hand that tied the knot &lt;br&gt;Can loose the tiger’s bell.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="157" marker="DoRCQuote">“Better by far the destiny of plant or stone, bereft of knowledge and consciousness, but blessed at least with purity and peace of mind!”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="158" marker="WutheringHeightsQuote">“Be with me always - take any form - drive me mad! Only do not leave me in this abyss, where I cannot find you! Oh, God! It is unutterable! I can not live without my life! I can not live without my soul!”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="159" marker="WutheringHeightsQuote">“If he loved with all the powers of his puny being, he couldn't love as much in eighty years as I could in a day.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="160" marker="WutheringHeightsQuote">“I have not broken your heart - you have broken it; and in breaking it, you have broken mine.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="161" marker="WutheringHeightsQuote">“I gave him my heart, and he took and pinched it to death; and flung it back to me. People feel with their hearts, Ellen, and since he has destroyed mine, I have not power to feel for him.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="162" marker="MobyDickQuote">“As for me, I am tormented with an everlasting itch for things remote. I love to sail forbidden seas, and land on barbarous coasts.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="163" marker="MobyDickQuote">“There are certain queer times and occasions in this strange mixed affair we call life when a man takes this whole universe for a vast practical joke, though the wit thereof he but dimly discerns, and more than suspects that the joke is at nobody's expense but his own.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="164" marker="MobyDickQuote">“Human madness is oftentimes a cunning and most feline thing. When you think it fled, it may have but become transfigured into some still subtler form.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="165" marker="MobyDickQuote">“Think not, is my eleventh commandment; and sleep when you can, is my twelfth.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="166" marker="CrimeAndPunishmentQuote">“We sometimes encounter people, even perfect strangers, who begin to interest us at first sight, somehow suddenly, all at once, before a word has been spoken.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="167" marker="CrimeAndPunishmentQuote">“I did not bow down to you, I bowed down to all the suffering of humanity.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="168" marker="CrimeAndPunishmentQuote">“The man who has a conscience suffers whilst acknowledging his sin. That is his punishment.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="169" marker="CrimeAndPunishmentQuote">“And the more I drink the more I feel it. That's why I drink too. I try to find sympathy and feeling in drink.... I drink so that I may suffer twice as much!”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="170" marker="DemianQuote">“The bird fights its way out of the egg. The egg is the world. Who would be born must first destroy a world. The bird flies to God. That God's name is Abraxas.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="171" marker="DemianQuote">“Those who are too lazy and comfortable to think for themselves and be their own judges obey the laws. Others sense their own laws within them.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="172" marker="DemianQuote">“You've never lived what you are thinking, and that isn't good. Only the ideas we actually live are of any value.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="173" marker="DemianQuote">“I wanted only to live in accord with the promptings which came from my true self. Why was that so very difficult?”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="174" marker="TheOdysseyQuote">“There is nothing more admirable than when two people who see eye to eye keep house as man and wife, confounding their enemies and delighting their friends.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="175" marker="TheOdysseyQuote">“A man who has been through bitter experiences and traveled far enjoys even his sufferings after a time”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="176" marker="TheOdysseyQuote">“Be strong, saith my heart; I am a soldier; &lt;br&gt;I have seen worse sights than this.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="177" marker="TheOdysseyQuote">“Men are so quick to blame the gods: they say that we devise their misery. But they themselves- in their depravity- design grief greater than the griefs that fate assigns.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="178" marker="MetamorphosisQuote">“As Gregor Samsa awoke one morning from uneasy dreams he found himself transformed in his bed into a gigantic insect.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="179" marker="MetamorphosisQuote">“He was a tool of the boss, without brains or backbone.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="180" marker="MetamorphosisQuote">“Was he an animal, that music could move him so? He felt as if the way to the unknown nourishment he longed for were coming to light.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="181" marker="MetamorphosisQuote">“The door could not be heard slamming; they had probably left it open, as is the custom in homes where a great misfortune has occurred.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="182" marker="DivineComedyQuote">“O human race, born to fly upward, wherefore at a little wind dost thou so fall?”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="183" marker="DivineComedyQuote">“The man who lies asleep will never waken fame, and his desire and all his life drift past him like a dream, and the traces of his memory fade from time like smoke in air, or ripples on a stream.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="184" marker="DivineComedyQuote">“The day that man allows true love to appear, those things which are well made will fall into confusion and will overturn everything we believe to be right and true.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="185" marker="DivineComedyQuote">“There, pride, avarice, and envy are the tongues men know and heed, a Babel of despair”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="186" marker="OrlandoFuriosoQuote">“Nature made him, and then broke the mold.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="187" marker="OrlandoFuriosoQuote">“...She can raise from the tomb those of whom she speaks or writes, and make them live forever.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="188" marker="ClockworkOrangeQuote">“The important thing is moral choice. Evil has to exist along with good, in order that moral choice may operate. Life is sustained by the grinding opposition of moral entities.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="189" marker="ClockworkOrangeQuote">“Goodness is something chosen. When a man cannot choose he ceases to be a man.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="190" marker="ClockworkOrangeQuote">“It's funny how the colors of the real world only seem really real when you watch them on a screen.”</state>
                <state img="#-quoth.png" oneShotId="191" marker="ClockworkOrangeQuote">“If he can only perform good or only perform evil, then he is a clockwork orange—meaning that he has the appearance of an organism lovely with colour and juice but is in fact only a clockwork toy to be wound up by God or the Devil.”</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-aroused.png" oneShotId="115">I'm still feeling some tingles.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png" oneShotId="117">What an enjoyable game.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png" oneShotId="116" marker="IndependentReadingTime">I do wonder what most people do when they finish. I can't really think of anything, so I may just read.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_victory">
            <case stage="0-7">
                <condition role="opp" character="mitama" sayingMarker="binah_victory" />
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">I suppose a winner does need a prize. Are you offering yourself, Mitama?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0-7">
                <test expr="~background.category~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-calm.png">While I am here, I may as well browse the book selection. Anyone wish to join me?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="0">
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I do not even need to redress. I shall make my leave.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">You could not even get me to remove my cloak. Truly, the threat of an arbiter was too much for you all.</state>
                <state img="#-laughing.png">I would say good work, but you did not even beat me once. A shame, is it not?</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="2">
                <state img="#-calm.png">A victory for me, and I hardly had to expose much.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">You got me into a more casual state, at the least.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I expect better next time, okay?</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">That was fun for me, but did you get what you wanted out of your time with me? Feel free to challenge me again, when you learn to play.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="1">
                <state img="#-calm.png">A win with minimal losses, that is the goal for all of my missions.</state>
                <state img="#-smug.png">All you were able to get was my cloak. Pathetic.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">I suppose you did beat me at least once. Still, you will need to do better next time.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="3">
                <state img="#-calm.png">Not enough,but good effort. I lost more than I expected.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I shall return to my home to repose now, good efforts everyone.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">Now, sink into everlasting quietude.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="4">
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I won, even if it meant taking off my shirt. Still, this should motivate you to beat me next time.</state>
                <state img="#-calm.png">&lt;i&gt;(Yawns)&lt;/i&gt; The sandman calls me.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">You missed the opportunity.</state>
                <state img="#-sadistic.png">Do not dare to stand before me.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="5">
                <state img="#-calm.png">At least I won, that is what matters anyway.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">Down to my underwear, but at least I won.</state>
                <state img="#-thinking.png">I at least managed to win without exposing my body fully.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="6">
                <state img="#-teatime.png">That was a close victory, but you did not succeed this time.</state>
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I almost thought I was about to lose there. Glad that it was avoided, even if just barely.</state>
                <state img="#-pensive.png">I almost lost there. But the keyword is almost, you need to do better to truly be victorious.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="7">
                <state img="#-pensive.png">You pushed me to the brink, bent my back, and exposed me. I won, but at a high cost. Until next time, ~player~.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

        <trigger id="game_over_defeat">
            <case stage="9">
                <test expr="~background.category~" value="library" />
                <state img="#-teatime.png">I may stay here awhile longer, if it is alright. I wish to explore the selection of books available. Care to join me, ~winner~? I will remain undressed, just for you.</state>
            </case>
            <case stage="9">
                <state img="#-anger.png">Congratulations, ~name~, you defeated me. But it will not happen next time.</state>
            </case>
        </trigger>

    </behaviour>
</opponent>
